Rue is in love with Jules, I think.
Hey, I'm Ethan.
I'm Kat.
You look different.
I changed.
'Sup, Cass.
You wanna ride the carousel?
That's the guy from the motel.
- You're beautiful.
- Thank you.
- That's Nate's dad?!
- Yes. That's Nate's dad.
Hey. Tyler?
God, are you broken inside.
I went through Nate's
phone, and it was weird.
I need you to promise me that
you're not gonna tell a soul.
I'm sorry I got so angry at you before.
Maddy knew who she was
from a very early age.
For as long as Maddy could
remember, everybody loved her.
♪ You must be my lucky star ♪
♪ 'Cause you shine on
me wherever you are ♪
She never knew exactly what it was.
She just knew that she
had something special,
something intangible,
something immeasurable.
♪ Star light, star bright,
first star I see tonight ♪
♪ Star light, star bright ♪
And it gave her confidence.
That's why she loved pageantry,
because you didn't have to be
the prettiest or the tallest
or the blondest or the whitest.
You just had to have fucking confidence.
And she probably would have
gone on to win Miss Universe,
if it weren't for... this guy.
A beauty pageant coach,
Marcus Cutler was arrested today
on 18 counts of child molestation.
That's it. You're done. No
more pageants. This is sick.
Her dreams were dashed by some random,
50-year-old creep who didn't molest her,
let alone even meet her.
She refused to eat for
a week out of protest.
Drama!
But then she realized how much
she liked not doing anything.
Maddy would never say it out loud,
especially not today, because
everybody's so political,
but she never really had any
desire to have a career... or job.
She was just interested
in doing what she did,
just, without school and
the other bullshit.
Her mother was an esthetician.
Which is a fancy way of saying she
gave pedicures to rich people.
And her dad was a drunk,
who was always pretending to
hold jobs longer than he did.
She quickly realized that there are
two kinds of people in the world:
people who sit in the chairs
with their feet in the footbath,
and the people who kneel
in front of the footbath.
She used to sit and study
the women who came in.
She'd pay attention to what they wore,
what they'd talk about,
and what she realized was that none
of them actually did anything.
I mean, they may have,
like, children to raise
or homes to decorate, but
at the end of the day,
they literally did nothing.
They literally did...
nothing.
And strangely, none of
them had confidence.
She had had a thing
for Nate for a while,
before he finally asked her out.
And at first, he was a gentleman,
like, flowers every day
kind of gentleman.
- And he was smarter than most guys.
- Maddy.
- Plus, Nate, like, really loved her.
- You're so sweet.
I love you.
I love you, too.
And she did love Nate.
She loved her relationship with Nate.
She was also a really good girlfriend.
Granted, she didn't
always tell the truth.
You're a virgin?
Because the truth-truth
is that when she was 14,
on vacation in Panama City Beach,
she met a guy who was, like, 40.
Hey. You from around here?
Which in retrospect seems
kind of rape-y and weird,
but honestly, she was
the one in control.
Yeah.
She could tell by looking in Nate's eyes
- how much it meant to him.
- Like fully?
Yeah.
That she was a hundred percent his.
What about, like, have
you ever been fingered?
Only my own.
Plus, it's not like anyone can
feel the fucking difference.
But that's the thing
with guys like Nate.
They don't actually want a person.
They want something they can own
and possess.
Like Sharon Stone in Casino.
But the cool thing about
Sharon Stone in Casino
is that she ran the fuck over De Niro.
I would fucking kill for that coat.
And she did the same to Nate.
How much do you think it costs?
Seriously, Sharon Stone
in Casino was, like,
Maddy's spirit animal.
She also watched a lot of porn.
Not because it turned her
on or anything, it didn't.
But if you analyzed it really closely,
there were a ton of really good secrets.
Sometimes, during sex,
she would imagine she
was a ventriloquist
controlling her body...
Moving her hips and arching her
back in just the right way.
She wanted Nate to feel good
about the way he fucked.
Because if you make a guy
feel confident and powerful,
well, they'll do anything.
- That one.
- I got you a present.
Really?
After dinner. It's in the car.
Oh, my God, it's perfect!
- I fucking love you.
- I fucking love you, too.
She did worry about the whole
monogamy thing, though.
It's not like she ever cheated-cheated.
But every now and then, she'd find
herself in, like, a gray area.
I'll do anything to fuck you.
You're so sweet... but no.
Except for that DJ who said
he opened for Calvin Harris.
And the stockbroker guy with the
family who lived on Oak Street.
And hot dude who ran the roller rink.
But honestly, those were all times
when Nate and her were on a break.
Plus, Nate could be a real asshole.
And sometimes, Maddy fantasized
about punching Nate.
But because of who he was as a person,
she was afraid he'd hit her back.
Especially because he was coming
to terms with his sexuality.
You're fucking dead to me.
It's, like, the root
of a lot of violence.
And when she got home that night,
she felt sick to her stomach...
like enough to throw up.
It wasn't the violence that scared her.
It was the fact that she
knew no matter what he did,
she'd still love him.
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com
Nothing in the world
comes close to opiates.
A good ES 7.5 Vicodin? Fuck.
But honestly, the best
thing I've ever had
is fentanyl.
And there is not a thing on the planet
Earth that compares to fentanyl.
Except Jules.
Jules is a close second.
Jules, Jules, Jules.
And then you know what would
be better? Jules and fentanyl.
But I can't do both, 'cause
Jules won't have me.
So for now, I'll choose Jules.
- Rue, dinner's ready.
- Okay.
- Are you coming?
- Yeah. No.
Yeah. For... aah... For dinner.
- Just, uh, give me a second.
- Okay.
You two have a good
time at the carnival?
- Yeah, it was cool.
- It was all right.
Rue said you got sick on the Gravitron.
I don't want to talk about it.
So...
Jules slept over last night?
Yeah. So?
Are you two in a relationship?
I mean, yeah, kinda.
It may not matter what I think, but...
I really like her.
Yeah, me, too.
Baby, just take your time.
You've come a long way.
You're delicate.
- I'm not delicate.
- Yes, you are.
It's fine, Mom. We, um...
We had a really long conversation
about everything, and...
we're just gonna take
things really, really slow.
♪ Okay, I'm Rambo, I ramshack ♪
♪ I'm next to that
cheese like rattraps ♪
♪ On top of that green like grass ass ♪
♪ That's over y'all head... ♪
Yo. Looks good.
You ready?
Um...
How bad does it hurt?
It didn't hurt, like, at all.
It's all good. I've been
doing this for years.
I love you, Rue,
but there's no fucking
way I'm doing that.
I didn't know what happened
the night Jules met Tyler.
I knew it wasn't good,
but I was afraid to pry.
And selfishly, things had
been going really well.
Show me exactly where the holdup is.
Granted, after the carnival,
things got really fucking weird.
Hey, I gotta call you back.
Slow down.
Slow down. What's happened?
I'll meet you out front.
Thank you for coming down, Mr. Jacobs.
Do you want to tell me what's going on?
Let's talk when we get inside.
- Cal, you okay?
- Yeah. Need a second.
Now, what had happened was...
that morning, Maddy went to school.
What are you, the Unabomber?
What are you, a dominatrix?
- No.
- I didn't mean for real, bitch.
Obviously.
But seriously, are you okay?
Yeah. I'm just on my period.
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
And Maddy's first class was
Intro to Calc in room 202,
which unfortunately was in the
upper left wing of the school.
Is the air conditioner,
like, not working?
It's broken. You could
always take off your hoodie.
Now, if it was a normal day,
Maddy would have just
taken off her hoodie.
But since Nate choked her,
Maddy woke up three hours early,
applied more concealer
than a burn victim,
and tried her best to cover up.
To compound the problem,
she also suffered from
a drop in serotonin
from the Molly she took at
the carnival, got depressed,
and therefore hadn't had anything
to eat or drink the entire weekend.
Plus, she actually was on her period.
Maddy?
She's in here.
I'm fine. Why is everyone,
like, so dramatic?
Obviously, you've been
through a lot this weekend.
But my real concern is the
bruising on your neck.
There is no bruising on my neck.
- Mm. Paramedics saw it.
- Yeah, well, they're lying.
Madeleine, look.
I understand that you may be afraid
to talk about how you got hurt.
But I want you to know
that it is not your fault.
I'm trying to find a really
respectful way to say this.
But, um, this doesn't concern you.
It does concern me, Madeleine.
You're 17 years old.
If I suspect that you're being abused,
I'm mandated by law to report it.
Fuck.
Was it someone you know?
Was it Nate Jacobs?
All I know is she, like, knocked
over a giant pot of chili
and, like, called his
mother the "C" word.
I mean, he did, like,
grab her by the arm.
Yo, straight up? The chick's crazy.
Do you know why Nate and
Maddy were fighting?
Um, I don't wanna talk
until I get a lawyer.
You're not being charged with anything.
Look, Nate's gay.
I'm being serious, Barbara.
No, I'm telling you, like,
Nate's actually gay.
That's why Maddy was upset.
I don't know about the carnival,
but I do know she smashed some
dude in the pool at McKay's.
Smashed?
That's why he attacked the new girl.
What new girl?
The one who cut herself.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Mr. Jacobs, would you
please come with me?
- What?
- Come with me.
You wanna tell me what the problem is?
Don't worry. We will.
What was that about?
Probably 'cause Nate
tried to kill Maddy.
What?
Well, 'cause she found all
that gay porn on his phone.
- Who told you that?
- You did.
- When?
- At the carnival.
Okay, Lexi, never repeat that,
because literally none of it's true.
Uh...
Daniel, I-I can't. I'm sorry.
I just... I'm... I'm
dating somebody, and...
I really don't want to fuck it up.
It's cool. Don't worry.
I just like you. I kind
of thought you liked me.
I do, I just...
I have a boyfriend.
Please don't say anything.
If I promise not to say anything,
can we hang out again?
...reproductive health
and your total well being
in all aspects of reproduction.
For example, physical, emotional...
Hey. Did you get my texts?
- No.
- Really?
- Well, I sent you a bunch of texts.
- Didn't get 'em.
Well, it says, like,
delivered on my phone.
Look, I really don't want to
talk about this right now.
What, are you for real?
Did I, like, do something?
I don't know, Ethan. Did you?
So the night of the carnival,
while fucking Luke Kasten,
Kat had an epiphany.
She was fucking Luke Kasten,
Luke motherfucking Kasten.
And for those of you who
didn't go to East Highland...
Luke Kasten was a fucking god.
I mean, he graduated years ago
and people still talk about him.
He has the biggest dick I've ever seen,
and I was looking at him
while he was fucking me.
I could see his face scrunching up when
he was coming all over my stomach,
and I had this, like, realization,
you know, like, this epiphany.
That no matter how cool, or, or sexy
or, or smart you think a guy is,
they're actually just fucking pathetic.
It's true, KittenKween.
Oh.
By the way, if you wanna come,
I put a body harness on
my Amazon wish list.
I'm gonna need you to buy it for me.
Yes, KittenKween.
- Can I be honest with you?
- Always.
- What I realize is that, like...
- Where are you going?
...my whole life, all I've tried
to do is to take up less space.
To the mall.
Try to hide from guys,
like, who might, like,
whisper to their friend under
their breath as I walked by.
I've spent my whole life afraid people
were gonna find out that I was fat.
But honestly, who gives a shit?
I'm so in awe of you, KittenKween.
There's nothing more
powerful than a fat girl
who doesn't give a fuck.
♪ You should see me in a crown ♪
♪ I'm gonna run this nothing town ♪
♪ Watch me make 'em bow,
one by, one by, one ♪
♪ One by, one by ♪
♪ You should see me in a crown ♪
♪ Your silence is my favorite sound ♪
♪ Watch me make 'em bow,
one by, one by, one ♪
Hey.
Thought you weren't from around here.
I'm not.
I get off work at seven.
You wanna hang out?
♪ One by, one by, one ♪
Why are you suddenly being so mean?
You don't understand,
Mommy. He didn't do it.
Then who did?
- It wasn't Nate.
- Maddy, stop lying.
- I'm not lying!
- I am not gonna let the son of a bitch
attack my daughter and get away with it.
- Right?
- Absolutely.
He needs to know that
there are consequences.
- Mom!
- I would like to press charges.
Well, you're not fucking
pressing charges!
- I am gonna press charges.
- No, you're not pressing...
- This is for your own good!
- No, you're not pressing charges!
O-Okay!
I would like to press charges.
- You okay, Mr. Jacobs?
- I'm fine.
Mr. and Mrs. Jacobs,
thanks for getting here so quickly.
So, it appears that
your son and Miss Perez
had a physical altercation
on Saturday night,
in which he allegedly strangled her.
What?
There are multiple eyewitnesses.
Miss Perez has extensive bruising,
and the family will be pressing charges.
There must be some misunderstanding.
This doesn't sound like
something my son would do.
I would like to talk
to the Perez family.
Actually, Mr. Jacobs,
I think it'd be best
to speak to your son
before we take him to the station.
He's just this way.
Did you do it?
Not really.
Did you admit to it?
No.
Did you do it?
Well, that's good to hear.
Her family's gonna press charges.
- Fuck.
- Hey.
Listen to me.
You need to stay composed.
Don't get angry, don't make a scene.
You walk out of the school
with your head held high.
Look at me. Hey, look at me.
What's about to happen to you...
to me, to our family...
is not gonna be easy.
You walk out first.
I'm right behind you.
Go on.
I love you.
- ♪ Hee, hee ♪
- ♪ Oh! ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Hee, hee ♪
Okay, one: what was that about?
Two: can we talk about the fact
that you fucked Nate's dad?
Rue, swear to God, like, on your life
that you will never tell anyone.
- That you fucked Nate's dad.
- I'm serious!
This is like, like,
even if you decide you hate me one day,
like, you can never tell anyone.
How would I ever hate you?
That's not the point. Like...
Seriously, this is some
go-to-your-grave shit.
I promise.
Okay.
Do you think Nate knows?
No. Why would Nate know?
I don't know. You went up to the
chili booth at the carnival.
Did... he look like he knew?
No, like, literally, I
didn't even notice.
Nate's scary.
The whole fucking family is scary.
I don't want to have this conversation.
You know what would be amazing?
If they paid you off
with a bunch of money and we do
a bunch of really cool shit.
Rue, this isn't a joke.
I don't know why Jules didn't trust me
or why she'd think I'd ever hate her.
There's literally nothing in the world
that Jules could do to make me
upset. I even told her that.
- Yeah, right.
- No, for real. It's true.
So, like, do you have a
lot of one-night stands?
Um, define a lot.
Um, like...
- More than five.
- Yeah.
More than ten.
I don't know.
More than 20.
- Rue, why does it matter?
- It's just a question.
Who cares?
Is the sex, like, good?
I don't know. It's, like, it's
not even the point, you know?
It's more about, like,
everything that leads up to it.
That's the good part.
I mean, you've had
one-night stands, right?
No.
But you've, like, hooked up with people
- that you've just met, right?
- Uh, not... Not like that. No. No.
Wait. How many people
have you slept with?
Not many.
No, like, what's your number?
Ugh, this is so embarrassing.
I had my first kiss at the age of 12
with a boy I didn't really like, but...
I just wanted to get it over with.
I gave four hand jobs in eighth grade,
two blow jobs in ninth,
one of which I was
emotionally coerced into.
I'm literally gonna tell the entire
school that you sucked my dick,
so you might as well just suck my dick.
Then there was that time that Lexi
got asked to the freshman formal
by Tucker Blake and I tried to
teach her how to French kiss.
Is this, like, really weird
and uncomfortable for you?
Mm, no. Not really.
Okay. Um, I'm gonna get ready.
Also, at 15,
I ate two Xannie bars, drank a
beer, which is super dangerous,
and lost my virginity.
- Did you come?
- Yeah.
Word.
You look like you came hard.
All I know is, life is not
a Nicholas Sparks novel.
- That's it?
- Yep. That's... That's it.
Wait, so, like... have
you ever been in love?
Fucking pigs!
Fuck you!
Hi, Maddy. I'm Detective Riley.
I understand this is traumatic,
but you're gonna have to cooperate.
If you literally step any
closer, I will fight you!
Miss, this is procedure. I need
you to remove your sweater now,
and if you don't, we
will remove it for you.
Really, bitch? How?
- You're fucking crazy!
- Calm down.
Take a deep breath. Take a deep breath.
Come on, Maddy. We don't
want to hurt you.
Get off of me!
- Maddy, please.
- Relax.
There we go.
Thanks, guys. I got this.
I know you're really upset right now,
and you don't want to hear this.
But trust me, when I tell you
that the person that did this...
...doesn't love you.
Mm-hmm.
So you grabbed her.
I grabbed her by the arm to drag
her away. I didn't choke her.
I asked her why she was acting that way.
Like, I asked her what she was doing.
I don't want to get her in any trouble,
but she'd taken a lot of drugs.
What drugs?
I don't want to get her in trouble.
She's not gonna get in any trouble.
Molly.
As in MDMA?
Yeah.
But I don't know if it was pure.
Like, I don't... I don't
do drugs, so I don't know.
And after that conversation,
was that the last time
you spoke to Miss Perez that evening?
Yeah.
Her and I don't have the
healthiest relationship.
I know that.
My dad's always telling me that she's
a distraction, and he's right.
I love her.
You know, I really
love her. No matter...
how crazy she acts, no matter
what she does, I love her.
It's kind of embarrassing
to admit, but, um...
on the times when we've broken up,
I know for a fact that she's
been with other guys.
I don't know, I mean, it's
possible that that night...
Aah, it doesn't matter.
- What were you gonna say?
- It doesn't matter.
I love Maddy.
I'd never do anything to hurt her.
The fallout from Nate's
assault was swift...
I'm suspending your son
until the investigation is completed.
Look, that could take months.
...and harsh.
East Highland football team
has a zero tolerance policy.
I'm a survivor of abuse.
It took me ten years to admit that.
Because the most insidious
symptom of abuse
is the inability to admit
that what you're enduring
is not normal,
not okay, and not love.
Those are the moments that
keep me up at night...
Thinking about all the
times that I ignored that,
that voice in my head.
You know, that told me,
"What are you doing?"
And what happens in a month?
Six months? A year?
When she moves away and goes to college?
When she tells you, she
just wants to be friends?
- You mean "if."
- No, Rue. I mean "when."
I mean, I don't know. We
talked about living together.
Like, if she goes to New
York, I'll just go with her.
I'll go anywhere she goes.
I think you're missing my point, Rue.
Nothing in high school lasts forever.
You should meet her.
Go ahead, Rue.
♪ What the fuck are we talking for? ♪
Uh...
Hey, everyone. I'm... I'm
Rue and I'm an addict.
Hi, Rue.
Uh...
I guess I just wanted to, uh,
make amends with everyone.
Because most every time I've shared,
I... I was lying.
Yeah, every time I collected a chip,
whether it be 30 days
or 60 days or 90 days,
I was lying.
Um...
But... I met someone.
And she's helped.
And now I want to stay clean.
And, shit, maybe that's...
Maybe that's me being selfish,
you know, and Ali just
scared the shit out of me.
'Cause he told me that
it wasn't gonna last.
And, fuck, you know what?
Maybe you're right.
But I really, really,
really hope you're wrong.
'Cause, uh, I've been clean for 13 days.
It's been okay.
Um, I've actually been really happy.
So, um...
Yeah, I don't know. I guess that's
why I wanted to come here, and...
tell you guys the truth.
Uh, thank you.
Thank you.
- Welcome back.
- Thank you, Rue.
So, is this like a friend thing
with Rue or is it, like...
I don't want to talk about it.
I was just wondering...
are you two, like, a thing?
No, we're not a thing. I
don't know what a thing is.
'Cause I've been thinking,
you know, if it was,
if you two were a thing...
We could all just do, like,
a family thing together.
Maybe go out to dinner or something.
I don't want to go to
dinner with you and Rue.
I'm sorry.
Why? Because you're embarrassed of me?
Or is it because you're a thing?
- You're hilarious.
- Yeah, I know.
Is she still going to meetings?
That's great.
You're a good influence.
_
McKay had heard the news about Nate.
Had a bunch of dick pics on his phone.
And was, like, what, sending
them to other girls?
No, McKay, it wasn't his dick.
It was other guys' dicks.
I'm confused. Who told you this?
What dick pics?
The ones you told me
about, on his phone.
I don't know if your
brain is all scrambled
from, like, all the Molly you
take, but I never said that.
If you spread a lie like that,
I will fucking come for you.
We good?
Yeah.
Anyway, look, Cassie,
I'm really sorry about what happened
the other night at the carnival.
It's okay.
No, I should have said
something to Nate.
It just really hurt my feelings.
It made me feel like you weren't
proud to be my boyfriend.
Cass.
Give me a kiss.
I'm proud to be your
boyfriend, trust me.
I'm sorry, too.
What do you got to be sorry about?
I love making music.
Yeah, I mean, but to be honest...
I don't think I'm, like, good
enough yet to just do music.
But that's, like, my dream,
you know or whatever.
- What about you?
- What about me?
You look like you're
creative or something.
Uh, you know?
- Creative.
- Yeah.
I don't know. Just, like, the
way you dress and stuff.
I just thought you might
be an artist or something.
Look, if you wanna hook
up, we can hook up.
Um... I wasn't expecting that.
Really?
Yeah, I was just making conversation.
I mean, that's my point,
you don't really have to.
♪ Doll, Eskimo, aye! ♪
- ♪ BankRollGotit ♪
- ♪ I'm so icy... ♪
Maddy wasn't doing well.
Over the course of the last five days,
Maddy has sent Nate a total
of 273 text messages,
none of which he answered.
Plus, everyone in her
life was against her.
_
- Who the fuck are you to judge?
- _
Seriously, Mom, Dad has slept on the
couch since I was ten years old.
_
I'm not.
I'm just saying love
is a million things.
Sometimes it feels good,
sometimes it doesn't.
The one thing I know is that
Nate loves me no matter what.
He'd fucking kill for me
and I'd kill for him.
It feels good to know
that there's one person
in this whole fucked-up world
who has my back.
You think I want this?
You live in the same house
and you don't even say
one word to each other.
That's the difference
between me and you.
_
Kat, I need to come
over, like, right now.
- I'm not home.
- What? Where are you?
- With a... friend.
- Who?
It doesn't really
matter. I'm just, like,
in the middle of something.
Can I call you back later?
Well, can you blow them off, please?
I really need you right now.
I... I can't. I gotta go.
- Sorry about that.
- All good.
Um...
So, like...
Oh!
Shit.
Mmm!
Fuck!
Shit.
Fuck.
It was just...
That was really good.
Seriously, that was like...
one of the best blow jobs I've ever had.
♪ Hour past time and I
didn't want to wake up ♪
♪ Eh, eh, oh ♪
♪ All that's fine, are
we headin' back home? ♪
♪ Headin' back home, headin' back home ♪
♪ Cross that line and
the second we make it ♪
♪ Eh, eh, oh ♪
♪ All come round, now
they sayin' don't go ♪
♪ Sayin' don't go, sayin' don't go ♪
♪ I'm tired, still we rockin' all days ♪
♪ Racin' 'gainst time,
think we're neck to neck ♪
♪ Got people talking that talk ♪
♪ Copy the rhyme but
ain't in their walk ♪
♪ From outside looks like a circle ♪
♪ From on this side it
seems like a wall ♪
♪ Rough ride, get me
through it some way ♪
♪ Another long flight,
make me earn the pay ♪
One more time, okay? One more time!
Rue seems really good.
Yeah. She does.
It's 'cause of you, you know.
Um, I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Okay.
I'm so sorry I'm late.
My landlord is such a
fucking cocksucker. Ugh.
You know that type of person that, like,
just tries to get under your skin
for, like, no reason?
Whatever. You don't care. I can breathe.
Oh, my God. You're actually hot?
Can I, uh... Would you
like a glass of champagne?
Honey, no. I don't do alcohol.
You from around here?
I'm from planet Venus, baby.
I'm Minako.
But the boys call me Mina.
♪ Bitch, you don't know
me so shut the fuck up ♪
♪ Can't walk like Naomi
'cause I got it tucked ♪
♪ It's right on my waist
and it's heavy as fuck ♪
♪ Leave a bitch under
like Harriet Tub' ♪
♪ I caught a whole body
now the block hot ♪
♪ You caught a half a
body like a crop top ♪
♪ If it's in my hair
then it's top notch ♪
♪ Niggas wanna cock-block Niggas
straight squares like hopscotch ♪
♪ Yeah, it's too late I'm pulling
up straight to the gate ♪
♪ This what you call on fate ♪
♪ It's only one way to
deal with the hate ♪
♪ Make a nigga disappear
like the period late... ♪
I'm, um... I just...
- Will you please stop the music?
- Jeez.
What is up with you?
- You want a popper?
- No.
Well, then, what do you want?
I just want to talk for a little bit.
What do you want to talk about?
I've just had a really long week.
- Wife?
- No.
- Kids?
- Yeah.
Mm.
- Boys or girls?
- Boys.
Mm.
Do you think this stuff affects them?
Even if they don't know it?
I don't know.
Do you think hiding it creates
the same thing in them?
Honey, I don't know.
Everyone knows who I am.
You know...
I spent my whole life trying to
keep this part of me separate.
But I feel like it's
poisoned everything.
I thought that
I was doing what was best for everybody.
And then, I look at my boys, and...
they have so much anger.
Not just anger...
but rage.
And it scares me.
Because... it's too late.
It's always gonna be inside them.
All those problems you have, baby...
I'm here to fix it.
All that bad energy...
you can give it to me.
I can handle it.
♪ You're still ♪
♪ The same girl ♪
♪ You always were ♪
♪ You're still ♪
♪ The same girl ♪
♪ You always were ♪
♪ A few more nights ♪
You know, it seems like
we never do this anymore.
Yeah.
♪ A few more holes ♪
♪ In your arm ♪
- You gonna spend the night?
- Uh, I should probably go home.
Okay. Uh, well, is it cool
if I just go with you?
Uh, yeah. Sure.
♪ Still the same girl ♪
- ♪ Same sweet smile ♪
- My God.
♪ That you always had ♪
What's up, bro?
Yeah, I'm with her right now. What's up?
He says can you tell Maddy
to download Signal?
♪ Same clear voice ♪
Get off the road, you fucking cunt!
Fuck you!
♪ The same girl ♪
♪ That I ♪
_
♪ Love ♪
♪ You're still ♪
♪ The same girl ♪
♪ You always were ♪
♪ Still ♪
♪ The same girl ♪
♪ You always were ♪
♪ With the same sweet smile ♪
♪ That you always had ♪
♪ And the same blue eyes ♪
♪ Like the sun ♪
- ♪ And the same clear voice ♪
- Hey, handsome.
♪ That I always ♪
♪ Still ♪
♪ The same girl ♪
♪ That I ♪
♪ Love ♪
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com
♪ It was just before the moon hung ♪
♪ Her weary, heavy head in ♪
♪ The gallows and the graves of ♪
♪ The milky, milky cradle ♪
♪ His tears have turned to poppies ♪
♪ A shimmer in the midnight ♪
♪ A flower in the twilight ♪
♪ And our screaming ♪
♪ Is in his screaming ♪
♪ Our screaming ♪
♪ In the willow tree ♪
Christopher McKay's father
demanded excellence.
Then he got to college
and he realized...
he didn't stand a chance of going pro.
If we go to this party
and you dress like that,
I ain't gon' ever hear the end of it.
The whole point of Halloween
is to look attractive.
The situation with your son,
a lot of people are talking.
You need a plan.
Every time I feel good, I
think it'll last forever.
But it doesn't.
I was drawn to Maddy as a
character because I knew
she would pull me out
of my comfort zone.
I think Maddy's always been confident.
Like when she was a little girl,
she was winning pageant after pageant.
So, I think her confidence is
something that she's always had.
Like I think Maddy definitely runs Nate.
She definitely gets what
she wants out of him,
but in those moments where
he gets angry and violent
and dark, she just...
she's so weak, and I
think she's in pain.
She's in a toxic, abusive relationship.
It wasn't the violence that scared her.
It was the fact that she
knew no matter what he did,
she'd still love him.
She thinks that what
Nate provides for her
and does for her is 100 times better
than what she's seen her dad do.
Growing up in a dysfunctional home,
you can end up in those relationships
because they either seem normal to you,
or they seem better than
what you've seen at home.
Maddy will do anything in her power
not to end up like her parents.
She doesn't want that life, so
she's... she's trying to find
a way out in any way
she can and I think...
that's where the relationship
with Nate comes in.
I think she likes the idea of it.
So even though he's
hurting her, she just...
She thinks it's better than
what she's grown up watching.
Just saying love is a million things!
Sometimes, it feels good.
Sometimes, it doesn't.
Trust me when I tell you that
the person that did this
doesn't love you.
I think Maddy feels like
everyone's against her,
and no one understands them.
It feels like the lowest
point of her life,
and even then, she's... She's
still rooting for Nate.
She wants him to figure out a plan.
She wants him to be okay.
She really feels like they
have this special bond,
but it's... you know, it's a
dysfunctional young love.
Working with Jacob was incredible.
I couldn't have asked for
a better scene partner.
Those scenes are really intense,
and you know, it is...
It's acting, but it's
physical and you know,
you're pouring all of
your emotion into this.
I think Maddy's searching for
any bit of love, any bit of hope.
I think we want love sometimes so bad,
we stay in these relationships
even when we know they aren't right.
But she doesn't want to
admit that to herself.
She just wants everybody
to leave her alone,
and she wants it to
just be her and Nate.
www.tvsubtitles.net