Subtitles by explosiveskull
I don't understand why we have to drive
seven hours to see a psychiatrist.
Because... we want the
best care possible for you.
When Jules was
eleven years old,
her mother took her on a road trip.
- Wasn't Dali, like, a sexual predator?
- Was he?
I hadn't heard that before.
Would you like me to take it down?
No. It's a cool painting.
It is a cool painting.
He was actually
really sweet, though.
They talked for over an hour,
and only later did Jules realize
that she hadn't lied once.
After the session, they wanted
to give her a tour of the Unit.
- Well, what's the Unit?
- Think of it like a second home,
where children can learn how
to feel better about themselves.
Okay.
Let me give you a tour.
So, this is our common area,
where we have group sessions,
watch movies, play games,
have art class.
Um, on Tuesdays we have
canine therapy.
Uh, Thursdays we have music therapy.
- Dr. Kay!
- Allan!
Suck my dick, you fucking cunt!
Allan!
Usually there's two to a room,
depending on how many patients
are with us.
So the kids live here?
For short periods of time.
And this is the quiet room.
I'm gonna fucking
rape you, Dr. Kay!
You just bought yourself another
30 minutes in the quiet room, Jesse.
It was around
then when Jules thought
she had just about
had enough of the tour.
I think I wanna go home.
And that's when Jules realized,
this wasn't a tour at all.
It was an elaborate plan
to admit her
to a fucking psychiatric hospital.
Mom! Mom!
No, no, no, no, no!
No! No! No!
During the ensuing
struggle, Jules accidentally
scratched an RA across the face,
which she felt really guilty about.
But quickly, that guilt
turned into anger...
and that anger, into defeat.
Hi. I'm Jules.
- How are you feeling?
- Better.
Good. Good.
Why don't you tell the group a little
about yourself and why you're here.
I don't know.
Maybe because I was, like,
sad for a really long time.
What do you mean by a long time?
Maybe since I was
seven or eight or something.
And I've been to see,
like, a bunch of doctors.
I've been on, like,
a bunch of medications,
but nothing's really helped, so...
Maybe these mitts will do the trick.
And, Jules, do you self-injure?
The truth was,
Jules hated herself.
She hated
how her brain worked...
the way it would
get stuck on a thought,
like choking.
All right. Keep present.
And it would just play
on an infinite loop,
until she couldn't think
or breathe or stand to be alive.
This is hard, Jules.
You're going to get through it, okay?
She didn't just
hate her brain, though.
She hated her body, not every part,
just her shoulders, and her arms,
and her hands.
Also her chest,
her stomach, her thighs.
Her knees were the worst.
Plus her ankles, and her big,
fucking, stupid feet.
She hated her life,
not because it was bad,
but because when you hate
your brain and your body,
it's hard to enjoy the rest.
So, Jules developed
a few coping mechanisms.
None of them healthy, and a few
scary enough to land her in...
So, how are you liking the Unit?
It's okay.
- Are you making any friends?
- Not really.
Well, that'll change.
Wait. Can you leave
me the rest?
Sure.
- This guy did some damage.
- Allan?
I did something really stupid.
Is everything okay?
I'm so sorry.
Please don't be mad at me.
Eventually Jules got
better and came home.
But her mom got
worse and went away.
And her dad quit his
job to be closer to home,
which she liked,
'cause she loved her dad.
By 13, she started to transition.
And by 16, Jules had gotten
a little slutty.
And every guy was the same:
cis, white, married,
engaged, in long-term relationships,
and always, always...
I mean,
I'm a hundred percent straight.
Um, cool.
So do you like top?
- No.
- Cool.
'Cause that's, like, not my thing.
Some were sweet.
Some were weird.
And a few were aggressive.
Spit.
And whenever anything
got too uncomfortable...
...Jules would just imagine
that she wasn't really herself,
and this wasn't really her life.
She was just a character
in a book or a movie or a show.
That none of it was real, and
if it was, how did it matter?
It's not like her body ever really
belonged to her in the first place.
But fuck it.
She'd save it for the memoirs.
'Cause that was the night
she met her new best friend.
And although she had never
really been in a relationship
or even in, like, love,
she imagined spending
the rest of her life with her.
How they'd live together in
some shitty New York apartment,
and maybe date other people, but
always sleep in the same bed.
She even said it to her once,
which was probably a mistake,
for, like, a lot of reasons.
Plus, that was before
she fell for Tyler,
like, hard, like, really hard.
What are you smiling about?
I don't know.
Just... life.
There's nothing I'm
really passionate about.
You know, like, I'm not dying
to say or do anything, really.
And every time
I admit that to people,
they're like, "Oh, my gosh,
that's so sad." But...
I think that's the case
for most people.
You know? Like, when I look
at my mom or...
like, the kids at my school...
like, their profiles or their
posts and their Tumblr rants...
you realize they're all just
fucked up, too... and lost.
They just have
a reason to mask it...
whether it be, like,
their, their families
or their boyfriends
or their hashtag activism.
And they're just reaching
for something
- to make it all seem meaningful.
- Rue...
But sometimes
I just sit and think...
- Rue. Rue.
- ...like, what's the point?
Rue, I don't give a shit.
- Why'd you call me?
- Honestly...
I didn't really have
anybody else to call.
Well, what happened
to make you call?
Um...
you know...
just like...
Open the fucking door!
Fuck!
...just the usual bullshit.
Rue, you know that drug addicts
don't reach out for help
unless there's no options.
So what happened?
Um...
I was with my best friend.
Okay, well, she's...
I mean, she's a new friend,
but we hang out every day.
And, um...
It's stupid.
- What?
- I just...
I misread...
the whole situation.
And now it's gonna be
really, really, really...
really fucking awkward.
And I guess that
hanging out with her was...
was the best thing that's
happened to me in a while, so...
Does the way in which you feel
about her remind you of anything?
- What do you mean?
- You know, like... the obsession,
the feelings, the withdrawal.
What, like drugs?
Bingo.
Okay, but this is a good thing.
Didn't drugs feel real good
the first time you tried 'em?
Shit.
Yeah. It's gon' be
a good night, tonight, man.
Let's get this money.
What's good, bro?
Fuck.
- You wanna go on the Gravitron?
- Uh, no.
- The Ferris wheel?
- Nope.
- Why?
- Because I don't wanna die.
Where are you? I'm standing
by the fucking Ferris wheel.
I don't see you.
Why do you always do this to me?
- Whoa! Whoa! Aah!
- We're gonna die, die!
Oh, my God.
Stop! Stop!
Stop! You're rocking
the fucking thing.
- You're rocking...
- Oh, my God.
Yo, are you at this Ferris
wheel or that Ferris wheel?
Well, how the fuck am I supposed
to know which one you're at?
You don't fucking tell me...
Yeah, I know, I know.
I'm on my way. I...
How am I supposed to know that
there's two Ferris wheels?
- Yo, why are dressed like a hooker?
- What?
Jesus Christ, Maddy.
I'm here with my parents.
- So what? It's the carnival.
- No. It's the chili cook-off.
It's very important. I can't have you
hanging out at the booth
dressed like that.
Yeah, well maybe it'll sell better.
Yo, this isn't a fucking joke, okay?
Why are you being like this?
Listen, my parents
already don't like you.
What?
Go home, get changed,
and come back looking like a person.
Fuck.
- Well, did you break up again?
- No.
- Looks like you broke up again.
- No, we didn't.
If you ask me, she's a distraction.
Hurry up, guy, go!
- Oh!
- Ew!
Hold on.
Oh, my God.
Jules!
Come!
Hands and feet inside the ride
unless you want to die.
- Hey.
I'm really fucking scared.
Oh, no!
- Hi.
- Hey.
- I missed you.
- I missed you, too.
Um, I think she's in love with her.
Really?
Yeah, like... Rue is in
love with Jules, I think.
- Are you mad at me?
- No. No, no.
Are you mad at me?
- No.
- Okay.
Don't you think?
I hadn't really thought about it.
Oh. I don't know.
Can we just pretend like
what I did wasn't super-weird?
- It wasn't weird. It...
- It was weird, but...
we don't have to talk about it.
Talk about what?
- Nothing.
- Right.
Okay, um... Anyway, I'm gonna
go catch some friends.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Uh-oh. Mr. Jacobs.
- Oh!
- Stingray McKay.
- I see you...
- I see what you got going on over here.
- All right, chili.
Let me get some.
- Yo, what's up, brother?
- How you doin', man?
Yo.
What are you... Are you guys,
like, in a relationship?
- Nah, we're just chillin'.
- Are you just chillin'?
Yeah, we're chillin'.
Okay. Okay.
Why haven't I seen you on the field?
Uh.... Just freshmen got to earn
their due, that's all.
You take that attitude, you'll spend
the rest of your life on the bench.
It's really not that big of a deal, Mr.
Jacobs. It's just the first season.
No, it is a big deal.
You got one of the best
slide-steps I've ever seen.
You've got promise.
You've got talent.
You're not pushing yourself
hard enough.
Dad, I think McKay's
gonna be just fine.
I'm just trying to help him
keep a girl like her.
Why? It's not like
we're in a relationship.
- Plus, I don't even care about football.
- Whoa.
It's not just football.
It's life.
It's about maintaining your focus.
It's about putting your all
into everything you do.
Why do you think I have
the business I have?
Why do think I have
the family I have?
The success that I have?
Why do think this chili
has been voted best chili in the
county five years in a row?
'Cause you refuse to lose.
It's about who you want
to become in the world.
I'm just lookin' out for you.
- Bye.
- Cassie.
- What the fuck is her problem?
- Come on, bro.
Yo, Cass. Cass.
Cass, stop.
Why would you say that?
That we're just chillin'?
It's not that big of a deal,
Cass. It's a figure of speech.
- It is a big deal.
- It's really not.
You literally just told me
that you loved me.
What does that have
to do with anything?
You just told Nate that we're not
even in a fucking relationship.
That's because I know the guy.
He's just gonna talk shit.
- Like what?
- Like about you.
Or whatever, Cassie.
What do you mean, whatever?
Like whatever the fuck you've done.
What have I done, McKay?
Look, I don't want to talk
about this right now, Cass.
We're in the middle
of a fucking carnival.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
It's not like it's that big
of a fucking secret, Cassie.
You know what?
It's cool.
We should just call it a night.
I gotta get back, anyway.
- So, what you was lookin' for?
- Molly.
Oh. She over there workin'
at the pretzel stand.
Thank you.
Hey.
- Hey.
- You're not having fun?
- No.
- Yeah, me, neither.
You wanna do Molly?
Welcome to Pretzelmania.
Can I take your order?
How many pretzels do you want?
- We don't eat carbs.
- Two, please.
That'll be forty.
So, you think Nate's
cheating on you?
I don't know. He's just been
acting super-weird lately.
Have you gone through his phone?
I've never not gone through
someone's phone.
Bitch, you're my soul mate.
Thank you.
Yo, what's going
on with you and McKay?
I thought you two were in love.
Nate asked McKay
if were were in a relationship,
and McKay said that
we were just chillin'.
- What?
- Yeah.
Honestly, fuck them both.
Right?
Okay, so if I
tell you something,
you swear on your fucking life
you won't say a word?
Yeah. What?
I went through Nate's phone.
And it was weird.
- Oh, my fucking God.
- What?
- That's him.
- Who?
The guy.
- What guy?
- The one from the motel.
Okay, what guy are
we looking at, exactly?
Okay, the one in the apron,
serving the chili.
- I swear to God.
- No fucking way.
Jules, do you know who that is?
- Yeah, the guy from the motel.
- That's Cal Jacobs.
- Who's that?
- Nate Jacobs's dad.
- That's Nate's dad?
- Yes, that's Nate's dad.
- No fucking way!
- Yes, fucking way.
- You're full of shit.
- No way.
You're full of shit.
Do you... Do you know who he is?
He fucking owns half this town.
He built it.
All the apartment buildings
past Kemper, they're his.
- Rue, I swear to God.
- There's no way.
- That's the guy I fucked.
Bullshit.
I'm being a hundred percent serious.
- You... You don't believe me?
- No, actually.
- I don't.
- Okay. Watch.
- Excuse me, sir.
- Hmm?
Hi. Can I help you?
Uh, can I please have
a small cup of chili?
Yeah, sure.
Oh.
Shoot.
Sorry.
Uh, it... it's okay.
It was my fault.
I'll get you another cup.
Hi. It's two dollars. All the
proceeds go to the football team.
Uh... cool.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Yo, Nate, who was that?
Her name's Jules.
She's new here.
She goes to East Highland?
Yeah. She's a junior.
Damn. That's jailbait.
That's too bad.
- ...nuts!
- Why the fuck did you let me do that?
I didn't let you do that!
You just fucking...
You just did it. You went over
there and you did it.
Did you see that
his hands were fucking shaking?
- Yes, and then he dropped...
- And then he fucking dropped the chili!
- Oh, my God.
- He dropped the fucking chili.
Oh, he dropped the fucking chili.
And then he...
And then you looked at me.
Yeah, because
I was screaming inside.
Yeah, well, that made him
fucking look at me.
- He looked at me in the fucking eyes.
- I'm sorry.
I feel so bad. That was
literally the meanest thing
- I've ever done.
- Oh, shit, hold on. It's my mom.
Hey, Mom.
Yeah. Yeah, no.
Well, because she's been in the
Gravitron for like 20 straight minutes.
Yes, yes. I promise.
We will be home by ten.
Okay, I love you, too.
Apparently, Gia's
not answering her phone.
- Uh...
- It's just going straight to voicemail.
It burns.
It's so weird
to think that, like,
no matter what happens,
the universe is just out here
giving, like, zero fucks.
Wow.
- You look super cute.
- Thanks. You, too. I love that shirt.
Thank you. Even though I
have the same body as Bruno Mars.
- Shut up, you look hot.
- No, I don't.
- Yes, you do.
- No, I don't,
'cause
these right here, they're cutlets.
No, they're not. Trust me,
these guys are super chill, okay?
Do not worry.
- Your mom's, like, all organic, right?
- Oh, yeah. Yeah.
- There's your issue.
- What do you mean?
Uh, organic food doesn't
have any good hormones.
You gotta get her to buy, like,
the regular stuff, okay?
What's the regular stuff?
- Trust me. Oh, and milk, and milk.
- No! I hate milk!
At least three glasses a day.
Three glasses.
That's how I went
from a small A to a full B.
Mm-hmm.
- Fine, I'll try it.
- I'm telling you.
- You gotta do it.
- How old are the boys again?
They're, like, our age.
Yeah.
That's a lot.
- I know.
- They are so good.
- Right?
- I could drink these, like,
- every day of my life.
- Yes.
Uh, how 'bout you grab
another slushie,
I go get more tickets, and then get
super drunk and ride the Ferris wheel?
Deal.
- Okay.
- Okay. All right.
All right.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Just tell your sister
I really need her
- to cover my shift on Wednesday.
- Okay.
For real. She's not
answering any of my texts.
I promise you I will say something.
I'm supposed to meet my
boyfriend's family for the first time.
It's really important.
Yeah, I got you.
Thank you.
You're the best.
- Honestly, fuck that whole family.
- For real.
'Cause right now I'm looking at
a thousand versions of myself,
and not only do I look good,
I fucking feel good.
- It's a bitch.
- So, if they've got something to say,
they should just say it
to my face, right?
Or you could just say it
to their fucking face.
- Right?
- That's what I would do.
- I feel like this is a turning point.
- Totally.
We should just pick the hottest,
most confident,
bad bitch version of ourselves,
and be that for the rest
of the school year.
Yo.
And this year's winner
of the chili cook-off is...
Cal Jacobs!
Make it six years and running!
Yeah, I'm not supposed
to be here right now,
because I'm dressed like a hooker,
and none of you like me,
but I just wanted to say
congratulations.
Maddy, get out of...
Ooh!
What in God's name is your problem?
You, cunt.
- Hey.
- 'Sup, Cass?
You wanna ride the carousel?
Cool.
Shit.
She's not answering.
- It's just going straight to voicemail.
- I mean, she can't be too far.
Well, I have to get her home
in like, 30 minutes.
- Gia!
Excuse me. Sorry.
Gia!
- Gia!
Fuck. Okay. Uh...
It'd be faster if we split up.
- Yeah. Okay. Text me. Thank you.
- Okay.
I'm not
gonna let you fucking embarrass me
like that again,
I swear to fucking God.
Shut the fuck up!
I'm fucking done with you!
- I'm so fucking done with you.
- So what else is new?
- I'm not fucking joking.
- Yeah, fucking right.
Calling my mom a cunt.
What the fuck is actually wrong
- with your fucking brain?
- I think you're overreacting.
You're fucking dead to me.
Fuck you.
- I do have one question, though.
- Yo, what?
Man, I'm telling you, that
girl has some real, fucking issues.
I have to use the bathroom.
Gia!
Got an extra cigarette?
Damn, you're so fucking hot.
I could ride the carousel for hours!
- Emma. Yo.
- Yo, Rue. What up?
- Have you seen Gia?
- Yeah, like, over there.
- Over where? Where is she?
- You know. Like, the Gravitron.
- Is she in the Gravitron?
- No, she's like, by it.
I... I really have to pee.
Gia!
Aren't you Luke Kasten?
Yeah.
You used to go
to East Highland, right?
Yeah, like, fuckin' forever ago.
I used to hear stories about you,
like, all the time in middle school.
Oh, yeah?
What kind of stories?
That you had a...
have a really big dick and
fucked every girl in your grade.
Basically.
That's cool.
How old are you?
Sixteen.
I'm just saying, as your girlfriend,
those pictures are a little suspicious.
It's not what it looks like.
Yeah? Well, then, explain
to me why you have
someone else's dick in your phone.
It's really fucking complicated.
How many reasons could there be?
I can't explain it to you right now.
Yeah, what does that mean?
Look, I'm going through
a lot of shit right now.
I need... I just...
I need you to promise me
that you're not gonna tell a soul.
I am not gonna
tell anyone, I promise.
- Like, on your life.
- Yeah, on my life.
I'm sorry I got so angry
at you before.
I am sorry.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Maddy, I love you.
I got a lot of sh...
a lot of shit going on right
now and I'm really confused.
I don't know what to do.
Ho, ho, ho. Nasty!
Gia!
What the hell?
I've been calling you.
Rue.
- Are you stoned right now?
- Nah. Um-mm.
- We're just chillin'.
- Yeah, that's my sister.
- Yo, Roy.
- What's up?
This is Rue's little sis.
Oh, yeah. I knew that by the
way she was hittin' the weed.
That's me.
All right, Gia, get up.
Let's go.
What do you mean, let's go?
You see we're having a funky good time.
- That's great.
- I'm having the best time.
- We need to go, now.
- We having the best time.
Gia, get the fuck up and let's go.
- I'm not playing with you.
- Wow.
What'd you do?
Decide to just clean up,
- and, like, oh, I wanna become a mom?
- Right?
- Gia, get the fuck up. Let's go. Now.
- Mom. What's your problem, Mom?
Hey, if she's a mom,
you know she a MILF.
Get up.
Yo, for real. When'd you
become such a bitch?
Excuse me?
Was it after you fuckin' OD'd?
Yeah. It's good.
I know it's only weed,
but you might get addicted.
Get up.
Just hope you don't
get addicted again.
All I'm saying is, if I were you,
I wouldn't be taking
advice from her.
Yo. Text me.
Don't do that
shit again, all right?
You fucking scared me.
Hey.
Look, I know you have the power
to ruin my life right now.
I'm begging you,
pleading with you,
please don't.
I know you already told your friend.
I saw her look at me.
She won't tell anyone.
- I promise.
- 'Cause if this ever came out,
I'd lose everything.
I'll do whatever you want me to do.
I have no intention of, like,
hurting you or anything.
I'm sorry about earlier.
That was kind of dumb.
That's okay.
I just wanted to...
It won't be a thing.
- Don't worry.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Where were you?
- What's wrong?
- I just think the Molly's, like,
way too strong or something.
So... did you come?
No.
Uh, do you think Mom's gonna be
sitting in the living room
when we get there?
- No, she won't.
- Okay.
Because, if, um...
If I walked in there,
I wouldn't know what to say.
- I wouldn't say hi.
- No, she's... She's gonna be in her bed.
Trust me. Look, I need you,
when we get home,
to just go straight to your room
and hide under the covers. Okay?
Just let me deal with her.
Wh-what are you gonna tell her?
I don't know yet.
What are you laughing at?
You good?
Come here.
She's still a little sick from
riding the Gravitron so many times.
- Should I check on her?
- Oh, no. It's good. I got it.
Thank you for looking out
for her tonight.
- Of course.
- Love you.
- Love you, too. Good night, Mom.
- Good night.
Hey. Shut the door.
Hey.
Tyler?
No. No!
No, I'm not trying
to hurt you. I'm not.
I'm not here to hurt you.
I know that you have
these ideas about me,
based on the first time that
we met, and I understand that.
But I'm not the person
that you met that night.
Can you let go of me?
You know, over the past few weeks...
I've spent...
every moment of every day
getting to know you.
At night...
I fall asleep to you.
And in the morning...
I wake up to you.
I kind of feel closer to you than I
do to anyone in the whole world.
I don't trust you, Nate.
I don't trust you, either.
- Open your mouth.
- Nate...
Wider.
Nate. Nate, stop.
God, are you broken inside.
And that's precisely why
I don't trust you.
Because you're so broken
you don't even trust yourself.
And that's scary.
Not just for you, but for me.
And for my entire family.
I wouldn't answer that.
You're gonna wanna hear this.
Over the last three weeks,
you have knowingly produced and
distributed child pornography.
Including obscene images that
were taken on school property.
I've compiled all these photos,
along with an IP address, and an
account that's linked to your name.
I don't know if you're familiar with
child pornography laws in this state.
But they apply to minors
just as they apply to adults.
I sent them to you.
No. You sent them
to an account of a person
that doesn't fucking exist.
And I mean, anyone can anonymously
report child pornography, right?
- Then I'd tell them everything.
- Okay.
You could do that, but, um...
here's what would definitely happen.
You'd end up on
a sex offenders list.
It means no more college.
It's gonna be very fucking
difficult to find a job.
And everywhere you go,
for the rest of your life,
you'll be harassed, and spat at,
and treated like a fucking animal.
You deserve better than that.
'Cause I know you.
You're kind.
You're smart.
You're generous.
You got a big heart.
You deserve whatever the fuck it
is in this world that you want.
So keep your head down.
Keep your mouth shut.
Don't try to ruin my life,
and I won't have to ruin yours.
You know what I think?
I think you're a fucking faggot,
just like your daddy.
You have a nice night.
- Hey.
Do you think
I could, uh, sleep over?
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
Come on.
Is everything okay?
Um...
Here.
So how'd the date go with Tyler?
Um...
He didn't look like his picture.
Come here.
Are you sure you're okay?
What?
Subtitles by explosiveskull