No, we just chillin'.
Why would you say that?
You literally just told
me that you loved me.
You grab another slushie,
I go get more tickets,
and then get super drunk
and ride the Ferris wheel.
Deal.
BECKY: I'm supposed to meet my
boyfriend's family for the first time.
I sent him a few pics
from the school bathroom
- during class because he asked me to.
- Wait, like nudes?
You have knowingly
produced and distributed
child pornography.
I sent them to you.
You can't be coming over here no more.
Open the door! You
fucking ruined my life.
(SCREAMS)
You wanna tell me what the problem is?
Other times, when we've broken up,
I know for a fact that she's
been with other guys.
That doesn't matter. I love Maddy.
I'd never do anything to hurt her.
RUE: Christopher McKay's
father demanded excellence.
Although she feeds me
bread of bitterness,
and sinks into my throat
her tiger's tooth,
stealing my breath of
life, I will confess.
I love this cultured hell
that tests my youth.
However strong you think you are,
you are stronger. (WHISTLE TRILLS)
MCKAY: Her vigor flows
like tides into my blood
giving me strength erect
against her hate,
- Her bigness sweeps my being...
- (WHISTLE TRILLS)
- ...like a flood.
- Let's go, let's go.
MCKAY: Yet as a rebel
fronts a king in state...
- There you go. Up, up.
- MCKAY: I stand within her walls,
without a shred of terror,
- malice, not a word of jeer...
- (VOMITS)
However strong you think
you are, you are stronger.
MCKAY: Darkly I gaze
into the days ahead,
and see her might, and
grin at wonders there.
Beneath the touch of
time's unerring hand,
like priceless treasures
sinking in the sand.
- (WHISTLE TRILLS)
- Great work, son.
Get some water. Get ready for practice.
QUARTERBACK: Ready. Set. Hut.
(CHEERING)
RUE: As much as he hated his father
for the pressure he put on him,
he knew it was because he was special,
because he had a gift,
because he saw something in him
that could one day lead to greatness.
(WHISTLE TRILLS)
Are you kidding me?
(MUTTERS)
- (GRUNTING)
- (WHISTLE TRILLS)
REFEREE: Hey. You're out of the game.
FREDERICK: You get emotional, you lose.
You get angry, you lose.
- Dad, he called me...
- I don't give a good goddamn.
Why do you think he's talking
to you in the first place?
- Because he...
- Because he's trying
to get a rise out of you.
Trying to make you upset, lose focus.
That's his game. That's
the world's game.
They want to push on you,
poke on you, see exactly
how much you can take.
And how much you can take is
what will ultimately define you.
Because the measure of a
man is in how he reacts.
How am I supposed to react?
By taking everything you feel,
all your frustrations,
your anger, your rage,
you bottle it up,
you take your position,
and when that snap comes,
- you let it explode.
- (WHISTLE TRILLS)
QUARTERBACK: Hut!
♪ ♪
(CROWD CHEERING)
RUE: The truth was, McKay was shy,
but winning gave him confidence.
And that confidence was the
result of his dad's beliefs.
Routine. Routine. Routine.
He was recruited to play
division one football
at the state college, 30
miles from his house.
(APPLAUSE)
He began to imagine a life in the NFL.
- This is it, son.
- (BOTH LAUGHING)
- This is it.
- Yeah.
RUE: He knew he was smarter
than most football players,
and that he would take the money
he earned and invest it wisely.
He would use it to build an empire.
- (PLAYERS GRUNTING)
- And then he got to college,
and he realized that everyone
on the team was as good as him,
- if not better.
- (WHISTLE TRILLS)
He spent all of preseason on the bench.
When the offensive coordinator
would break down plays,
he'd find his mind wandering,
trying to do the math
on the odds of him going pro.
If there were 129 D1 teams,
and 85 players per team,
that made him one of 10,965.
And he realized...
OFFENSIVE COORDINATOR: 17-yard game...
RUE: ...he didn't stand
a chance of going pro.
But at the same time, he
started dating Cassie.
You are literally the most
beautiful girl I've ever seen.
RUE: And as stupid as it sounds,
he fell in love with her.
That's probably what was
getting in the way.
Cassie is all he ever thought about,
and those fucking photos
and that fucking video.
He just couldn't understand
how she could have so
little respect for herself.
But the thing that really pissed him off
was when she'd play dumb about
it, like at the carnival.
What have I done, McKay?
It's not like it's that big
of a fucking secret, Cassie.
RUE: I mean, even her mother said it.
I tell you, it's not easy
to hold her attention.
Like mother, like daughter.
RUE: But he also liked the
way she made him feel.
And he liked the way she
dressed, to a certain point.
But it's not like he would say
anything, he wasn't that possessive.
And he liked how she'd walk in the room,
- and every guy would turn their head.
- Hey.
RUE: That's what made it fun.
Hey.
I've seen you around, but
I don't think we've met.
I'm Daniel.
Nice to meet you, Daniel. I'm Cassie.
RUE: They were jealous of him,
because she was his.
♪ I only have eyes ♪
♪ For you ♪
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com
RUE: Every time I feel good,
I think it'll last forever.
Wow. (CHUCKLES) Um...
You... You look... fucking amazing.
Thank you. I don't really
feel it, but... you know.
RUE: But it doesn't.
Um, you smell like alcohol.
Uh, I mean, it's Halloween, right?
Right. (SIGHS) Yeah.
(RAP MUSIC PLAYING)
RUE: Daniel was throwing a party.
- You Ted Bundy?
- You're Alabama Worley.
Yes, I am.
RUE: Cassie was very
proud of her costume.
In fact, she had worn
it last night, too.
SUZE: Holy smokes! Look at you! Wow!
Isn't Halloween tomorrow, hon?
At college, they have Halloween
parties all weekend, Mom.
SUZE: Oh.
Aw, sweetie, you look so beautiful.
CASSIE: I'm Alabama Worley.
From True Romance?
MCKAY: Look, I'm gonna be
honest with you, Cass.
I feel like if we go to this party
and you're dressed like that,
I ain't gonna ever hear the end of it.
In, like, a good way or a bad way?
In a bad way.
Okay, so what do you
want me to do about it?
- This isn't even a real costume, okay?
- Yeah, it is!
- What's wrong with a football player?
- GIRL: Woo!
Welcome to Sig Pi Nu, bitches!
Straight up. That's the coolest
Halloween costume I've ever seen.
Thanks, Daniel.
I love the scene where they
fuck in the telephone booth.
Me too.
(SCOFFS)
Ted Bundy was taller.
So?
RUE: Kat's parents were out
of town for the weekend,
which was good, because it gave her
the freedom to focus on
the important things...
♪ I'm a thick bitch, I need tempo ♪
RUE: ...expanding her empire,
and collecting her motherfucking bag.
♪ Kitty cat, kitty cat,
kitty, kitty cat ♪
♪ Prrr me a glass, boy,
I like my water wet ♪
You're so fucking worthless.
RUE: She now had four men that she
cammed with on a regular basis.
All of whom she affectionately
referred to as her "pay pigs."
- Let me see you oink, piggy.
- Oink, oink!
- (SNORTING)
- Weeeee!
- (OINKING)
- (LAUGHING)
♪ Slow songs, they for
skinny hoes, can't move... ♪
My dream in life is to bankrupt you.
RUE: She was a getting a
number of incoming requests
for cam sessions, most of
which she turned down.
(PHONE CHIMES)
And then, last night...
_
(CHIMES)
- Wow, you look fuckin' cool.
- Wow.
- KAT: It's, like, whatever.
- (BOTH CHUCKLE)
I think I'm gonna get
really fucked up tonight.
Mm. Same.
KAT (CHUCKLING): Cool.
- (RAP MUSIC PLAYING)
- (ROWDY CHATTERING)
RUE: The only other time
I'd ever seen Jules drink
was the night of McKay's party.
It's not like I'm a drag and want
everyone to be sober around me.
It's just, something felt off.
Tequila makes me aggressive.
Ugh. Tequila makes me want to dance.
I, uh, I once took, like, ten Vicodin,
and drank an entire thing
of tequila, and then,
I, like, blacked out for three days.
But while I was blacked out, I,
like, still went to school
and did homework and shit.
It was really weird.
Well, let's not do that tonight.
Uh, I won't. I'm... I'm clean,
so we're good. (CHUCKLES)
Wait a minute. I was supposed
to be your chaperone.
But now I'm drunk.
I don't, like, actually
need a chaperone.
Oops.
- Um, where's Lexi?
- KAT: Uh, she's...
kind of hard to miss.
I'm Bob Ross.
The painter from PBS?
- (CHUCKLES)
(SNORTS)
SUZE: (LAUGHS)
Hey, creepy.
The whole point of Halloween
is to look attractive.
No, it's not.
Oh, really?
You do me a favor and you count
how many girlfriends of yours
are dressed up like 50-year-old men.
Report back to me.
Is it too much?
- No.
- Absolutely not.
KAT: Wow.
RUE: You know when you're with someone
and things just aren't right?
But you're afraid to ask, because
the answer might be worse
than the feeling right now.
- Wait, did you guys hear about Nate?
- KAT: No.
RUE: Nate had been temporarily expelled.
Nate, if you're innocent,
you act innocent.
You walk in here with
your head held high.
Michael, good to see you.
- MICHAEL: Good to see you, too, Cal.
- How are you?
- Good, good.
- CAL: Booth in back?
Yeah, yeah. One second. Let me...
Let me check on that for you.
- You gonna get the mac and mash?
- AARON: Yeah, probably.
What about you? Mac and mash?
NATE: No, I'll probably
just have the broccoli.
Broccoli, right, with the garlic.
Yeah, that's a good dish.
MARSHA: I wonder what's
taking him so long?
- Good to see you, Cal.
- Tim, likewise.
Yeah. Listen, um...
Come here.
I don't want to make a big to-do,
because I know you're here with
your family and everything,
but the situation with
your son, it's just...
A lot of people are talking, and...
- He's innocent, Tim. He didn't do it.
- I know. I know.
It's just, with him here and
at this time, it's just...
(CAL AND TIM SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Look, if you want to wait in the car,
- I'll get your order to go.
- Hmm.
I'm gonna remember this.
Have a nice night.
I told you it was a stupid idea.
RUE: At first, Nate spent
most of his days in bed.
(WHIRRING)
RUE: Then he decided to spend his
days driving around aimlessly.
(WHIRRING)
RUE: Sometimes he'd check in on Maddy.
RUE: Sometimes he'd check in on Jules.
(WHIRRING)
(DOG BARKING)
RUE: Or watch her house at night.
He met Maddy every Friday
night at the motel.
He looked forward to it every week.
Maddy always made him feel better.
♪ ♪
Get your fucking finger out of my face.
...fucking one time.
- Let me talk.
- (NATE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
RUE: And in turn, he
made Maddy feel better.
♪ I need you to hold me down... ♪
(MADDY MOANING)
♪ Will you hold me down ♪
(NATE PANTING)
♪ I need you to hold me... ♪
Do you think it's always
gonna be like this?
I don't know.
I feel like you need a plan.
♪ ♪
(WHIRRING)
♪ And a bang, bang, bang at the window ♪
♪ A bang, bang, bang at the back door ♪
(RAP SONG CONTINUES)
- Is she okay?
- I don't know.
- LEXI: Does she normally drink?
- RUE: No.
Something's definitely going on.
(SIGHS)
- This must be weird.
- What?
Like, being a teenager,
but not really being able
to do teenager stuff.
Yeah, well, when I'm an adult,
I won't be able to do
adult things, either.
Is that Gia?
You gotta be fucking joking.
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here? What
the fuck are you doing here?
- TROY: Getting lit.
- (BOTH CHUCKLE)
I'll deal with your ass later. Get up.
- TROY: What?
- I said get the fuck up.
_
Fuck you.
Now let me just be real
straight with you.
You ever been to rehab, Roy?
- No, I'm Troy. I'm...
- Roy, Troy. I don't give a fuck.
- I said have you ever been to rehab?
- No.
Well, in rehab, there are some
real fucked-up motherfuckers.
We're talking people who are
on the hook for armed robbery,
attempted murder, real fucked-up shit.
- Hardcore motherfuckers.
- LEXI: It's true.
I went once. It was scary.
You know what happens when you spend
an extended amount of time in rehab?
You tend to make friends with
those hardcore motherfuckers.
So let me be very clear with you.
If you so much
as go past first base
with my little sister,
or try to get her high again,
I will call Omar, I will call Marlo.
I will call Avon, I will
call Brother Mouzone,
I will call fuckin' Bodie, and
I will call fucking Stringer.
And I will have these motherfuckers
standing outside of your front lawn.
- Do you hear me?
- Or even Wee-bey.
A hundred percent. Do you know
what kind of people these are?
These are the kind of people who
will strip you fucking naked,
and go to work on you
with a pair of pliers
and a blowtorch. Do you hear me?
- Rue, I think he understands.
- I don't think he understands.
- Tell her you understand.
- I understand.
RUE: There you go. Now go in there,
tell my little sister she looks nice.
(SNORTS)
Gia, I think you look
really nice tonight.
- Really?
- Yeah, really.
TROY: Uh, you want a drink or
anything or something to eat?
They got fruit punch, you
know, if you're thirsty.
♪ ♪
♪ Act one, scene four, yeah ♪
♪ Run, Ricky, run, run, nigga,
run, jump, nigga, jump ♪
♪ Come here they come,
run, run, run, run ♪
♪ Gun with the drum, bum, bitty,
bum, slump in the trunk ♪
♪ My city go dumb, dumb, dumb, dumb ♪
♪ 151, rum and a blunt, young
nigga numb, numb, numb ♪
♪ And he got a little gun ♪
♪ A little-bitty killer
really doing it for fun... ♪
(HISSES, LAUGHS)
I'm, like, a street vampire.
- I can see that.
- Yeah.
Um, you dressed as a slutty nun?
I'm Thana from Ms. 45.
Huh. Nice.
Um, what's that?
It's a movie about this mute seamstress,
who gets brutally raped at gunpoint.
And at the end, she
puts on a nun costume,
goes to a Halloween party
and shoots everybody.
- That's cool.
- Yeah, you should watch it.
Um, can I ask you a question?
Sure.
Um... like, um...
What happened the night of the carnival?
'Cause I feel like it felt like we
were, like, having a lot of fun
when we were, like, hanging out.
And then you just kind
of, like, disappeared.
What is, like, your weird fascination
with me? I don't get it.
What? I don't have a weird
fascination with you.
Okay. Say we hung out that night.
And then what?
Um...
I... I don't know. And then we
would, like, hang out again.
Ethan, why would we hang out again?
'Cause we, like, enjoyed hanging out?
Ethan, if you want me to
suck your dick or fuck you,
just say it, but...
stop acting like we'll be
boyfriend and girlfriend,
because the chances of that happening
are, like, literally zero.
Thanks, bro.
(CLEARS THROAT)
- Hey, what's up, kid?
- Hey, man.
Uh, look I owe you an apology.
Nah, come on, now. We're good.
Bro, man. I, um...
I said some really fucked
up shit I didn't mean.
Listen, Rue. You a drug addict.
I don't take nothin' a drug
addict says personally.
'Cause I don't believe
nothin' a drug addict say.
I love you, I hate you. You
the best. Go fuck yourself.
It's all the same shit.
You know what I'm sayin'?
- Y'all just lookin' for a angle in.
- RUE: Yeah, I know, but...
As your friend, I need you
to know that I'm sorry.
- And I love you.
- I love you, too, kid.
And thank you for not...
selling me drugs.
As your friend, I got you.
(SIGHS)
FEZCO: You sober?
(EXHALES) Yeah.
FEZCO: And how's that?
You know, it's weird.
I've been fucked up so long that
it kind of feels like a new drug.
I feel you.
The highs are high.
But the, uh...
The lows are low.
♪ ♪
♪ When I think of you ♪
♪ My heart ♪
♪ Remembers ♪
♪ All the love we never had ♪
♪ Just me and you ♪
♪ Do-do-do, do-do-do, do-do-do, do-ooh ♪
♪ When I think of you... ♪
RUE: The truth was, Cassie and McKay
were in a really weird place.
♪ I remember ♪
♪ Springtime ♪
♪ That was when we fell in love ♪
You gonna stay mad?
You think you can stay mad.
You can't stay mad at
me. Look at this face.
- (CASSIE LAUGHS)
- Huh?
♪ And I still think of you ♪
♪ And the promise we made ♪
(GIGGLES)
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
- FRAT GUY: McGay!
- (CASSIE SCREAMS)
- Get him!
- (YELLING)
- CASSIE: Stop!
- (YELLING CONTINUES)
Oh, fuck! Stop!
(YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
CASSIE: Stop! Get off of him!
Stop!
FRAT GUY: Fuck me, McKay!
FRAT GUYS (CHANTING): McGay!
McGay! McGay! McGay!
CASSIE: Get the fuck
off of him! Stop it!
- Stop!
- FRAT GUY: Oh, fuck me, McGay, yeah!
- Woo!
- (FRAT GUYS LAUGHING)
FRAT GUY: Sig Pi Nu, bitch!
- (PANTS)
- (DOOR SLAMS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY) Babe?
(SHUDDERING)
_
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(SIGHS)
(SOBS SOFTLY)
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
(SHUDDERING)
Hey.
Are you okay?
I'm good.
CASSIE: I can't believe they
did that to you, McKay.
- It was so fucked up...
- Cassie, it's all good.
It's not that big of a deal.
Why do you have your shirt on?
I don't know, McKay, like...
eight guys just came in here and
it was really fucked up and weird.
So do you not want to have sex anymore?
No, I mean... I mean, I guess.
Of course.
Well, then, get undressed.
Do you want me to put it in my mouth?
Just give me a second. Hold on.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING, PANTING)
(MCKAY BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MCKAY GRUNTS, GASPS)
(SNIFFLES)
♪ Sittin' here lonely
like a broken man ♪
♪ I serve my time doing the best I can ♪
♪ High walls and bars,
they're surrounding me ♪
♪ But I don't want your sympathy, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, baby, oh, baby ♪
♪ I just need your tender lovin' ♪
♪ To keep me sane in this burnin' oven ♪
♪ When my time is up, be my rebirth ♪
♪ Like I was worth on
God's green Earth ♪
♪ My rebirth, my rebirth ♪
♪ Baby, yeah, mean it's my rebirth ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
What are you doing?
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, baby, yeah, baby ♪
♪ Come on, yeah, come on, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
Yo, ain't that your
homegirl right there?
(SPLASHING)
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Can't you feel my love? ♪
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- ♪ Baby, baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ I need you, baby, squeeze you, baby ♪
_
♪ Baby, you girl, baby ♪
♪ I love you ♪
What's your number?
What?
How many people have you had sex with?
Like, um, like, sex-sex?
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, sex-sex.
Um...
Oh. Holy shit, you're a
fucking virgin, aren't you?
- I mean, uh...
- Is that why you wanna fuck me?
- What? No, no. No. That's not...
- So... So you don't...
No, I mean, I mean, I...
You do or you don't
want to fuck me, Ethan?
I do want to fuck you.
Well, I don't fuck virgins.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Oh.
Why?
'Cause, they just, get too
emotionally attached.
Plus, they're too shy.
I like to fuck people
who know how to fuck.
(MOANS SOFTLY)
- (KAT MOANS SOFTLY)
- ETHAN: You're, like, soaking.
(MOANS)
What are you doing?
Oh. (GASPS)
- Oh!
- Does that feel good?
Yeah, yeah. Oh, right there. Wait.
(MOANS)
♪ ♪
Jules, what are you doing?
JULES: Although I joy in thee,
I have no joy in this contract tonight.
What are you talking about? I
don't know what that means.
It's too rash. Too
unadvised. Too sudden.
Too like the light in which
thou doth cease to breathe.
Jules, you're drunk, okay?
And you sound like an idiot. Can
you please get out of the pool?
Ere, one can say it
lightens sweet good night,
this bud of love by
summer's ripening breath
may prove a beauteous
flower when we next meet.
RUE: And maybe Ali was
right about Jules.
'Cause this doesn't feel good.
Stop, okay. Can you stop?
Stop. Stop.
- S-Stop, stop. Jules...
- (SPLASHING)
RUE: I just wish she'd
told me about last night.
What do you want?
NATE: I need something from you.
Nate, why would I do a
single thing for you?
'Cause I'll put you in jail.
Or on a sex offender registry.
I mean, it's your choice.
I don't want to force
you to do anything.
(COUGHING)
(LAUGHS)
(COUGHS) Oh!
♪ ♪
JOCK: Yo, Stingray McKay.
- What's up, man?
Have you seen Cassie?
Yeah. I think she's dancing.
(SNIFFLES)
Um... Daniel, I can't.
But I'm dying to fuck you.
I know, but we can't.
Why?
'Cause I'd feel really guilty about it.
But I wouldn't.
♪ ♪
_
(DANIEL BREATHING HEAVILY)
All right.
Wait.
- You're not turned on?
- It's not about that.
So we can't have sex?
No.
But I can kiss you.
♪ ♪
Can I feel you up?
(WHISPERS): No.
So I can't do that. And
I can't finger you.
Um-mm.
But feel how hard my dick is.
Come on. You have no
idea how much it hurts.
Like, it's so fucking painful.
♪ ♪
You're the most beautiful
girl I've ever seen.
Has anyone ever told you that?
- Oh. Sorry, go ahead.
- GIRL: Hey, close the door!
LEXI: Hey!
Lex. (CHUCKLES) What's up?
Have you seen your sister?
Oh, she went home a while ago.
All right, yeah, 'cause she's not
answering my phone calls right now.
- Oh, she's probably sleeping.
- All right, well,
when you see her, can you
tell her to give me a call?
- Yeah, definitely.
- Okay. Thank you.
Hey.
Aren't you, uh, supposed to
be that painter guy from PBS?
- Yeah, Bob Ross.
- Bob Ross. That's funny.
Thank you.
Daniel, come on.
Cassie. Look.
I really like you. I
wouldn't tell anyone.
- I know.
- Okay.
So no one will know.
Daniel, I'm... I feel really
drunk. I should just go home.
- What, are you joking?
- No. I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
(SCOFFS)
Who the fuck do you think you are?
What?
Well, this is literally the second
time you've done this to me.
So, if we're not gonna fuck
then what are we doing?
Are you being serious?
You think I'm here because
I'm interested in you?
In what you have to say? Or
what you think about things,
as if you're so fucking interesting?
Fuck, are you dumb.
You came on to me, remember?
And ever since then,
you show up, you lead me on,
and then you whine about
your fucking boyfriend.
Like, every time you start
talking, I think to myself,
who the fuck does this
girl think she is?
You are so fucking boring.
Hey.
I'm gonna be honest with you,
because no one else will.
Any guy who says he's interested
in you beyond just fucking you,
is full of shit.
So good luck with your boyfriend.
Wow. You're crying now.
What else is new?
♪ ♪
♪ To your soul ♪
♪ Cry ♪
(MOANING)
- What?
- Uh, I, uh...
I just gotta go... I
gotta use the bathroom.
All right. Okay.
♪ You leave in the morning
with everything ♪
♪ you own in a little black case ♪
(SIGHS) Fuck.
(WHISPERS): Shit. Fucking...
(SOFTLY): Fucking idiot. Goddamn it.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
What the fuck?
Rue? Rue?
Rue.
What happened?
- Um, I'm a burden.
- What?
Yeah. Um, I'm sor... I'm just...
I'm a burden, and it is what it is,
and it's embarrassing, and it's
stupid, but, um, it's true.
- So, I'm sorry.
- No, don't say that.
You're not a burden.
♪ Run away, turn away,
run away, turn away ♪
♪ Run away ♪
♪ Pushed around and kicked around ♪
♪ Always a lonely boy ♪
♪ You were the one that
they'd talk about... ♪
JULES: Rue!
- What's wrong?
- I think we're gonna head out.
No. No, it's just 'cause
you're not dancing with me.
That's not it, Jules.
Jules, you're soaking
wet, and really drunk.
You're dry. And dressed like Bob Ross.
- Okay, I think we're gonna go.
- (JULES LAUGHS)
Don't be fucking boring.
This whole town is so fucking
boring. I don't care.
Uh, would you like to go with us, Jules?
Okay, well, then, how
are you gonna get home?
I don't know.
And I don't care.
LEXI: Okay, let's go.
I can't... I can't fucking leave her.
♪ Run away, turn away,
run away, turn away ♪
♪ Run away ♪
♪ Run away, turn away,
run away, turn away ♪
♪ Run away ♪
♪ Cry, boy, cry ♪
♪ Cry, boy, cry, boy, cry ♪
Fuck.
MCKAY: My whole life, I've been
working towards this one thing.
Going pro. Being the greatest.
And for as long as I can remember,
I thought that was actually possible.
Then I get to school, and...
I look around, everyone's good.
Like really, really good.
I don't know, Dad.
I'm not the best.
I know if I'm not the best, there's
no way I'm getting drafted.
I don't know what to do, Dad.
It's all in your head.
You let doubt creep in, you're done.
♪ Run away, turn away,
run away, turn away ♪
♪ Run away ♪
♪ Run away, turn away,
run away, turn away ♪
♪ Run away ♪
(SNIFFLES)
- Morning, Tyler.
- (GASPS, SHUDDERS)
(WHISPERS): Fuck. Oh, God.
- Sit down, Tyler.
- Please, man.
Please don't fucking
hurt me again. Please.
Tyler, I'm not gonna hurt you.
You're in a fucking neck brace.
Just sit down.
I want to have a mature
conversation. Come on.
- About what?
- Your options. It's okay. Sit.
- What are my options?
- Not good, man.
- But one's better than the other.
- Oh, fuck.
Please, dude.
I-I was in the hospital for,
like, seven days. I-I...
My retina detached, and
I can't... I can't see,
and, and... (SIGHS) I get
migraines constantly,
and I can barely breathe
through my nose...
Tyler. Tyler.
I don't care.
I need you to take a breath. Relax.
I need you to go in your room
and put some clothes on.
Then I need you to get in
your car and drive down
to the East Highland police station.
You're gonna walk up
to the receptionist,
and you're gonna tell her that
you'd like to confess to a crime.
What crime?
The second night of the carnival,
you ran into Madeline Perez,
who's a junior at East Highland High.
You'd been stalking her since she
turned down your sexual advances.
You confronted her and asked her
why she'd been ignoring you.
She said it was because
she had a boyfriend.
You became enraged, and you choked her.
What's my other option?
Well, I mean, go about your day.
But, at some point,
Madeline Perez is gonna go down to
the East Highland police station.
(SNIFFS) She's gonna walk
up to the receptionist.
She's gonna say that she'd
like to report a crime.
- What crime?
- On the weekend before school started,
she went to a party.
She got intoxicated.
She was raped in the swimming pool
by a 22-year-old college
student named Tyler Clarkson.
Who, on the second night of the carnival
assaulted and raped her again.
You cannot prove that I
was at the carnival.
- You sure about that?
- Yeah.
- 'Cause I was here.
- Here.
Alone?
I'm not gonna confess to a
crime that I didn't do.
Then we'll make you confess
to one that you did.
Either way, it doesn't fucking matter.
♪ ♪
- Can I help you?
- Yes.
I'm here to confess to a crime.
DETECTIVE RILEY: Do you
recognize that man?
MADDY: Yes.
He's the guy who assaulted me
the night of the carnival.
Something about this whole thing just...
I don't know. It just feels odd.
Riley, we got a girl in 202 who says
she witnessed the Perez assault.
JULES: I was walking to the bathroom.
And, uh... I saw this guy
yelling at this girl,
behind one of the trailers.
And, I kind of, like, stopped
and looked for a second.
And then he grabbed her by the
neck and kind of, like...
pushed her up against the
side of the trailer.
And then I immediately
recognized that it was Maddy.
And I knew... I knew the guy's
face from somewhere. I just...
couldn't, like, place it.
Uh, and then...
Last night, I realized
where I knew him from.
And, uh, he's the guy that
hooked up with Maddy the
night of McKay's party.
DETECTIVE RILEY: Did anyone coerce you
into making this statement today?
No.
DETECTIVE RILEY: And you realize
that filing a false police report
or making false statements to the police
impeding a criminal investigation
is a very serious crime,
punishable by up to
seven years in prison.
I do.
DETECTIVE RILEY: I'll
ask you one more time.
Are you telling us the truth?
Happy Halloween.
♪ ♪
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(CROWD CHATTERING, CHEERING)
CROWD (CHANTING): Nate!
Nate! Nate! Nate!
Nate! Nate! Nate! Nate!
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (CHANTING): Nate! Nate! Nate! Nate!
Nate! Nate! Nate! Nate!
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
♪ ♪
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com
♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah, ah ♪
♪ Goddess I, it's all right ♪
♪ Lovin' is a fairy tale,
least in my head it's so ♪
♪ Childish-like, immature ♪
♪ Batman, Robin mess everything... ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ I feel like dyin' for sure ♪
♪ Blockin' the pond for sure ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ I feel like dyin' for sure ♪
♪ Blockin' the pond for sure ♪
♪ Pompous-like, Pomeranian ♪
♪ You say I'm a dog, and I'm
crazy, yeah, may be true... ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
♪ But I never stray from you, shoo-op ♪
♪ Always by your side,
tongue out for the ride ♪
♪ Darlin', I'll stay with you ♪
- ♪ Just to lay with you ♪
- ♪ Ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ I feel like dyin' for sure ♪
♪ Blockin' the pond for sure ♪
RUE: Cassie's family wasn't perfect.
♪ (ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
But Cassie was.
You're an angel.
RUE: She'd made a couple of mistakes.
They weren't things you
couldn't come back from.
So, how are the suburbs?
I came here so I wouldn't
have to think about it.
CAL: I don't know how you
got outta the situation.
I just hope it didn't teach
you the wrong lesson.
I need your help.
Let me say a single word.
RUE: Life was always this way.
One endless, suffocating loop.
You know this isn't gonna end well.
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪