(DOOR OPENS)
(SIGHS)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
(CREAKING)
(LAUGHS)
(BOTH SPEAKING POLISH)
(SLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ Dear diary
what a day it's been ♪
♪ It's been just like a dream ♪
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
♪ Wasn't where
I should have been ♪
♪ For goodness sake
♪ What's happening to me
♪ Write lightly
yours truly, dear diary ♪
(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
Niko.Hey.
(SPEAKING POLISH)
(CHUCKLES)
(NIKO SPEAKING POLISH)
(NIKO CHUCKLES)
(COMMENTATOR SPEAKING IN POLISH)
(ALL SPEAKING POLISH)
(GLASSES CLINKING)
(SPEAKING POLISH)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(ALL CHEERING)
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(SNIFFS)
(BLOWING)
(SIGHS)
(MESSAGE ALERT)
(DOOR OPENS)
AUDREY: I could pop out
during my lunch.
Okay. I'll see you then.
(MUNCHING)
JAMIE: On the phone
for three weeks.
I've been trying
to get through to you.
(TAPPING KEYBOARD)
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(SNIFFS)
You do realize that's my desk?
Don't you guys hot-desk?
Yeah. And that's
the hot-desk I choose.
Every single day.
Fine.
(EVE MUNCHING)
Would you like
some of my Coco Pops?
Yes, please.
Here you go.
(KEYBOARD TAPPING) Okay, where did we get to
with the money trail?
Er, with Kruger dead, we're
kind of back to square one.
Let's take a look
at the other kills.
There's got to be a connection.
BEAR: There's
a political agitator
in Catalonia, responsible
for organizing violent protests.
Then...
a CEO of a French
semiconductor company
with no links to Spain, at all.
What is that smell?
I can't smell anything.
There's something
about this I've seen before.
What's that? Something about...
Something about the powder.
No, no, no. What's that?
Pants.
Don't put them in my bin!
Look up, Soviet-era murders.
In their early '80s, I think.
Something to with,
er, the Olympics,
or a sports team... Eve.
You need to sign for this.
Oh?
Thanks.
BEAR: Is it your birthday?
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, guys, it's Eve's birthday.
COLLEAGUE 1: Happy Birthday.
COLLEAGUE 2: Happy Birthday.
WOMAN: Happy Birthday. You're supposed
to share the cake!
(SLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERS)
Is it really your birthday?
What? Today. Is it really
your birthday?
Actually, yes, it is.
How does it feel?
What? Waking up in the office
on your big day.
Er, what makes you say that?
(INHALES)
Look, I can't have you
camping out on the sofa.
Where's Bear gonna
take his power naps?
I'll find somewhere else.
Where?
Oh, I didn't realize
you had, er...
dependents.
Bathroom's down the hall.
Cistern makes a weird noise.
Okay.
(SIGHS)
(BANGS)Ow! Shit!
(EXHALES)
(TALKING ON TV)
Oi!
Oh, no, it's okay. You have it.
Consider it a birthday gift.
(SIGHS)
Thanks.
You're like a sad teenager,
waiting for a like on Instagram.
(CHUCKLES)
Don't you like having fun?
Honestly, I don't know
if I can any more.
That's bollocks.
Oh, well, you don't...
(CHUCKLES)
You don't know what it's like when
you've chosen to destroy your own life.
I promise you,
whatever you've done,
is not half as bad as the
stuff in my checkered past.
I know that's not true.
Mmm-hmm.
This morning
I took a piss in the shower.
You did not!
(CHUCKLES) Yup.
Just let it go. Your turn.
I (SIGHS) have...
never bought the Big Issue.
You can do better than that.
Er... (BLOWS)
I was unfaithful to my husband.
I put him in so much danger,
he ended up in hospital
with PTSD.
I took my kid to the zoo
when I was high on ketamine.
I stabbed someone.
JAMIE: GBH charge when I was 18.
I left a man to die
so I could save a psychopath.
JAMIE: My best friend died
on the drugs I gave him.
I...
Jesus. Really?
Do not think that you are
the only self-loathing
arsehole in the room, ever.
(SIGHS)
JAMIE: Choices, Eve.
It's all about choices.
(FLUSHING)
(SIGHING)
What do you want from me?
(MOBILE BUZZES)
Oh?
(SLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
BEAR: Eve!
Does this look familiar?
Chalk.
This was in 1974.
It was a suspected
sporting rivalry.
Like a Russian Lee Bowyer
and Kieron Dyer.
Except no one died.
No one was convicted?
Nope. Not even a suspect.
So what's all this
got to do with Kenny?
It doesn't, on the surface,
but if you take
a look at the Catalan murder...
(MESSAGE CHIMES)
JAMIE: Okay, they're similar.
No, they're not similar.
They're the same.
Our current assassin clearly
copied this killer, which means...
Er... JAMIE: What?
Whoever this killer was,
might lead us to The Twelve.
This was over forty years ago.
I mean, how are we supposed
to find this person now?
Eve?
I have to go. What?
Choices. It's all about choices.
What the bloody hell
are you talking about?
(PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOG BARKING)
(HAMMERING)
Niko?
(DOG CONTINUES BARKING)
(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
(HAMMERING)
Niko!
(COCK CROWS)
(SIREN WAILING)
(HORNS HONKING)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
Irina? Want to skive off?
Ask me in Sanskrit.
No.
You're going to sneak
out of school with me
because I'm your father,
because I'm telling
you to do it.
(SPEAKING SANSKRIT)
How does your mother's new
boyfriend afford a German car?
He's an oil company exec.
He's a crook.
Like you.
But he doesn't buy
you ice cream, huh?
Can I stay with you, tonight?
Tonight? Ooh...
I have to be back
in England tonight.
Is England better
than your daughter?
Yes. No.
England is terrible.
Way worse than you.
But it's my job
to do terrible things.
You job?
Working for the Russian
State Security Service, Irina.
That's a big deal.
Do you think I'm a moron?
You might pretend
to be working for the FSB.
to be helping MI6.
We both know what
you're really working for...
Yourself.
And it's only a matter of time
before they all catch up with you.
And you'll be dead
and I'll be even more alone
and miserable than I am now.
I will try to patch
things up with your mother.
That's not what I want. What, then?
I want you to have a plan.
I have a plan.
You're full of shit.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
The day it happened,
Charles sent me
such an odd email.
(SNIFFLES)
I think he must have
written it in a hurry or...
What did it say?
Erm...
something about a lot of money
that had gone missing.
He'd worked out who'd taken it
and...
if anything happened to him,
I had to forward
an email onto someone.
Who? I didn't recognize
the address.
It... It had, erm,
some kind of file
attached to it.
I just have this feeling
he was mixed up
with something awful.
Did you send the file?
I'm in such a muddle.
I don't know what to do.
This is what we do.
You send this file to me, okay?
Yes.
And we get you somewhere safe
as soon as possible.
I could go to the holiday house.
That's perfect.
(MOBILE RINGING)
Boo!
(CHUCKLES)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING
ON HEADPHONES)
So not over me.
So not over...(TIMER RINGS)
Ah. You made me cake.
It's not for you.Oh.
It really doesn't
look like the picture. I know that.
Okay.
No, wait, wait!
Just because it looks bad
doesn't mean it tastes bad.
Throw it away.
Don't do that. DASHA: You don't deserve
nice things
if you don't look after them.
So London went well?
Yeah, it was good.
DASHA: Did you do anything
when you were there?
Hmm. Hmm.
A Jack the Ripper walking tour.
Why are you lying to me?
I'm not.
I gained valuable insight
into Victorian gender politics.
Who did you see in London?
Okay.
Fine.
Not that it's anything
to do with you.
I saw Konstantin.
You're close, Villanelle.
You're so close to getting
what you want.
But you have
to play by the rules.
(GASPS)(SOFTLY) You are
so annoying today.
Oh, I'm annoying? Hmm.
(SCOFFS) She thinks
I'm annoying.
Who are you talking to?
I am just trying to save
you from yourself!
So, bear with me,
if I get a little frustrated.
They want to meet with you. Why?
They need to discuss
your new contract.
Holiday pay,
benefits, et cetera.
So I'm getting promoted?
You work well, you move up.
In the meantime,
they want you to rest.
Conserve your strength.
So, spend your money.
Get an ombre balayage.
Enjoy yourself.
But no travel, okay?
You stay put.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Yes! (SIGHS)
♪ Satan is the name he goes by ♪
♪ He gotta lot of devil
in his eye ♪
♪ He got a kiss of fire
and it burns you well ♪
♪ Breaks your heart
and it hurts like ♪
Boo!
(CHUCKLING)
You know, you really
don't have to be so dramatic.
Oh, no, no, no, don't
make me go in there.
Let's go somewhere we can talk.
Somewhere relaxing.
VILLANELLE: This would be
a really bad... Stop it.
Way to go.
Stop it!
Are you upset because soon
I'm going to be your boss?
You won't be my boss.
Don't worry,
you'll be my favorite.
All the other employees
will hate you.
What got you
in such a good mood?
It's Eve's birthday today.Ah.
But you shot her
and ruined her marriage.
Isn't that enough?
The mustache is gone?
I hear he's in Poland.
I got what you asked for.
Your family.
(HICCUPS)
You know where they are?
Not yet. But I can find out.
But I need you to
do something for me. Do something for me.
Something personal.
Off the rec... Off the record.
I really hate it
when you do that.
I'll do it.
Okay?
But please do it nicely.
Something efficient.
You want it nice
or you want it efficient?
Just make it done, okay?
(HICCUPS)
(WOMAN SPEAKING FRENCH)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Erm, it's still
very raw, you know?
Of course.
We were together
for nearly 30 years.
We knew one another inside out.
Now that he's gone, I...
VILLANELLE: You're free now.
You can be whoever you want.
But I... I don't
want to be free.
(WEEPING) I want to be a family.
(CRYING)
(VILLANELLE HICCUPPING)
You have the hiccups?
(CHUCKLING)
Can't get rid of them.
(SCREAMS)
I used to do that
with my children.
To scare the hiccups away.
Did it work?
(CHUCKLES, HICCUPS)
Oh, dear.
Try again.
(BOTH SCREAMING
AND THEN CHUCKLING)
♪ Tiptoe through the window
♪ By the window
that is where I'll be ♪
(ROARS)
(GASPS)
♪ With me
♪ Tiptoe by the garden
By the garden ♪
♪ Of the willow tree
(VILLANELLE ROARING)(BERTHA SCREAMING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(ROARING)
♪ ...in the flowers
we'll stray ♪
♪ We'll keep the showers away
♪ And if I kiss you
♪ In the garden
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(CHOKING)
(GASPING)
(HICCUPS)
♪ We'll keep
♪ The showers away
♪ And if I kiss you
in the garden
(RINGTONE)
KONSTANTIN: Is it done?
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
(ALARM BEEPING)
(FROGS CROAKING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
WOMAN: Morning, Mum.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
I didn't order this.
Erm, consider it
an olive branch.
Look, I was tone deaf,
and in the light of
everything that's happened...
I'm really rather embarrassed.
If I'd been given the proper
authority form the start,
we might've avoided
the needless death
of an innocent man.
But Kruger wasn't innocent,
was he?
Thought he was embezzling money.
Kruger was up to
his eyebrows in debt.
Foreclosures
coming out of his bottom.
His actions
were not that of a man
with a casual six million
sloshing around
in his sock drawer.
So he was framed?
How would I know?
I've been ordered
to stay away from all of this.
PAUL: Tell me what you need.
(SCOFFS) Well,
you've changed your tune.
PAUL: You had a close call.
Now if anything
had happened to you,
I would've been
partly responsible.
That's something
I take very seriously.
Losing my husband in the divorce
set me into a grief of its own.
I know
it's not the same thing...
but I just want to say...
(WHISPERS) I do understand loss.
My office.
Sorry?
Well, that's
the first thing I need.
But you don't even know
where your office is.
Well, that doesn't mean
I don't need it back.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Mum?
What are you doing home
at this hour of the day?
Why? Was I supposed
to run it past you?
No, of course not. I just...
It is a bit odd here
in the day time, isn't it?
Whatever do you find
to do with yourself?
(PAPER RUSTLING)
Must be rather dull.
Not really.
I get up to all sorts of stuff.
Have you had
any visitors lately?
Erm...
Just my friend
Lily from university.
You, erm, you don't know her.
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
(SOBBING)
Oh, Mum.
Geraldine, I've had
a very long day and, erm...
I feel so lost.
(SNIFFLES) You know?
You... You barely even
look at me and...
Nonsense. We just had
a perfectly pleasant
exchange in the hall.
I'm trying to tell you
that I'm worried about you, Mum!
You!
What for?
'Cause it's weird
to carry on like this.
Not even saying his name,
for God's sake.
I'm doing more for your brother
than you can possibly imagine.
Then talk to me about it.
Let me in.
If you and I
are to inhabit this space
together, Geraldine,
we have to respect each other,
our privacy and our grief.
I dare say there are
things you don't tell me,
though perhaps
for quite different reasons.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm going upstairs
for a lie down.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ Dark bird flies above ♪
♪ The land of dreams ♪
♪ Silent flight above ♪
♪ The shadowed streams ♪
♪ Land of crystal waters pour ♪
♪ Flows onto the
blackened shore ♪
(RECORDING OF FROGS CROAKING)
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
♪ Hovers laughing
♪ With the winter's light
♪ Calling others with him soar ♪
♪ Soar beyond the open door
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
You have hat hair.
You said you had
everything under control.
I did. I do.
Then why is she
running around London
pursuing her agent friend?
The one who wears the...
Turtleneck.
She's a little
skittish right now.
She's lot of changes.
I have it in hand,
all we need to do...
That's not how it looks.
You want to go back home,
to Russia?
Where the people
will be dancing in the street
and chanting your name?
Dasha, Dasha! Dasha.
Well, you can't.
Until we say you can.
"Skittish" is not acceptable.
Get her working.
Without this, er,
extracurricular crap.
I can kill Polastri.
No. This will cause
too many other problems.
Just drive a wedge between them.
I don't care how.
Use your, er, imagination.
Milena.
(IN POLISH)
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
(SPEAKING POLISH)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
(SPEAKING POLISH)
No more food
for you little piggies.
Good piggies.
(PIGS SNORTING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(COMMENTATOR SPEAKING POLISH)
(MOBILE CHIMING)
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
Not getting any, huh?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
(CAR APPROACHES)
(DOG BARKING)
EVE: Niko?
(HAMMERING CONTINUES)
Eve.
(CHOKING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROANING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)