Eve... she is alive.
It's not possible.
Poor Kenny.
I can't let people know
I'm looking into things.
I have Kenny's phone.
- We just guessed it was you.
- What?!
They are making me a Keeper.
They want you to work
with somebody first.
Bonjour !
Management is not easy.
It's watching someone
do job worse than you.
I deserve more. More than you.
What was Kenny working
on before he died?
There's a thumb drive.
The police have it.
I need to know what happened,
who killed him.
_
♪ A la nanita nana ♪
♪ Nanita ella, nanita ella ♪
♪ Mi niña tiene sueño ♪
♪ Bendito sea, bendito sea... ♪
♪ A la nanita nana ♪
♪ Nanita ella, nanita ella ♪
♪ Mi niña tiene sueño ♪
♪ Bendito sea... ♪
Ay, Dios mío. Dios mío, no.
No, no, no, no.
No.
¡No, no, no, no, no!
El bebé, no, por favor.
Por favor, el bebé, no, no...
¡No! ¡El bebé, no!
¡El bebé, no, por favor!
¡Se lo ruego! Se lo pido, por fa...
No...
¡No, no, no, no, no!
¡El bebé, no, por favor!
¡Te lo pido! ¡No, no!
- No!
- You really like that baby, huh?
It's not even yours.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
And what about the coroner's report?
There's no signs of a struggle.
No evidence of asphyxiation
or internal injury.
Basically, he was
absolutely fine until he...
- ... hit the ground.
- May I?
So...
... the head of the MPS
is still saying it's suicide,
despite the lack of note or motivation.
That is reassuring.
It'd be really unsettling if he
actually got something right.
Geraldine said I could
come straight in...
Oh.
Wow!
Oh, get over it, Eve.
I have all my best thoughts in the bath.
If Mo can manage, you can.
I haven't looked up in 10 minutes.
Did you get Kenny's thumb
drive back from the police?
- At quite a cost, yes.
- I'd rather not know.
- Oh, I'll... I'll meet you downstairs.
- Oh!
Who's that?
Our Bitter Pill representative.
I invited him.
Before I knew this meeting
was in a bathroom.
Mo, would you just pass
me a towel, please?
So, we have the burner
phone and the thumb drive.
What else do we have to go on?
Excellent. Good meeting.
- Meetings have biscuits.
- You can have a biscuit
when you tell me what
the point of you is.
Planning on analysing those
yourself, then, are you?
I think the world's foremost
intelligence agency might handle it.
What, that public school,
what-ho-ing, old boy's network?
I don't think a beer fridge
and a beanbag breakout area
gives you any great insight
into global politics.
- That's...
- Enough, okay? Enough!
Carolyn, you and Mo take
the phone, we'll take the...
... thumb thingy.
'Cause you know what we do from now on?
- We share.
- Wow.
That is literally the most parenting
this household has ever seen.
So, you thought this was good idea?
I'm practising my characters,
like you told me.
Young mother and baby... and Grandma.
What got into you? You have been
unfocused and manic for days.
I'm just having some fun.
Stop that. I don't like it.
You would think, after your
last managerial disaster,
you would learn to keep your head down.
It is not my fault he was an idiot.
I keep telling them to look
harder for good recruits.
But what can you do?
Eh...
You think that's funny?!
I'll show you what's funny.
You come with me,
because I've had enough.
Now, that is funny.
You want to amuse yourself, go crazy.
But I will not have you put
both of our futures at risk.
- I'm the one doing all the work.
- You think handling you isn't work?
Why you think no-one else
is prepared to do it?
Bad pension scheme?
You should get your act together.
You know? Jobs will get tougher.
And they will not let you
get away with being sloppy.
Sloppy? Hmm...
_
No.
"No"? What do you mean, "No"?
It's too soon.
I have to prepare.
I'm not ready. How about that?
Not ready for London?
All you need is anorak
and face like cheese.
You're right.
You're right. I know what I'm doing.
I can handle this.
This is bank stuff.
Financial data.
Oh, he said something about accounts.
Damn it. What was it?
Do you want one?
What? Oh... No, I... No.
Once I pop, I just can't stop.
You can. It's just about self-control.
But I don't have any self-control.
All these are different accounts,
in different locations.
One of them must have
meant something to Kenny.
That one is different.
Mm.
R-U-R'.
Code, maybe?
It is. Where's, um... ?
Where's that Rubik's Cube?
The only way I can solve this is
by taking off all the stickers.
No, we don't need to solve it.
It's cube notation.
He's told us what to do.
Okay, um, turn it right
face, 90 degrees clockwise.
Is that supposed to
mean something to me?
No.
Okay. Uh, U.
Upwards, 90 degrees.
- R'.
- Right face, anti-clockwise.
U2.
And F'.
That's it.
"Shh... nap."
"Shnap".
Panda.
Kenny named the account 'Panda'.
Kenny and I were looking into
an international organi...
Okay, but before I go on,
you have to understand
that once I tell you about them,
your lives are in danger.
- Then don't tell us...
- They're called The Twelve.
And they've infiltrated
governments and organizations
all over the world.
We don't know what their endgame is,
but we do know they've been responsible
for a significant number
of international murders.
Okay, now, Fat Panda was a
Chinese intelligence officer
killed in Berlin.
He was tracking a double
agent for The Twelve
who was being paid from
a bank account in...
... the Cayman Islands.
Right.
The double agent was an MI5
officer named Frank Haleton.
What happened to Frank?
He lost his knob...
... and his life.
In that order?
Well, The Twelve wanted a hit on him,
but the...
... but the assassin was...
- ... she had a flair for...
- She?
The account went dormant
after Frank's death,
but Kenny found it was active again.
Three bank transfers in
the last two months,
totalling just over six million euros.
And the remaining balance moved
to an account in Geneva.
So, who owns the Geneva account?
We don't know.
We need someone who can get into
some very classified banking info.
Yes, we do.
- No, we do not go to them.
- Yes, we do.
The thing is we can't trace the account.
Well, yeah. You don't set
up an account in Geneva
for transparency.
But you could trace it, right?
I thought you were
looking into the phone.
That was the deal, wasn't it?
Or did Charlie Big
Potatoes change his mind
because he didn't get a Hobnob.
- Come on. We're in this together.
- Are we?
Because no-one else is
having to work at MI6
whilst moonlighting for Carolyn,
and now you want me to trace...
Did you take this job thinking
it would be easier?
If you did, quit now, 'cause
it's only getting tougher.
I'll see what I can do.
Great.
Oh, and, uh...
That's who we think has been
on their hit-list so far.
You know, I've been going
through the MI6 case files
you and Kenny worked on.
You really should have some kind of
protection. You know that, right?
Do you have any idea what happens
to people who are protected by MI6?
What?
It's not good.
- Charles Kruger.
- It's me.
- Who's me?
- Just let me in.
Na zdorovie.
Ah!
Look at us, Kostya. We're old.
The kids are all grown up.
I'm going to see my son's
graduation next month.
This modern dance is... is so visceral!
Have you ever locked and popped, Kostya?
No! You'd, uh, displace
a hip these days.
Hey? Wouldn't you?
You wanted to see me.
Yeah.
Um...
Somebody's been siphoning money
from the Geneva account.
I managed to retrieve what's left,
but a pretty sizeable
chunk's been taken.
How much has gone?
Uh, six million, in total.
Whew!
- Do you know who?
- No.
Not yet. But I will find
the person responsible.
I'll make some calls,
see what I can find.
Uh, the money, Konstantin.
I... I prefer the money.
If you could...
... tide me over.
You know, just buys me some
time till I find the scoundrel.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
How's Irina these days?
Still a little shit?
She's like a little shit
taking a shit on a big shit.
Three shit combined
into one enormous shit.
That's wonderful!
Kids!
Kids...
_
I want to smell powerful.
I want to make people gag with it.
Can you do that for me?
Well...
... we have some lovely floral
fragrances for ladies over here.
The iris, in particular,
- is a very powerful...
- Maybe I should describe to you
what I'm thinking.
Let me get a pen.
Hmm.
I want to smell like
a Roman centurion...
... who's coming across an old foe...
... who, in battle, once...
... hurt him greatly.
Oh, but since then, the Roman
centurion has become...
... Emperor...
... and is now powerful beyond measure.
Maybe something more woody.
Mm.
I think it's wonderful
you're letting people in.
We all need intimacy in our lives.
Even people who keep
secrets for a living.
Nonsense, there are monks in China
who go years without seeing
another human being.
They probably have different kind of...
Emily Bronte. Hardly left the house.
Mum...
... I'm proud of you for
trying something new.
Dating is scary, but...
... pushing ourselves out of our
comfort zones is how we grow.
You know what's scary, Geraldine,
is how much I regret
telling you it's a date.
I'm so happy you're doing
something for you.
Kenny would be too.
He always wanted you to meet some...
Here, let me...
No, it's better without it.
And don't talk about Stalin.
He's strictly third date.
Another drink while you wait, madam?
No, thank you, Tom.
I think there comes a time
when one must admit... defeat.
Henrik?
Carolyn!
Wha...
Mwah.
Sorry.
How incredible!
I adore a coincidence!
It makes me feel I'm in the right place.
It must be, what 20 years?
Yeah.
Yeah, 21, it must be.
1999's the year I got divorced.
- Oh, yes.
- Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
For the first time.
- Well...
- Yeah.
If it makes you feel any better,
I've just had the novel experience
of being stood up.
No... What?!
Surely... You?!
Don't worry. I'll have him killed.
Listen, you, um...
Do you want to get something to eat?
What about your charming friends?
Hmm? They disgust me. Come on.
Come on. What do you fancy? Seafood?
- Oh...
- Steak? No?
There is one thing...
I must say, the years have
been good to you, Henrik.
Yeah.
Terrible lifestyle... suits me, hmm?
So, Geneva's still treating you well?
What, the bank?!
I-I... Don't get me started.
No, do go on.
There's nothing I enjoy more than
some salacious financial gossip.
Is she okay?
The official line is migraine.
I'm having an aura, Eve.
It's probably stress-related.
You know a great cure for that?
Paracetamol.
Did you find out who owns the account?
Yes.
It's a 92-year-old sugar-beet
farmer in East Anglia.
Who died nine years ago.
The real owner... is this guy.
Charles Kruger.
Born Sergei Korchmarev in East Berlin.
And who was very gorgeous in his day.
Oh, another one of your Cold
War boyfriends, Carolyn?
Don't be ridiculous, Eve.
- We barely had a night together.
- Yeah, we get it.
You had a great time in the '80s.
So, Korchmarev disappeared
from Russia around 1989,
eventually showing up in London
and presenting himself as amiable
accountant Charles Kruger.
Do you think he could actually be
the accountant for The Twelve?
I'm thinking he's definitely
worth a visit to Kensington.
- I'll head right there.
- And do what?
Wait in the car with a bottle
of pop and a bag of crisps?
Be hard enough to get him to talk to me.
He's definitely not gonna talk
to somebody he doesn't know.
- Are you sure?
- Of course I'm sure.
I know how he operates, Eve.
No, I mean...
... this is different, remember?
I'm gonna have a shower.
Oh, God...
Oh...
First Henrik, then Sergei.
It's not fun, Eve,
using people you once loved.
It's all rather painful, really.
Do you believe a word of that?
No, I think she loves it.
Would you like to make a talking bear?
This place is psychopathic.
_
I should have shot you in the head.
I should have shot you in the
head and watched you die.
I should have shot you in the head
and watched you die.
_
I can't stop thinking about you.
Eve?
Oh, Valerie, hi.
- Can I be of help?
- No. I'm just waiting for Niko.
He discharged himself.
What?!
Last week.
He was actually doing very well.
Uh, did he... leave me a note or...
... a forwarding address?
- I'm afraid I can't...
- Valerie...
I'm his wife.
He did say something about Poland.
_
Hi, Eve.
Eve!
I'm not here for you.
No! No!
Smell me, Eve.
What do I smell of to you?
Oh...
I don't want to talk about it.
- Eve?
- I said...
... I don't want to talk about it.
So, what now?
We eat toffee eclairs
and watch that doorway.
Can't we just go in?
And ruin the fun of a stake-out?
You wouldn't do that to an old spy, Mo.
Plus... if we go in...
... we're trapped.
Out here, he's accountable.
What happened?
Okay, fine.
I don't give a toss.
As long as it's got nothing to do
with what we're working on.
There is this... assassin...
... who works for The Twelve.
- Have you got to the chocolate yet?
- Mm.
I've just got it.
When I was younger...
Wait there.
Damn.
Follow him.
I don't think we're gonna
lose him, somehow.
Ah...
_
Villanelle said she wasn't here for me.
So, let's just think who The
Twelve would want to murder,
aside from me.
Right. Okay.
- Possible assassin targets.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
- Carolyn. It's Carolyn.
They must know we found
their accountant.
So, after you came to
England, what did you do?
An eclair?
Well, that won't get you that
three-book deal, Sergei.
Tell me what you're going to
wear at your son's graduation.
It's next month, isn't it?
Tell me how he does that
thing with his shoulders.
She's not picking up.
Try mine.
Should I share what I think happened
when you swapped the Stasi for HMRC?
I think you accepted a
job from The Twelve,
like the money-grabbing
bottom-feeder you are.
Am I warm?
They're on a stake-out!
Who doesn't answer their
phone on a stake-out?!
Uh-oh.
What's going on?
Nothin'.
Just everyone look innocent.
_
Ah...
Oh...
Ohh...
The husband of classical musician
and influential political
campaigner Isabel Fernandez,
was, this afternoon,
reunited with his baby
who had been missing since
Mrs. Fernandez was found dead
at her home yesterday.
He's so happy.
I'm fine.
There's no need for...
Would you, um...
... pour me a whiskey, Geraldine?
Yes, of course.
Aaaagh!
Don't wait for me in the dark like that!
It's rude!
It's bad for my heart.
Don't you want to know
why I'm in your bed?
Not really, no.
I am too tired for games
and I have to find six
million euros tomorrow.
You will never find
six million in a day.
Not even if you sold
both of your kidneys.
Technically, you don't
even own them anymore.
The Twelve do.
They own every little bit of you.
Goodnight, Villanelle.
What kind of baby do you think I was?
I think I was cute.
Hmm.
Do you think people smiled with
joy when they saw my little face?
God, you're boring.
You're more boring than that
accountant I just shot.
And accountants... are really boring.
Hey! Hey! Huh?!
Wakey-wakey, Konstantin!
I think you were ugly as hell, okay?
Right.
Well, now you're just
looking for a reaction.
No, I'm not.
I've seen a photo of you.
Very strange head. Bulbous. Unnatural.
Who was I with?
I don't remember.
Hmm.
I want to find my family.
Why?
So you can feel like dirt the whole time
about how you're letting them down?
Smell me.
No.
Smell me, hmm? What do I smell of?
What am I wearing?
- I don't know.
- Ah.
Power.
I'm wearing power, and to keep power,
you need knowledge.
You'll find them for me.
Okay?
I sleep on the couch.
Hello?
Oh...
Admit it, Eve.
You wish I was here.
- You wish I was here.
- Oh...
Admit it, Eve.
You wish I was here.
Oh, God...
Oh...
Admit it, Eve.
You wish I was here.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --