Are you faking it?
-Where is the money?
-My pocket.
-Oh, did someone die?
-It was Mo.
It's starting to feel personal.
[Grunts]
Eve: What was it you said to her
in that prison?
I offered her work,
and she refused.
Good for her.
You're a beautiful monster,
Villanelle.
Villanelle: I don't want to
do this anymore.
-We had promoted a dud.
-[Grunts]
Have you been under
any increased stress lately?
[Laughs]
Villanelle:
We have to stop running into
each other like that.
It's not good
for both of us.
(ORCHESTRA PLAYING
CLASSICAL MUSIC)
A little over-dramatic,
don't you think?
I got the tickets
yonks ago.
When you asked to meet
I thought, "Why not kill
two birds with one stone?"
What do you want,
Villanelle?
I want to know
what the canteen's like.
Here?
MI6. (CHUCKLES)
It's heavily lasagne-based.
Sometimes they branch out
into cannelloni.
What do you want?
I want to accept
your job offer.
Are things not working out
with Helene?
Helene?
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
Helene loves me.
Yeah...
Actually a bit much,
you know?
I got promoted.
Goodness.
I know!
She's very happy with me.
They all are.
But?
I'm looking
for a new challenge.
You want to kill for us now?
No.
I'm confused.
What would you do for us?
(SCOFFS)
I could do
all sorts of things.
Spy stuff,
fake moustache,
codes, information.
Who killed Mo Jafari?
(SCOFFS)
I don't know.
Who killed my son?
What?
Rather a poor start
to a job interview,
don't you think?
(SCOFFS)
You're turning me down?
I don't know what it is
you're offering.
You were trained to do
one thing and one thing only.
If you can't do that,
what use are you to me?
To anyone?
I can change.
If Villanelle has retired,
what's left?
Oksana?
I can't see that working
for MI6. Can you?
Mahler's 10th.
I've got to get down for the end
of the first movement.
Good luck.
(EKG BEEPING)
Is this really necessary?
You had a massive
heart attack.
I know. I was there for it.
(LAUGHS) Listen...
I know you like to keep people
here for observation,
but you can discharge me.
Please take your hand
off my arm.
Do you know what "haggis" is?
These Scots are barbarians.
(SIGHS) I came to say goodbye.
It's dangerous to discharge
yourself, you know.
It's more dangerous staying.
Have you been a naughty boy?
What have you heard?
Nothing.
Good.
Are you going to find her?
You know
she did this to me.
She and Polastri woman.
Are you surprised?
You tried
to kill Villanelle.
It was years ago.
I was trying
to show them that
she was not ready.
She was ready.
She was not ready.
You know your mistake?
You expected her
to play by your rules.
I had to.
You give her none.
I was old-school.
Old-fashioned.
Brutal.
The West has
turned you soft.
(SCOFFS)
She has become loser,
just like you.
Neither of you
have backbone.
You have infected her
with your disgusting
lack of ambition.
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
No. Please don't go. Please.
(WEAKLY) Please.
(EKG BEEPING)
I wish my son was here.
You need to forget him.
You need to forget
Mother Russia.
You're going to die
in this room.
If you didn't like
how I treated her,
why didn't you do
anything about it?
We are both to blame.
You are just as much a...
A...
(EKG BEEPING RAPIDLY)
(WALTZ MUSIC PLAYING)
Hi.
How are you?
Why here?
I did my first ever kill
in this country here.
I strangled a high-ranking
police officer.
He was a tango champion.
Imagine if I'd refused.
What do you think
I would have become?
An interior designer, maybe.
If you had,
it would've saved me
a lot of heartache.
Niko's in hospital.
Dasha stabbed him
through the neck
and blamed it on you.
Are you listening to me?
Do you ever think about
the past?
All the time.
That's all I think about.
It's nice to watch them.
They seem happy.
Carefree.
Well, dancing will do that.
I want to feel like that.
What happened?
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
MAN: Time for
the next dance, ladies.
We encourage all
to the dance floor,
rhythm or no rhythm.
(MUSIC STARTS UP)
Come on, then.
Dancing's not my thing.
Mine either, but it's good
to try new things.
Are you leading
or am I?
I have no idea.
(CHUCKLES) Hmm.
Do you want
to be like that?
Not any more.
Why not?
We'd never make it
that long.
We'd consume each other
before we got old.
It sounds kind of nice.
I've killed
so many people, Eve.
I know.
You should go.
Why?
Take this.
I'll meet you later.
What is it?
Freedom.
What's going on?
Our party's getting crashed.
Go, Eve.
Go.
Oy, Helene wants
to see you.
If you want to dance,
you just have to ask.
Okay.
Where does
she want to meet?
(SOFT GRUNT)
Talk me through your outfit.
I like to be comfortable.
Why?
What do you mean, "why"?
Comfortable is what
you make people
with a terminal illness.
I was trained
to wear clothes that allow
a full range
of movement.
So weird.
I was trained
to look devastating.
(POPS LIPS)
Obviously.
Isn't it funny?
Two ruthless killers,
when somebody says "jump",
we just... We just jump.
Jump, jump,
jump, jump, jump!
Autonomy's overrated.
Sheep are happier
than wolves.
(LAUGHS)
You spend your time off
surveying sheep?
It was an expression.
You know, you have almost
no sense of humour.
I take my job seriously.
Mmm.
What if I tickled you?
Would you laugh then?
Don't tickle me.
(SCOFFS)
That's a yes.
(TRAIN APPROACHING)
(HIGH-PITCHED LIP FLAP)
TRAIN ANNOUNCER: Mind the gap.
(MAKES FUNNY NOISES)
I don't care that
you've checked out.
In fact,
it's better for me.
the bigger your crisis,
the quicker that
I can take your place.
So keep having
your wobble.
Keep hoping that
the universe has got
something else lined up for you.
But do me one thing, okay?
Come quietly, little sheep.
I promise,
you'll be happier that way.
I'm sorry.
What?
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
(WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMS)
I'm sorry.
I-I didn't mean it.
(GASPING FOR BREATH)
(TRAIN ANNOUNCER SPEAKING)
Please.
Help!
Help me, please!
(SCREAMING)
♪ Nothing matters
if you bury it deep
♪ Take away the worry
What's left, you keep
♪ Never say you're sorry
if what you mean is
♪ Do what you do
and I won't hate you somehow ♪
GERALDINE:
"...for not trusting you.
For not hearing you.
"For holding you up
to the model of motherhood
"dictated by society.
"For pursuing
an intimate relationship
"with your former lover,
even if I didn't know
"I was being coerced
by him.
"And for my active faults,
judging you,
"lying to you,
thinking the worst of you."
Which I suppose
is the same as judging you.
"I bring this
acknowledgement to you
"and ask for
your forgiveness
and acceptance.
"Your loving daughter,
Geraldine."
What am I supposed to do,
applaud or...
Your turn.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Dear Geraldine, I think
it's time you left.
That's it? That's...
everything you wished
you'd ever said to me?
It's all I want to say.
So, you're throwing me out?
I'm not throwing.
I'm firmly suggesting.
Living with your mother
is no kind of life for you.
When I was your age,
I was an integral part
of a kibbutz in Tel Aviv...
In Tel Aviv,
of course you were.
As you always tell me
when you're trying
to avoid a real
conversation.
So, tell me, Mum,
what is this
really about?
It's about you
wasting your time
on Earth,
navel-gazing
and researching
natural deodorants...
That's what you
say it's about.
What is it
really about?
I'm not going to be
drawn on this, Geraldine.
So it's not about
you feeling guilty
that your ex-shag
bugged us
and used me
to get at you?
It's not, no.
Or that, that
your assistant was killed
carrying out
your orders?
Or that you haven't
found out
who "killed" Kenny yet,
because the likelihood
is he just killed himself
because he was so deeply,
bloody unhappy!
(SIGHS)
No, it's not about
any of those things.
Things are coming
to a head, that's all.
Why? What's happening?
(EXHALES)
You've got until
the end of the day.
Mum, please.
Don't "please" me,
Geraldine.
I know you think I'm heartless
but I do care, in my own way.
And I'm telling you,
you are no longer welcome here.
(EXHALES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(EVE READING)
Uh, 100 on Bruce.
What?
Thirty-eight to 50
on Bruce?
You taking
the piss?
I... I don't know.
Am I?
Comedian, are ya?
Sharon... Sharon, listen.
I think we got off
on the wrong...
Oh,
I found this on the floor
and well, do you want it?
You've not tried to bribe
someone before, have you?
(SNORTS)
Dave, d'ya see that?
Lady just tried
to bribe me.
(CHUCKLES)
Will you just
take it, please?
What is this "Bruce"?
A horse? A dog? A boxer?
Who's Bruce Fletcher?
The owner. Lives upstairs.
(SIGHS)
Can I just speak
to him, please?
Fletch, someone here
to see ya.
A woman called...
Tallulah.
Shark.
Tallulah Shark.
What d'ya want?
I'm here to make
a collection?
Collection.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CREAKS)
I expected you to look
more like a stripper.
I'm in disguise.
Have you got
a tree fern, Tallulah?
You've gotta wrap them
for the winter,
otherwise they freeze to death.
What box you
collecting from?
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION
OVER TV)
This is the
Russian's box.
Oh, he sent me.
No, he didn't.
Yes, he did.
You telling me,
that a lady like you
is mixed up
with a man like him?
I'm not a very nice lady.
All right then,
you've got the code,
I can't stop you.
(UNLOCKING BEEP)
CAROLYN: I don't like meetings
where I don't know
what I'm meeting about.
(EXHALES) I...
CAROLYN: So what's
so urgent it can't wait?
Christ, it's worse
than the MI6 in here.
Carolyn, Can... (EXHALES)
Can I make you
a cup of tea?
Why do you say it like that?
How did I say it?
Like I'm about to need one.
Carolyn...
Oh no, not you as well.
We thought it better
to show you this
face-to-face.
Show me what?
Er...
Well, we've had
a breakthrough. Please.
(CAROLYN EXHALES)
Ma'am.
For God's sake. Will someone
tell me what's going on?
Are you familiar
with Tangfastics?
Extremist organisation?
A hacktivist group?
Lone wolf?
They're a sweet.
Er, not a sweet,
sweet, though.
They're more of a sour,
sugar-coated gummy
in various different shapes.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Anyway, I get through
a packet a day.
Two if I'm stressed.
And a couple
of months ago,
I realised someone
was dipping their finger
into my Tangfastic
honey pot,
so I set up
a secret camera.
(INHALES)
(LIGHT CHUCKLE)
I haven't checked
the footage in a while
because the thief
seemed to give up,
but, er, today
I find this...
(CAROLYN GASPS)
Kenny.
Pilfering bastard.
Sorry.
Er, there's more.
BEAR: This is from
the day Kenny died.
I see.
(ZIP CLOSING)
You?
I would say
it's nice to see you
but last time,
you were leaving me to die.
Why aren't you in hospital?
I needed to collect
a package.
That package.
Give it to me.
No.
It's mine.
No. No, no.
Villanelle asked me
to get it.
Yes,
because she's supposed
to be getting it for me!
(EXHALES) Don't make
a sick man run.
You think I'm just going
to hand it over to you?
It's a gift for my daughter.
You have literally
no use for it.
Look for yourself.
I will.
Stay there.
See?
Each Russian leader
births another.
(LAUGHS)
Yeltsin's come off
poorly, huh?
Why would your daughter
want this?
She's not right in the head.
I promise you, this is just
a cheap piece of tourist tat.
Oh, so you won't mind it
if I throw it in the street?
No, no.
No!
(LAUGHS)
What is it?
There is a barcode on it.
It opens another
safety box
with money, passports,
emergency toiletries.
Are you okay?
No.
Okay, okay,
slow, slow.
(GROANS)
Slow, slow, slow...
I have a meeting
with Eve Polastri.
She's not here.
Can I take
a message?
I'll wait.
Huh.
Would you like a drink?
So much death.
That one...
That wasn't me.
I swear.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
It's her.
Who?
Her.
(GASPS)
BEAR: Oh, my God,
it is her.
She's directly
in front of us.
And she likes Tangfastics
She is amazing.
What do you think
she does with
all the penises...
(SHUSHES)
(JAMIE CLEARS THROAT)
(BEAR TAKES DEEP BREATH)
Yes?
(MOBILE RINGING)
Excuse me.
Okay.
This better not be
you calling to tell me
you're dead.
KONSTANTIN:
Will you please
tell your friend
to give me what's mine?
VILLANELLE: (OVER PHONE)
You're with Eve?
Eve, I'm at your work.
Everyone here
is really strange.
KONSTANTIN: (OVER PHONE)
What the hell are you doing
getting her involved?
I had no choice.
You were busy
having a heart attack.
Let me speak to her.
Tell her to
hand it over, now.
VILLANELLE: And let you leave
without me? No way.
I'm very sick.
I can't handle
this right now.
Then you better
leave it with her.
Meet us. Now.
She said for me to hang
onto it, didn't she?
Hmm.
The good ones...
I pickle.
The bad ones...
You don't want to know.
This has been great, guys!
(BEAR AND JAMIE GASP)
Really. Thanks
for the good time.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(ALL EXHALE WITH RELIEF)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(MUMBLES NERVOUSLY)
How do I drop a pin
on these things?
Here, let me...
(MOBILE RINGING)
Yes?
PAUL:
(OVER PHONE) I know.
What?
I know you're the one who's been
stealing money from the account.
KONSTANTIN: (OVER PHONE)
What do you want?
I want you at my house
in half an hour.
Change of plans.
I have to go.
Give me what's mine.
No.
I'm coming with you.
That's a very bad idea.
Tough.
You know your problem?
You don't know
what's good for you.
Says the man who just
had a heart attack.
Don't touch me!
Who was that?
Don't question me.
(DOOR OPENS)
KONSTANTIN: Don't say anything.
I do the talking.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Huh, now he's here,
we can start properly.
EVE: Carolyn?
CAROLYN: Eve, what are you
doing here?
I'm helping...
Villanelle.
Of course. I'm surprised
she's not with...
(DOOR BUZZER SOUNDING)
Shall I?
What have you told her?
PAUL: As I've explained
to you, Carolyn,
he only knows me
because I've been
working undercover.
And you believe that?
Sit down.
No, next to him.
Well...
This is something new.
Who's he?
Someone who's going to answer
a couple of questions.
Carolyn, things will go
a lot easier for you
if we just end this now.
Just sit down, Paul!
He's the one who's been
giving me orders.
Who is he?
KONSTANTIN: Whatever this is,
we can talk about it.
Do you even know
how to use that?
Please, give the gun to me.
(GUNSHOT)
Oh! Seems to be working.
You're going
to burn for this.
Both of you.
Shut up, Paul!
What is going on?
I have no idea.
What happened?
I'm fine.
CAROLYN: If you two
are going to be here,
the least you can do
is just sit down and be quiet.
KONSTANTIN: Carolyn,
you know I've been
working for The Twelve...
FSB, the British
Security Service.
That's can't be
a surprise for you.
PAUL: This is why
we've been investigating him.
He's betrayed everyone.
He's even been
stealing millions
from The Twelve.
Don't listen to him,
he is The Twelve.
(CHUCKLES)
He's The Twelve?
Yes.
Do you know Helene?
Helen who runs
the Treasury Desk?
No, Helene,
she's my boss... Ex-boss.
It was a very toxic work place.
Mmm.
Did you order Dasha Duzran
to kill my husband? Did you?
I don't know
any of the people
you are talking about.
Dasha is dead.
Dead?
Will you all be quiet?
Carolyn, what is
this about?
Justice.
Why did you kill my son?
What?
(GASPS)
Ha! That's ridiculous.
I saw the footage.
What footage?
On the day Kenny died,
you were there.
You were there?
I can explain.
Please do.
Because I'm very close
to pulling this trigger.
I'm waiting.
Tell her.
We were at the rooftop.
You killed Kenny?
VILLANELLE:
He doesn't kill people.
He makes other
people do it for him.
Why were you there?
Because of Paul.
What?
Kenny was getting
too close to The Twelve.
I told him,
if he wanted to live,
he needed to come
working for The Twelve.
I was trying to save him.
I promise.
PAUL: He's lying.
I was trying to save him,
I swear!
Yet, he died.
He got scared.
He kept stepping back.
I tried to stop him,
but he fell before
I could do anything.
I wish I could believe you.
You have to believe me.
The problem is,
Konstantin, I don't.
I wouldn't have...
CAROLYN: Wouldn't have?
Why wouldn't you?
I wouldn't do that
to someone I once...
Don't say "loved".
It's true.
Get down on your knees.
(SHUDDERS)
I loved you.
You never loved me.
Not even close.
Get down on
your knees!
Carolyn, think of what...
Why just...
Why just me?
Why not him
as well?
CAROLYN: Because I don't
care about him.
He doesn't mean
anything to me.
But I did care about you.
This was inevitable.
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
(VOICE TREMBLES)
Villanelle, do something!
Villanelle!
(GUNSHOT)
(GASPS) Oh, my God.
It should have been you.
Go before I change my mind.
Go!
(GULPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GASPING)
Are you coming?
No.
Why not?
You're not family.
Why kill him?
He had everything we wanted
to know about The Twelve.
He was a traitor.
Mo found the evidence
and Paul had him
killed for it.
He was a source.
It was Konstantin
who killed your son.
No, Eve.
I am responsible
for Kenny's death.
Look, it was not
your fault.
Kenny was killed trying
to expose The Twelve.
Isn't that what
we're all trying to do?
What I've come
to realise
is that one cannot
destroy The Twelve.
You should
listen to her, Eve.
CAROLYN: I know it.
She knows it.
Maybe it's time
you went cold turkey?
What do you mean?
(SCOFFS)
You know precisely
what I mean.
I like turkey.
Don't you want to just
trot along after her?
Hugh...
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION
OVER PHONE)
Yes, a suicide.
Five minutes.
VILLANELLE: Eve!
(PANTS)
(DISTANT SIREN WAILING)
Hey.
You can be pretty athletic
when you choose.
I killed Dasha.
No, I killed Dasha.
I hit her over the head
with a golf club.
I crushed her...
With my foot.
You did?
Uh-huh.
(EXHALES)
Then I guess
we both did.
(EXHALES)
Isn't that romantic?
You know, the only people
who would think that are?
Who?
Us.
I don't want
to do it any more.
Any of it.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
What's happened
to us?
I used to be
like them.
What?
Badly dressed?
You were
never like them.
You only thought
you were.
No.
I had a life.
I had a husband
and a house
and a chicken.
You still want that stuff?
When I try and think
of my future,
I just...
See your face over
and over again.
It's a very beautiful face.
Oh.
(CHUCKLES)
Did I ruin your life?
Do you think I'm a monster?
You're so many things.
(SCOFFS) Doesn't answer
my question.
I think we all have
monsters inside of us.
It's just that most people
manage to keep theirs hidden.
Well, I haven't.
No. (CHUCKLES)
Neither have I.
I think my monster
encourages your monster.
Right?
I think
I wanted it to.
(CHUCKLES)
Help me.
Help me make it stop.
So no more tea dances?
(CHUCKLES)
If that's really what you want,
it's not difficult.
You're going to
tell me to jump?
No! Of course not.
You'd die
if you jumped.
Nah.
It's easier than that.
If only that were true.
Stand up straight.
Stand up straight
and look at me.
(SIGHS)
Now turn around
and face the other way.
What?
I'll turn this way.
Have you turned?
I can't see you.
(EXHALES)
(DEEP SIGHS)
Now what?
Now we walk,
and we never look back.
But, I... I...
Don't turn.
Just walk.
♪ Tell me I'm your baby
♪ Be mine for always
♪ I'll be yours forever
♪ Tell me I'm your baby
♪ And you'll never leave me
♪ Tell me that you'll kiss me
♪ Forever ♪
(THEME MUSIC)