What's the deal with you and Villanelle?
I hate to be strict, but she
really mustn't kill anyone.
Eve would never forgive me
if I hurt you, Niko.
Kenny, I didn't know you'd be here!
This is a setup.
You're the person who made
this whole operation possible.
You should let yourself go.
That's what you leave behind.
It's finished.
I've got to go home.
I thought you were special.
Sorry to disappoint.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
... especially if that love,
introduces themselves,
by marching up to you in
the middle of the airport,
saying, "I'm going
wherever you are going."
This day, this speech,
and this toast...
is for us.
We love you!
If I'd have known getting married
would be this much fun,
I'd have done it loads more by now.
When I first met Maria...
I thought, "Great shoes."
But then I learned,
there's so much more to her than that.
She also has a great house,
and a pool and tailor.
Hairdresser.
It really is the all-around
excellent package.
When we met...
I'd just had a really bad breakup.
It was really bad.
But when I think about my ex today...
I realise...
I am so much happier now she's dead.
This is my special day.
Sincere... congratulations!
Stop it! Stop!
Apparently, I've lost their trust.
Was that something you
ever wanted to find?
Not quite. The problem being,
they've brought someone
in to oversee the desk.
Someone dreadful, I might add.
You're joking.
Diane doesn't joke.
She's too constricted.
And she specifically chose,
a Whitehall Warrior
in a rather successful
attempt to irritate me.
So we're basically being overseen
by a massive wanker.
- Precisely.
- What would you like?
Orecchiette please, Sam.
I mean, Diane's been waiting for years
to strike back at me,
and now's her chance.
She is a prime example of upper level
preventing the real
work from being done.
Bureaucracy in all its glory.
Parmigiano?
Carolyn?
Here we go.
I hear you've been very naughty.
Have I? How thrilling.
This is Mo Jafari.
A very promising young agent,
who I unearthed in Comms of all places.
Mo, Paul Bradwell.
Paul was once the rising star of MI6
until he defected to the other side.
I don't think the Foreign Office
can be considered the
other side, Carolyn.
Don't you?
I'm back now, with bells on.
So we can hear you coming?
Oh, we're always like this, aren't we?
Yes. Yes, we are.
Now listen, I understand
you're feeling a bit chippy,
but I honestly had no idea
they were going to ask
me to run the desk.
Oversee, Paul, not "run".
Oversee.
Whatever you say.
You know, I very nearly
called you over Christmas.
I was going through a terrible divorce
and I thought, if anybody knows
how to get through this, it's Carolyn.
She's done it enough times.
Divorces are easy.
It's marriages that are impossibly hard.
Are you joining us?
No, no, no. I have to dash.
Lunch with the chief.
We're going to make a fabulous team.
And, Carolyn,
I'm so sorry about the
whole office debacle.
They told me I had to take yours
as it was closer to the department.
Paul, I don't even know
where my office is.
Good luck with Diane.
I hear she's in a feisty mood.
Three clean-up operations, unauthorised.
The employment of former
MI5 agents, unauthorised.
Safe-housing an FSB agent...
Unauthorised.
Former agent, Hugo Turner,
who is currently, suing MI6
for injuries incurred during
your operation in Rome,
also unauthorised.
£416.27, unpaid lunches
at the canteen.
And that's to say nothing
of Polastri's fate.
Well, Carolyn, what on earth do
you have to say for yourself?
Hey, watch it!
Screw you.
We have been watching you since Rome.
You know that, don't you?
You're not easy to replace.
You should see some of the cretins
they send for me to train.
If you did ever want back in,
I can get you more of everything.
Money, travel, apartment.
All better than you've ever had.
You're so talented.
You're the best I ever trained.
- You're destined for greatness.
- "Destined for greatness."
It's true.
You have brilliant career
ahead of you, Oksana...
Do you think I'm stupid?
I'm still champion.
Best out of three.
Kopveska?
- I get them imported to...
- Yeah!
Hey, that is cheating.
So...
If I do ever want to come back,
and you give me all
this amazing stuff...
What's in it for you?
Hmm?
Knowing my most talented student
is doing work of her destiny.
Uh-uh.
I repeat...
What is in it for you?
If I get you back and working well...
they will send me home, to Russia.
Whatever you want, I will do it.
I will get you anything.
Just tell me.
Trust me.
Power is there for the taking, Oksana.
You just have to be smart about how.
Slowly, slowly, catch a monkey.
A Keeper.
I want to be a Keeper.
A Keeper is big.
Higher than Konstantin,
it's higher than me.
You said what I wanted,
that's what I want.
Ah-ha. Okay, okay.
We... We can work with this.
- Right?
- Yeah, we can work with this.
She wants to be Keeper.
"Oksana, the Keeper."
Oksana wants to be Keeper.
Oksana, the Keeper.
I will go to them tomorrow
and I will say she wants...
"Villanelle."
You call me Villanelle.
Okay. Okay. Villanelle.
- Are you all right?
- Ow!
No, I'm not.
Some bastard's been stealing
my Tangfastics again.
Better call in the troops.
Well, you joke, but theft
is theft, my friend.
Tangfastics today, data tomorrow.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Pop quiz tonight?
Erm, I can't this evening.
But we need you for all
the football questions.
I'm meeting someone.
A friend.
And I'm not the only one
who knows about football.
You have friends?
Ha.
You realise to fit in here,
you have to be socially inept
like the rest of us.
Oh, I'm that too. Don't worry.
So, who's the friend?
It's erm... It's nothing, really.
You know, a normal person
would flake on their friend
when something better turns up.
Well, remind me not to
rely on you for anything.
I liked your piece on evasive
jellyfish migration, by the way.
Thanks. I liked yours.
Oh, wait, you haven't
written anything, have you?
I'm working on it.
I don't care!
No, you promised us...
You said he doesn't push it
if it's not ready, right?
I said that about me.
Look, I could help you,
if you tell me what it's about.
I don't really know yet.
Okay, then.
Unbelievable!
I will find you.
I like the kitchen.
Okay.
I'll take this.
This is sweet.
- Are you visiting?
- Yes.
No. This is for my daughter.
She likes London, does she?
She hates everything about it.
That's why I'm sending it.
One and two,
and stretch your legs!
And finish!
Are you crying? Don't be a wimp.
When you really, really
want to piss her off,
you say, "Russia is a corrupt state,
clinging to the shadows
of its Soviet glory."
You see this woman?
She was useless just like you,
but I showed her how to be strong.
- And fight dirty.
- Yes.
Fight dirty, but listen to Dasha.
Now piss off.
And tomorrow, I want you on fire.
I scared the shit out of them.
Really?
They're open to it.
That doesn't sound like a yes.
They'll promote you with full benefits,
but first you have to show them
you're up to the job.
No. That's not what I asked for.
It's a process.
Nothing good comes fast. You know that.
- Slowly, slowly...
- Enough with the monkey!
A good solid job, nice,
political agitator...
and local, too.
Plus, big, fat, welcome-home bonus.
Have fun with it.
Your work was always
so inventive and fresh.
Almost as good as mine.
Better than yours.
- Hmm?
- Hmm.
You know they still study my kills,
for their brilliance?
My work remains totally untouchable...
Because it's out of date.
Do you want this job or not?
Shit.
First message.
Second message.
Dad, you need to come home now.
Mum's driving me crazy
and her sack of shit boyfriend is...
Delivery?
... a total dick.
And I need you to come back and get me.
Why are you still in that damp
dump of a country anyway?
You said you'd be back in a few weeks,
but it's been...
What the hell are you doing here?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry. You texted me.
- No, I didn't.
- Yes, you did.
It didn't make a lot of sense.
Something about "loo paper, beer"?
Oh. Oh, God.
I was a bit worried if I'm honest,
so I tracked your phone.
You know, you really shouldn't
leave your front door open,
considering the amount of people
that have tried to kill you.
Okay, I'm just gonna say it.
I'm really, really sorry
- about what went down.
- No, no, no.
- Let me say it.
- It's really best if you didn't.
- I prefer things...
- Buried.
Exactly.
Well, that's very... British.
- Cheers.
I went to see you,
after they transported you
- from the hospital in Rome.
- Really?
But they weren't allowing visitors
and I felt a bit, erm...
Lucky those tourists
found you when they did.
You missing MI6?
Absolutely not.
- How is it?
- I have no idea. I quit.
I've started working at Bitter Pill.
You're a journalist?
"Open-source investigator"
is the official title.
No way.
It's been decent, to be fair.
The site's good
and they let me investigate what I want.
The guy who runs it is pretty cool.
Working for someone
with integrity, it's...
Better than working for your mom.
Let's just say, different.
- You still in touch with...
- Oh, God. No.
I'm totally done with her.
Done with that.
End of story.
I was gonna say Niko.
Oh. Right.
Of course, I...
Yeah, we see each other
every few days. He's...
- You know.
- Yeah, I heard.
And what about you?
Do you ever worry about The Twelve?
There are plenty of other
people worrying about them.
But there's not.
MI6 shut everything down months ago.
Yeah, well, it's not my problem anymore.
- Yeah. Yeah, not our problem.
- Kenny, it's not.
- So I've been looking into them loads.
- No shit.
And I was looking at the
financial trial again.
And the thing is, after Fat Panda
- and Frank, there were...
- Kenny...
I've seen some activity in
their accounts that show...
Kenny, I'm serious. I am not
going down that road again.
It almost killed me.
You should come to the office
after work for beers.
I'm there most evenings and weekends.
I think you could do with
people, or something.
- You don't seem very, er...
- No, Kenny, I'm fine.
I know.
You just don't seem
very happy. That's all.
Who says I want to be happy?
- Bye.
Ahhh!
Untouchable.
♪ ... one another... ♪
♪ And between us ♪
♪ We have one... ♪
Kenny!
I thought you said you were going
to sort all this before we packed.
I did.
Memories.
You see this, and you're transported
- to a time of happiness?
- Yes.
I'll sort it when I'm back.
Now, you are the one who
persuaded me to make this move,
so you can just pitch in.
The thing is, I've got
some work stuff to do.
That website has you
working at the weekend?
You had me working at the weekend.
That's because people get
murdered at the weekend.
- I'll see you when I'm back.
- As you wish.
It is as I wish, actually.
- Right.
- That's why I'm not staying.
- I think I got that.
- All right, then.
Because I'm not gonna be
told what to do any more.
Clearly.
Are you ever going to apologise?
I think I'm at a loss here.
You really don't think you did
anything wrong at all, do you?
Your father chose our last house
and to be honest, I never liked it.
But I lived there for
years without complaint
because I knew it made him happy.
Life is just a series
of trade-offs, Kenny.
For all of us.
And my job is no different.
Now, you might disagree
with my decisions,
but I will never be able
to apologise for them.
And I'd have thought that if
anyone could understand that,
it's you.
Now, do you want fish and
chips for when you come back?
Okay.
- Battered sausage?
- Yes, please.
Right.
And it's not a website.
It's an online publication.
Oh, very good!
How are you feeling today?
- He's in the garden.
- Thank you.
I brought you these.
I ate the green ones for you.
Thanks.
They exchanged on the house.
I've got some stuff for you to sign.
- Just here.
- I know. Eve...
I'm not an idiot.
We are going to get through this.
You have to know that.
It's one day at a time,
and you are getting
better with every day...
This isn't something you can fix, Eve.
Her parents think she killed
herself, you know that?
Also, MI bloody six can
wash their hands...
It's better if her family don't know.
Better for who?
Our entire relationship has had you...
- at the centre of it.
- Well, I never wanted that...
Well, you didn't do much
to change it, did you?
And if we're being honest,
we'd both admit that I deserve more...
a bit more than that.
And more than you.
She's lying. Okay?
She was lying when she
had work the next day.
She was lying when saw her mom.
She was lying when she had the flu.
He knows it.
I know it.
You know it.
You're not even crying because of her.
You're crying because...
because you feel stupid.
Because you were stupid.
Hey.
Hey, these drinks don't involve games,
or organised fun, do they?
Erm, it's pretty chill.
Chilled works.
Okay, I'll get the...
Hello?
Kenny?
Hi. This is Kenny. Leave a message.
Hey. Erm, I'm here.
Oh, I think I have your phone.
Where are you?
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --