♪ Sha la, la, la, la, la
How's he doing?
You're awake.
Every time I visit,
he's asleep.
I wonder why.
Did the doctors come by?
They did.
And?
And he getting better.
But he must avoid all stress.
You're stress.
Coming from you, Maciek,
that's pretty rich.
The first time I meet you,
I tell him,
"Don't marry her.
"She will be
great big ball-ache."
"She will make your life
a total nightmare."
It's so good to see your eyes.
I am gonna find out
why this happened to you.
And I promise you...
♪ Just as they said ♪
♪ For two...
Welcome.
Let's sit over there,
shall we?
It's more comfortable.
I've wanted to meet
you for a long time.
I've been watching you.
Er, watching in a kinky way?
You're remarkable.
Are you trying to seduce me?
Excuse me.
What is your name?
Helene.
Is that your real name?
Do you know why I wanted
to meet you in person?
To watch me some more?
I wanted to
tell you face to face
that your request
has been successful.
It's official.
To Villanelle, the Keeper.
Your first assignment in
your new role is very exciting.
A big job that will
cause a great stir.
A politician in Romania.
I was told I would be
giving orders.
By who?
This is the same stuff
I was doing before.
This is bullshit.
You bargained
for what you wanted,
and we're giving it to you.
You'll get all the material
perks you were expecting.
What more do you want?
Enjoy Romania.
So, if the texts
weren't from Niko...
Villanelle must have sent them.
Making Eve
go to Poland to see...
Her husband being pitchforked.
Sorry.
Which means Villanelle is...
Stark raving mad.
This can't be about the bus.
What bus?
What did you do on the bus?
She knows she can't touch him.
What's she saying here?
Er, she's saying
she's "still got it."
Actually, if she
still did have it,
he'd be dead
and not just pitchforked.
Sorry.
Maybe she's trying
to torture you.
Not like this.
Am I being too harsh?
Wait, what's this?
Bertha Kruger.
The wife of Charles,
the, er, accountant
for The Twelve.
Killed in Lyon.
When? BEAR: Last week,
when you were gone.
Are you okay?
I just want a muffin.
No one usually gets those.
Ugh. Yeah.
Jan, 2011.
Here.
You know that it would be okay
if you're not okay.
That is...
I mean, aside from
Kenny dying which,
let's face it,
is a bit of a blow.
And being lured to Poland
because you thought your
husband wanted you back,
when really it was just
to see him being punctured.
You're alone,
homeless,
and trying to figure out
who's killed all your friends.
I mean,
I'd be a total wreck.
Why won't you give me a break?
Sometimes you just
need to let it win.
Hmm.
I wanted to show you this.
Dasha Duzran.
That's who's responsible
for the '70s gymnast kill.
At least, that's what
all the rumors say.
Who is she?
An Olympic gymnast,
who supposedly
works for the KGB.
They say it was The Chalk Kill
that got her recruited.
Why would
Villanelle imitate her?
Flattery and all that.
Hardly.
Where is this?
Oh, that's in Barcelona.
Yeah. She teaches
wee kids to do roly-polies.
Wha-what?
Eve.
Tell me everything
about Dasha Duzran.
I'm afraid you've
interrupted a rather delicate operation.
Drought can be endured,
but rot is an instant killer.
Dasha.
Oh, yes.
Well, I first met her
when she had just been
kicked out of the KGB.
Sorrento.
And the weather was
unusually hot for that time of year,
and I waited for her at a cafe.
And before she sat down,
she plucked a lemon from a tree,
and took the most
enormous bite out of it,
rind and all.
Why do you want to know?
I think she's running
Villanelle out of Barcelona.
Well, that is
a heady combination.
Villanelle and Dasha.
Volatile.
If I'm right,
Dasha knows where
Villanelle was last week.
Because, I don't think she
was the one who attacked Niko.
Interesting.
I think she was
in Lyon at the time,
killing Bertha Kruger.
I hope that doesn't mean you're
thinking of going to Barcelona.
Someone tried
to kill my husband,
I intend to find out who.
But if it's The Twelve, Eve...
Does it really matter who?
I could say
the same about Kenny.
Just be very careful of Dasha.
She was the KGB's top assassin,
until she killed
one of their own.
I mean,
that's why she was exiled.
Irina!
What are you doing?
I love
hockey! Irina's good.
That was the other team.
It is? Yes.
Oh. Go, other team!
Villanelle.
Do they sell hot dogs here?
You can't watch sports
without a hot dog.
Villanelle!
What is going on?
I'm coming with you.
Your plan to get out?
I'm in.
You're in?
It's exciting, huh?
How was your trip?
Er, turns out I'm excellent
at dung-throwing.
And your mother?
No, Villanelle.
She deserved it.
Of course,
she deserved it.
Everyone's mother deserves it.
But you're not
supposed to do it.
You are supposed to grow up
and realize she isn't actually
evil. I don't want to talk about it.
I don't want
to talk about it! She's just insane.
Where are we going?
It better be some place hot.
No, it's too late.
You haven't even left.
It's too dangerous
for us all to go together.
Konstantin, please.
I send for you.
Er, no.
No.
We can't go together.
They will be on to us
before we get there.
Get where?
You will know
when I send for you.
Hmm, we'll go.
Then, you can send for Irina.
I can't do that.
Once we're safe,
you'll come. I promise.
I don't believe you.
But that's the only
way we'll make it.
You haven't told anyone
about this, have you?
Of course not.
Don't let them see you
even think about getting out.
Do you hear me?
They'd kill you the
second they realize...
Oh, Irina.
Because of her.
I just scored
in the final minute,
and you missed it.
That was good.
He's a really shit father.
You should run away.
What is she doing here?
Er, I'm planning
our travel arrangements.
Please tell me you're joking.
She is joking.
I'm not going if she's with us.
Great!
Problem solved.
When do we leave?
Irina, you go and get changed.
We'll talk about this later.
Go.
I don't
think you really want this.
I want it!
You know what it means?
It means you have
to leave everything,
the clothes,
apartment... and her.
I know.
Don't let them see
something's up.
Promise me.
The plan only works
if nobody knows there is one.
I'll act totally normal.
Then they'd definitely
know something's up.
Are you coming
to poker this week?
What day is it?
Wednesday.
This Wednesday.
I'm afraid I don't think I can.
That's a shame.
Shirley's making her risotto.
Mushroom?
Naturally.
Well, let me see what I can do.
Right. To the matter
at hand.
Phone records.
Calls to and from
Kenny's work phone
the two days before he...
Died.
Was he working for you
around this time?
No.
He'd left the service by then.
It's just...
There were several
incoming and outgoing calls
to a Russian number.
Anyway, I'll leave you
to go over it all.
Give me a shout if
you have any questions.
Thanks, Mike.
I emailed this to your desk
over a week ago,
you know.
Really?
That's why I suggested this
when you asked where they were.
Didn't want them to get lost.
Let me know about Wednesday.
You have to let us win it
back sometime, you know.
Ah! Hello, Carolyn.
Time for P.E.?
Indeed.
Do you think you could manage
to get those
phone records to me?
They're taking a very long time.
Hmm. I, er, had a call
about those just this morning.
Scotland Yard dragging
their feet, as per.
Shouldn't be too much longer.
What?
Are you...
working for them, Paul?
Excuse me?
Are you?
Are you, Carolyn?
Why on Earth
would you ask me that?
Well, the same reason
you asked me.
Because we don't
trust each other.
Should I...
trust you?
Heavens, no.
None of us are to be trusted,
that's why we work here.
Quite.
Well, I'd best be off,
I have an appointment.
Right.
Carolyn.
This is your office.
Oh.
That's very good light.
Was that your boyfriend?
My mum's boyfriend.
Is he a pervert?
No. He's just...
really, really... nice.
You want to bunk off?
Do you think I'm dumb?
I'm not going anywhere with you.
Come on!
It'll be fun.
We can do anything you want.
Anything.
You'll need me
to help you translate.
I remember your languages
were...
Piss off!
I'm fluent in Spanish.
Ooh, Spanish.
I know what you're trying to do.
You're not coming with us.
I bet you
get homesick in a week.
No, I won't.
The heat will be awful.
You'll have to wax all the time.
You're so old.
People don't just wax any more.
I don't want to look
like a 12-year-old girl.
You are a 12-year-old girl.
I'm 14!
Where is your Dad?
London.
So, you're stuck with your mum?
Don't remind me.
Mums are the worst, right?
You know how annoying it is
when you have to be
around two people in love?
Ugh.
Well, imagine one of
those people is your mum.
It's disgusting.
He's disgusting.
If it's that bad,
kill him.
You're a
real role model, you know that?
Oh, my
God! You're really bad.
The humidity in South America
will not be kind to that hair.
Cuba's in
North America, you idiot!
Cuba!
You are totally delusional.
Shall we go for a drive?
Mmm.
This is nice.
Is it?
How are you?
Galvanized.
I can see that.
Are you in a rush?
Not rushed,
just impatient.
Are we going
somewhere in particular?
Yes.
Are you going to tell me where?
No.
What are you doing?
Give me your wallet. Why?
Just give me your wallet.
What the hell are you doing?
What did you want with my child?
I'm going to
ask you again, Konstantin,
and you're going
to answer me correctly.
What did you want with my child?
I swear, I try nothing.
She kissed me.
Geri kissed you.
You don't have to do this.
I already know you are scary.
Why did Kenny call you
the night before he died?
Konstantin?
Okay, okay.
He called me.
What did you get him into?
Nothing.
If you don't tell me...
I don't know what
this is, or what you're...
Tell me.
He ask if I was his father.
Hey.
What did you tell him?
I told...
I told him I didn't know.
Get out.
You're cooking.
I thought we were
having veg stew tonight.
I really just felt
like a pork pie,
if I'm honest.
I went shopping specifically.
They're wonky.
The ones that no one wanted.
Geri, are you comparing
yourself to a carrot?
I know you don't
like me very much... Geri.
And now you have to
put up with me because
you and I are all that's left
of this family, and...
I don't love being here either,
having you treat me
like I'm some kind of
idiotic annoyance
whose intellectual power
could never match up to yours.
Could we do this after we've...
But I choose to stay because...
Because you're all I have, too.
And I thought that
maybe we'd learn to...
I don't know,
do more than just
tolerate each other.
It would be so much better
if we could have this
conversation after I've eaten.
All right.
You were your father's.
And Kenny was mine.
And that is how things
were when we were all alive.
He understood you and you him,
in a way I never did.
And I understood Kenny
and he me,
in a way your father never did.
So... No.
You're not easy
for me to understand.
And I know I'm
not supposed to say that.
But it's the truth.
There's no more
can be said about it.
Now, I can pretend
to enjoy wonky carrot stew
and listen to gong bells
and all the other inane
things that interest you,
but I don't,
because I can't lie,
do you see?
I know other parents do,
they tell their children they're
wonderful at this
and great at that,
but I just...
I don't have that gene.
So...
To you,
I am harsh and cold,
and to me you are
disappointed and expected.
Oh!
Ooh.
But you're right,
Geraldine.
All we've got left
is each other.
So, you make your stew and
I'll try and pretend to enjoy it.
And while I do,
you can tell me exactly
what's been going on
between you and Konstantin.
Where you've been,
what you've done,
and why he came to visit you.
Because it seems while
I've been unable to lie to you,
you've had no problem
lying to me.
Call me when it's done.
Where've you been?
Will people
stop waiting for me in the dark!
Bit late for an evening stroll.
I was
trying to get my step-count up.
Hmm. You know, it turns out
Kruger wasn't the man we were after.
No?
No.
It was someone else who
was dipping into the honey pot.
Then why make me stay here?
His wife, Bertha,
she's our focus now.
Because she was
stealing the funds?
No, because she's dead.
Whoever ordered that hit
is who we want.
Do you have any idea
who'd want that woman dead?
Why would I?
Does this mean
I can leave London?
It means the
job description's changed.
Find out who gave that order,
whatever it takes.
If there's a breach,
we're both to blame,
but believe me,
you will be the one who'll fall.
Up for a game?
You're up.
Total fluke.
So why you here?
You want to ask
about my gold medals?
Oh, I thought it was bronze.
Do you know who I am?
I know you're working
for The Twelve.
I know you're working with her.
Your turn.
You bowl a lot?
Never.
I noticed the way Villanelle
copied your first kill.
Very original.
She must really admire you.
Though, whoever
tried to imitate her
did a really poor job.
My husband's still alive.
You don't talk to people
when they are bowling.
That was a strike.
Did they send her to kill Kenny?
My God,
is this what
she has to deal with?
Where is she?
Just because you
don't want it to be her,
doesn't mean it wasn't.
It wasn't.
Do you know she's been promoted?
She will never be loyal to you.
And she's loyal to you?
Aye, she respects me.
Really?
I created her.
I took raw shit and
moulded it into steel.
I broke her back,
I gave her wings.
She's perfect killing machine.
That's all she's there for.
That's all she knows.
I don't think so.
Oh, you think she cares
what you think?
She's moving up in the world.
You'll never touch her now.
You think you are winning.
You will never win at this game.
You can't beat us.
You understand?
I can kill you...
any time.
End of game.
She's off sick today.
Hmm.
Don't worry.
I'm going to make you
look amazing.
Irina, school's out
early this year.
Be ready.
What the hell have you done?
I'm done with this shit.
I'm done with it.
I'm leaving.
What do you mean you're leaving?
Oh, I've got to get out of here.
How was your meeting
with Helene?
That's not her real name.
Look at you.
I'm a Keeper now.
You get to go home.
You think I get to go home
after this disaster?
Here, give it to me,
give it to me.
You can...
You can pinch it
with this, go on.
Yeah, grab it.
Pinch it.
Good.
Come on.
So, what happened?
I don't want
to do this any more.
Come on.
Just clean yourself up,
and I'll order pizza.
Hmm? Okay.
♪ There was a girl There was a girl ♪
♪ Who loved a boy Who loved a boy ♪
♪ Remember him Remember him ♪
♪ Remember us Remember us ♪
♪ Turn the time ♪
♪ They cried ♪
♪ So they fell So they fell ♪
♪ Out of love Out of love ♪
♪ Into the plane Into the plane ♪
♪ Of the sea Of the sea ♪
♪ Where I'm with you...
Where I'm with you... ♪
♪ Together for
♪ Eternity