_
Oh...
Bastard!
You need to go electric.
Great advice. Thanks.
I saw you talking to yourself earlier.
Excuse me?
And you drink a lot.
Okay, this might have
worked for you before,
but just so you know, it's failing.
And for your information, I'm not drunk.
You will be by the end of the night.
It's pull, by the way.
No judgement on my part.
I'm just making an observation.
Well, go observe somewhere else.
Oh-ho-ho.
Wow! Are you always this defensive?
Are you always this much of a dick?
I... I'm not... I'm not drunk.
He's just very...
... very annoying.
_
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
Vodka. Straight.
And make it double.
Not because I'm Russian.
Because it works.
Kenny would be so touched.
What do you want?
Gin.
Gin, please.
I hear you are a walking miracle.
- Oh, hallelujah!
- Ha!
You know, when a bullet
has been through you,
it leaves something behind.
Poor Kenny.
Oh, he'd hate this.
He chose it.
How do you know what he chose?
Jumping off a building
- is a very clear choice.
- Oh, bullshit. Don't say...
Why is everyone saying he jumped?!
Just be quiet.
You must think of the family.
Please, don't pretend... for one second,
that you ever think of
anyone but yourself.
- Oh...
- I'm sorry, I'm so sorry.
Oh, you...
- Having a good night?
- Yeah, well, you know what?
You've really got this whole, um,
smug face thing down, don't you?
It's just my face.
Tune!
Yeah, he'd... he'd always play this
when he won the office table tennis.
Which wasn't very often, was it?
Excuse me? I'm sorry.
Um... did you... did you work
with Kenny at Bitter Pill?
Uh, yeah... yeah, that's right.
- How was he? I was...
- Jamie Hayward,
founder, editor of Bitter Pill.
Now, if you have any queries
about Kenny's work...
- No, I...
- ... you can come to me.
I have no queries.
Excuse me.
Hmm.
Can you make sure everyone's
topped up, please?
♪ Giving back the time... ♪
Oh.
- The crisps are a safe bet.
- ♪ Stilling my desire ♪
You'd think it was one
of her bloody dinners.
She does have very good dinners.
♪ The snow's come back ♪
What?
Do I have crisps in my beard?
It's you.
It's you!
It was one of Mum's dinners.
I was about eight, nine,
and I'd had a nightmare and you
found me crying on the stairs.
Hmm!
You told me you were
there as monster watch,
to make sure that nothing scary
would come into the house.
And... then you taught me
how to swear in Russian.
- I did?
- Mudak.
- I did.
- Yeah.
You haven't changed a bit.
You have!
Geraldine, can you ask them
to change that music?
It's terribly dreary.
Today isn't about pretending
we're not sad, Mum.
It's about acknowledging
the sadness together.
Couldn't we be sad and
listen to good music?
- She staying long with you?
- No idea.
Apparently, she wants to help me grieve.
Do you need help?
Absolutely not.
Just excuse me.
Um, Eve...
I'm sorry for your loss.
I left you several messages.
Oh...
Eve, it's push, by the way. Can we talk?
Do you think he jumped?
Yes.
Hmm!
- Eve, I need you to...
- No.
- But, Eve, Eve...
- I said no! Do you hear me?
No! No!
No!
Bloody hell.
Just... didn't like the buffet.
Hmm.
You ask Dasha for the best,
Dasha gets you the best.
You're welcome.
Everything you asked for.
Good light, high ceilings.
Chan, did you check the water pressure?
- Excellent.
- That was hard to get.
You know if you quit smoking,
you'd look, like, 10 years younger.
Why would I want to
look 10 years younger?
This neighbourhood is nice.
You like what you see?
It's good to have many lovers.
It keeps you limber.
But you have to know, we are
different from these people.
Things they take for granted:
package holidays, car in drive,
date nights on sofa.
We can't have these things.
Winners win alone.
You can't go down that path anymore.
I dealt with it.
Ah. Hmm.
So, you don't think about her anymore?
- I dealt with it!
- Mm-hm.
Okay.
So, the job went well, they're happy,
they're very happy with you.
And I appreciated the homage to Dasha.
I improved an untouchable relic.
- Original's always best.
- Come on!
The paprika was kind of fun.
- I'd have gone turmeric, but...
- So, what do they do now?
Do they send me a letter
of promotion or something?
They want you to work
with somebody first.
What are you talking about?
You have to show them
that you're up to the job.
He's a new recruit.
You will be overseeing him.
You will be giving him orders.
If you want more control,
you have to show them
you have some judgement.
I know.
Carolyn? Carolyn...
Your blouse is, uh...
I like it like that.
Morning!
So...
Shall we just dive right in?
Maybe we should start with
the report on Agent...
Carolyn! We weren't... expecting...
Well, we certainly weren't
expecting you... so soon.
Why ever not?
Well...
How bloody gallant of you.
- Mina?
- Roger...
- Your FSB intelligence...
- Your Volgograd asset...
- Are we looking at a honey trap...
- Regarding the Daesh Takfiri terror cell,
are we talking about fully formed...
- What travel arrangements... ?
- ... high-level targets... ?
Let's all just...
... take five.
It's too soon.
For what?
You're... on leave.
Surely, that's my decision.
I know returning to work
is a welcome distraction.
I don't believe in distractions.
I'm fully capable of doing my job,
without any approval from you.
I know you think I'm
a self-serving prick.
And... well, maybe I am.
But, Carolyn, your son has just died.
Some things are bigger than
the job, and this is one of them.
You have to start taking
care of yourself right now.
Or it's going to catch up with you.
- Your name?
- Jeffrey.
Can you give me the
status of the situation?
Why are you never the same person?
We work on rota.
It's like seeing a new
doctor every time.
I have to explain everything
from the beginning.
Can you please look in
your notes or something?
Do you have my airline tickets?
They want you to stay
in London a bit longer.
Is that really necessary?
They need you to keep an eye on things.
That old MI6 friend of yours.
- How long do I have to stay?
- No idea.
That's very useful. Thank you.
Treat it as a working holiday.
Holiday, you need sunshine.
- _
- Mm.
_
Thirsty work, I imagine.
I worked on a farm.
My father arranged...
Both you and I know perfectly
well that... Kenny...
... didn't take his own life.
Yes.
But I have to be...
... discreet.
I can't... let people know
I'm looking into things.
You were potentially the last
person to speak to him properly
and it's imperative we talk.
Carolyn, I would do anything
for Kenny to be alive
and I am sorry you are
going through this, I am.
But I don't work for you anymore.
Not after what you did in Rome.
I have something that I
think may interest you.
An agitator in Catalonia,
killed in her own shop.
No-one's claimed it.
She hasn't been active for months.
Not since Rome.
We actually thought she was dead.
She's back, Eve.
And she's working.
I can't help you.
I thought you'd want to know.
So, who am I working with on this thing?
Felix Telep.
They say he has real potential.
And I just watch him
and give him a grade?
A: for excellent killing.
B: could do better.
- That kind of thing?
- You don't grade him.
You guide him.
Make sure his plan is clean,
his character work is strong.
You know, just like I
used to do with you.
- What if he's totally useless?
- Then encourage him.
You tell him he's great.
You tell him you know he can do it.
You make him believe he can be good.
Why can't I just do the
work and he watch?
- So much easier.
- Management is not easy.
It's watching someone
do job worse than you.
That's why it sucks.
But to be Keeper, that takes
patience and responsibility.
You need both.
I don't have both. I have neither.
Then pretend that you have!
Come on, look around you, Villanelle.
They don't give places
like this to anybody.
Money, rewards, lifestyle,
it all gets better and better,
the more you succeed.
I believe in you.
So, it's that kind of thing.
Exactly.
Hmm.
_
Hello? Eve?
Eve, if this is you, don't speak.
You've stolen a dead man's phone
with highly sensitive information,
a phone we're tracking right now.
We both know you've got the phone,
with no way for you to unlock it.
So, why don't you just stop dicking
around with this elusive crap?
Just bring it in and we can...
_
How did you know I had the phone?
Oh, that was bollocks.
We just guessed it was you.
What?!
Well, the police didn't
find Kenny's work phone.
You were the last person here.
It's pretty straightforward.
She's here.
Just give the phone to Bear.
I'm not giving it to anyone.
The phone stays with me.
Why'd you nick it?
I didn't nick anything. I just...
forgot to mention I found it.
What was Kenny working
on before he died?
You tell me.
- I asked you.
- Why did you hire him?
MI6. Whiz online.
Integrity.
He was a triple threat.
You didn't want him to look
into anything specific?
I don't tell people what to investigate.
They work on what's important to them.
And Kenny didn't say
what is important to him?
What's important to you?
See, this isn't about me.
See, that's where I think you're wrong.
If it wasn't about you,
you wouldn't have the phone.
Look, two options here.
Either you keep it,
with no way of cracking into it,
and Kenny's death grows
colder by the hour,
or you hand it over and we get going.
I want the files he was working on.
There's no way I'm handing
over classified information
without seeing that phone.
Yeah, well, this phone isn't
free, so where's his laptop?
Every device is clean.
We don't store in the cloud.
We work off encrypted thumb drives.
Fine!
As soon as we crack that phone.
Fine.
Le France.
_
I'm Felix.
What are you?
- 10?
- I'm 19.
I'm tough.
- I have five older brothers.
- Wow!
- Five big brothers?
- Yeah.
And I beat the crap out of all of them.
Take off your hat.
Anybody can fight.
It takes a special person to kill.
I've killed, loads of times.
- Bullshit!
- There was this kid
that bullied me in school.
- Textbook. Basic.
- His sister.
- His father.
- I'm falling asleep here.
His cousin. Best friend, uncle,
dance teacher and grandma.
They were in the same car.
Just so you know, I'm kind of
a big deal in this industry.
- Okay.
- You do everything I say,
- exactly when I say it.
- Okay.
If you make me look
bad, I will kill you.
- O... Okay.
- Okay.
Great talk. Good skills.
Excellent work.
The travel is what I'm
most excited about.
I love hotels.
Well, make sure you ask for first-class.
None of this "submit
receipts after" bullshit.
They should pay up-front.
Okay.
That kid bullied you bad, huh?
He beat up my boyfriend.
You did all that for a boyfriend?!
Well, I was in love.
After everything I did,
he didn't want to know.
When you love somebody and
they don't love you back,
it's... it's worse than...
I don't know what it's worse than,
- but it's really...
- Shit.
Yeah.
Shit.
- Sorry...
- Oh, it's okay.
Oh, hi.
Ah, it's you!
- Good to see you again!
- You too.
I'm sorry I didn't get to say
goodbye after the funeral.
Ah, that's okay.
There was just so much going
on, and I'm hyper-empathic,
so I get over-burdened with
other people's emotions,
which can be... a lot
to process, you know?
Staying in England long?
Undecided.
I have some work I need to finish.
I was just sending this
to my daughter in Russia.
Oh, that's adorable.
I used to collect those
when I was a kid.
Ah.
She's too old for them, really.
Mum used to bring me and Kenny
small bottles of booze.
She says you only know a country
once you know its drink.
You should have this.
Oh, your daughter...
Oh, she wouldn't even notice.
Please.
Thank you.
Oh, no...
I didn't want to upset you.
You haven't. It's just...
Moments of kindness
mean a lot right now.
Bonjour !
Papa! Papa! Papa!
No manners.
That's the target.
_
Merci.
There he goes.
Stick to the plan.
- Okay.
- Behind the ear.
- Clean and clinical.
- Okay.
Okay, go. Now!
What happened to the plan?
I improvised.
Oh?
Oh, management sucks.
This is everything
I could find right now.
The rest is gonna take more time.
Audrey.
- Who's Audrey?
- That's Audrey.
Did you know?
Yeah. He had started wearing deodorant.
It's good to know he was
getting some before he died.
What?!
It's good to know.
Uh, what else is on there?
The rest is gonna take a while.
He... he knew what he was doing.
- Well, how long is a while?
- A few days.
Okay. Well, then, uh,
give me his thumb drive.
The police have it.
Are you serious?!
- It was in his pocket.
- Oh!
Bastard.
Yeah. No, you're right.
This is never gonna be
solved without you, right?
Maybe we're just clinging to the idea
that something happened to him
because... we're too
afraid of the truth.
That he was just an unhappy kid,
and topped himself.
That's what you really
believe, isn't it?
Or why else would you be walking away?
Audrey?
Uh...
- Oh, hi...
- Hi.
I'm very glad you recognised
me from the, um...
Well, we met at the funeral, didn't we?
- Mm. Yeah.
- Mm.
Um, what I'm keen to
ascertain is... is whether...
What I mean to say is, do you
think that, uh, Kenny, was happy?
Do you think?
He used to sing to himself
when he was on the loo.
S Club 7, mostly.
- And he liked the job?
- Loved it.
He missed you, though.
He said nobody kicked
his arse like you did.
I could be hard on him.
My mum told me I was
brilliant at everything,
even when I wasn't.
I spent four years
trying to be an artist
without any actual talent.
Being hard on someone is
sometimes what they need.
The ancient Celts used to
mourn their loved ones
with wailing and shrieking.
It was just a public ritual for them.
They weren't embarrassed
about it in the least.
Don't be embarrassed, will you?
There you are!
I said...
Can I get in?
Can I turn this... ?
Okay.
Are you coming in to work?
There's no point.
Why?
There's no point coming in because
I'm not allowed to do my work.
And there's no point in going
home because my daughter...
... is taking over the house, wanting...
... to talk.
Well, you can't just sit here.
I can.
I've got my sandwiches. I'm fine.
What a way to go.
Sorry?
What a terrible death.
Dido...
... abandoned by Aeneas...
... dies of grief.
Oh, right.
I can't...
... solve it, Mo.
I can't investigate it.
My hands are tied.
It's my son...
... and I can't... solve it.
I need to speak with Carolyn.
I'm not sure she's really up for...
Mum?
It's all right.
Geraldine, why don't you go and
do your thing, where you...
... close your eyes and breathe?
Do you mean sleep?
Go ahead.
Eve, if you have come here to
berate me about the other day,
do you mind if we do it in the morning?
- I'm a little tired.
- I have Kenny's phone.
I see.
I need to know what
happened, who killed him.
Well...
... as you know...
... in the field, when someone dies,
they can... fuel you, in a good way.
But this is different.
Do you understand?
I understand.
All right.
I miss his smell.
Carolyn...
What do you want from me?
There's a thumb drive he was working on.
The police have it.
We need to get a hold of it.
We need to crack into it.
We'll keep it confidential.
_
Nice place.
No...
- Oh, yes.
- No.
- No?!
- Really?!
- Aah!
Oh! Oh! No! Stop!
You do not get to come here
without an invitation anymore!
Fine!
Fine.
Can I please come to see you?
Aagh!
I'll think about it.
Ohh...
Oh!
Oh, God...
Oh, I missed you.
- Hmm.
- You look good.
Haven't you heard?
I'm moving up in the world.
Really?
They're making me a Keeper.
- Who told you that?
- Dasha.
- Dasha?
- Mm.
You trust Dasha after
what she did to you?
I trust her more than I trust you.
You always said you
were going to kill her.
If I killed everybody who betrayed me,
there would be nobody left.
You know I had no choice in Rome.
Ah, I hope your family was worth it.
That's up for debate.
Look...
... now you're back with
The Twelve, especially now,
you have to know,
- you're not safe.
- I'm fine.
You think you're in control,
but you are not.
And you think I'm going to listen to you
- after everything that you did?
- Okay, fine.
There's something else.
Eve...
... she is alive.
It's not possible.
I saw her with my own eyes.
I shot her.
When you get angry and run away
without checking if the
person is actually dead...
... miracles happen.
But don't go to London.
I don't want anything to happen to you.
Villanelle?
Villanelle...
I'm fine.
Really, I'm fine. You should go.
How do you know I'm
back with The Twelve?
'Cause I never stopped working for them.
You know I care about you.
I know you're full of shit.
Can't it be both?
Oh...
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --