Oksana Astankova, or as
she prefers to be called...
Villanelle.
- You call me Villanelle.
- Her mother was dead.
- Her father was a drunk.
- You choose your family over me?
KONSTANTIN: That's what
families are. It's what they do.
I wouldn't know. Mine are all dead.
Most of them, sure.
VILLANELLE: What do you
mean, "Most of them"?
What kind of baby do you think I was?
I've seen a photo of you.
You had a strange head. Unnatural.
I got what you ask for. Your family.
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[HONKING CONTINUES]
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
[BELL CLANGS]
[DOG BARKS]
[SIGHS]
[COWS MOO]
[VEHICLE PULLS UP]
[MAN ON TV SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
- [CROWD ON TV GASPS]
- [MAN ON TV CONTINUES IN RUSSIAN]
[CROWD CHEERS]
[LAUGHS]
Who are you?
Do you speak English?
Elton John is English.
Yeah.
He is.
- [LAUGHTER ON TV]
- [LAUGHS]
Do you live here?
This is a nice home.
Are you from Pinner?
- No.
- Watford?
No!
[SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
[SIGHS]
- Yula?
- Shh.
- [SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
- [MAN SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
Who's that?
- Fedya's girlfriend.
- Who's Fedya?
My brother. Half-brother.
Who are you?
- BOY: She speaks English.
- Yeah.
OLDER MAN:
Who are you?
Dad, you have to speak English.
Why you come all way
from England to Grizmet?
You have wrong house.
Does Pyotr live here?
[SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
[ENDS CALL]
Who the hell are you?
- Svoloch.
- Tvoyu mat...
You two are great together.
[OLDER MAN SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
That won't be necessary.
It necessary if you don't
want to say who you are.
Ask Pyotr.
[SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
OLDER MAN:
Oksana?
So, you know who she is?
Eta moya sestra.
Ya znayu.
[COW MOOS]
You look just like Grandma.
[PIANO BALLAD PLAYS]
[LAUGHS]
BOY: What do you think Elton
would eat when he's in Berlin?
Uh...
currywurst, with paprika.
- Istanbul?
- Uh, kebab.
- Go to Lezzet's. Ask for Ayaz.
- Vienna.
Great ice-cream in Vienna.
PYOTR:
OLDER MAN:
FEDYA:
PYOTR:
YULA:
Athens?
Taramasalata.
You've been to every
city Elton's played in!
[CAR HORN HONKS]
- Who's that?
- Mum.
I'm saving up for London
to see his farewell tour.
But I'm nowhere near 50,000 roubles.
['BUMBLE BEE' BY LAVERN BAKER PLAYS]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Where are you going?
- Oksana. Oksana. Oksana.
- [HYPERVENTILATES] Agh!
Oksana!
LAVERN BAKER: ♪ You've been
treating me like a clown ♪
♪ You know you've hurt
me once before... ♪
- Oksana, uspoykoysya.
- [HYPERVENTILATES]
♪ You'll never hurt me anymore ♪
♪ Shoo-ee... ♪
- Oksana?
- ♪ You hurt me like a bee ♪
♪ A bumble bee, a evil bumble bee... ♪
[SOBS]
[SOBS AND SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
[KISSES]
[SOBS]
[CONTINUES SOBBING]
They told me you died in fire.
The orphanage phone me and
say... you burn place down.
It was one floor.
Two at most.
- And many people die.
- 'Many' is a very loose term.
And you die with them.
This is what they tell us.
Sestra, I found it. Was at back of loft.
[SIGHS]
Why didn't you leave him?
Where?
All he did was cry.
I thought I'd come back
for you after one month.
[DOG BARKS]
[COWS MOO]
[SIGHS]
- Is that me?
- Mm.
[LAUGHS]
My head really was bulbous.
You were beautiful baby.
Everyone would stop me in street
and say, "She's beautiful baby."
Head was big, but beautiful.
MOTHER: Oh, yeah.
I used to like dressing up
and you always wanted my clothes,
so I would make costume
from old curtains for you.
Here.
I look ridiculous.
Oh. That's me.
[LAUGHS]
Where is Dad?
There has to be one
of him before he died.
I make tea.
You still like Kopveska?
Hmm? I bring for you.
She gets sad if anyone speak of Dad.
- [CROCKERY RATTLES]
- Oh!
Look, Oksana. You punching me in face.
[CUTLERY CLINKS]
[CROCKERY RATTLES]
That's a good punch.
[LIGHTER STRIKES]
You have all that innocent look.
Because I am innocent.
I believe her.
Bor'ka, speaking good English
doesn't make innocent.
I know a killer when I see
a killer, and she's a killer.
OLDER MAN: Are you
seriously accusing her?
Yes.
- Ooh!
- [OTHERS LAUGH]
I can't believe it!
BOR'KA: So, who killed me?
[LAUGHS]
- I told you. I was right.
- But who killed me?
Okay, okay. So, Oksana is not killer,
but we ask now who is.
YULA: Hmm.
Oh!
You? You?
- I got the card.
- Mum, you murdered me!
I had no choice, Bor'ka.
You could have murdered the others.
I knew it was her. I knew.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Nu ladna.
- I did. I did.
Why I'm so bad at this game?
Pyotr, you are too naive.
He means you're idiot.
You were wrong too.
He is, uh, like little puppy dog.
You know, he lives in the barn.
I like to sleep there some nights.
There's a hole in the
roof and I can see stars.
There is hole in roof and...
he can see stars.
- Screw you.
[BOTH SPEAK RUSSIAN]
Na.
FEDYA: Oh, yes, sit down,
mummy's boy, yeah.
- Is good...
- Fyodor!
Enough!
Izini, Papa.
Good.
I like to make speech.
This night is very, very special for me.
My girl...
... my little girl.
Welcome home, Oksana.
I've never actually lived here.
- Welcome home.
- Welcome.
I'll go along with it for
the sake of the moment.
[GLASSES CLINK]
- Ahh!
- Mmm!
[TAPS RHYTHMICALLY]
[PIANO INTRO TO 'CROCODILE
ROCK' BY ELTON JOHN PLAYS]
♪ I remember when rock was young ♪
♪ Me and Suzie had so much fun ♪
♪ Holding hands and skimming stones ♪
♪ Had an old gold Chevy
and a place of my own ♪
♪ But the biggest kick I ever got ♪
♪ Was doing a thing called
the Crocodile Rock ♪
♪ While the other kids were
rockin' round the clock ♪
♪ We were hoppin' and boppin'
to the Crocodile Rock, hey ♪
♪ Crocodile rockin' is
something shockin' ♪
♪ When your feet just can't keep still ♪
♪ I never knew me a better
time and I guess I never will ♪
♪ Oh, Lawdy, Mama ♪
- ♪ Those Friday nights... ♪
- Come on. Come on.
♪ When Suzie wore her dresses tight ♪
♪ And the Crocodile rockin'
was out of sight ♪
♪ Laa ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la la-la ♪
♪ Laa... ♪
[DONKEY BELL CLANGS]
[GROWLS ANGRILY]
Having fun?
This is my, uh, how you call this, uh...
- Anger problem.
- [PANTS]
Wow.
You saw this wood all day like that?
It's not so bad, uh...
- I used to do woodwork.
- Really?
Where?
You always wanted to be a firefighter.
Right?
You remember.
Yeah, that was before I realise
I'm scared of heights.
So, you've had a good life, huh?
What makes you say that?
Mm, Bor'ka say you've
been all over world.
Is that why you became pilot?
So you could travel?
Sure.
- I missed you.
- [SIGHS]
You really don't remember Dad?
What was he like?
Funny.
Strong.
Taught me how to fight.
He was much better.
Than what?
- She was mean.
- You were mean.
You were annoying.
I beat the crap out of sofa
so I don't beat the crap out of people.
You think that's weird?
Just beat the crap out of people.
It will make you feel a lot better.
Did you think we were dead too?
That's what orphanage told you.
How they say we die?
Car crash.
[LIVELY MUSIC]
This is the greatest
golubtsi you ever tasted.
What are they doing over there?
PYOTR: Annual festival tomorrow.
We host for the local villagers.
It's so great.
You'll have lots of fun, I promise.
You can't promise that.
Everyone have fun at
festival. You'll see.
Don't you want to get out?
Mum needs me.
- For what?
- I'm not like you.
You were always strong.
Being strong is a choice.
Don't stay here for her.
She wants to control you.
She's not a bad woman.
People here say she's saint.
People here don't know her.
Why did you come, Oksana?
'Cause I had the hiccups.
[SIGHS AND SNIFFS]
What are you doing?
Having a moment.
Look, it's me and sister having lunch.
Uh...
Nadege has been cooking
for me since I was a kid.
Nadege enters her piroshki every year
and has won the last...
19 years.
Wow.
You know Bor'ka is entering
a piroshki this year?
He wants the prize money.
I'm terrified.
And I am going to help him.
But you are shit at cooking.
- I know, but he needs help.
- [LAUGHS]
Are you weird arsehole like him?
VILLANELLE: Weirder.
- [LAUGHS]
Bozhe moy...
[CHUCKLES]
[DOOR CREAKS]
MAN: [ON TV] Armstrong said
moving in the lunar gravity
was easier than the simulations.
And once Aldrin joined Armstrong...
FEDYA: You see this?
Giant leap for mankind was in Nevada.
They're trying to fool us, you know?
- Who?
- Them.
All of them.
They never even went to space.
You know why? 'Cause they
don't want us to know
that the earth is flat.
Ha!
Ha-ha-ha!
MAN: [ON TV] ... while working...
You serious?
Do you think this funny?
[LAUGHS]
FEDYA: There is secret organization
that make influence on
every government in world.
And they will cause downfall
of planet and you won't laugh.
And you know that in every, um...
[MUTTERS IN RUSSIAN]
... the intelligence agency, yes?
- Yeah.
- FSB. DGSE. MI6.
All have people working
for this organization.
YULA: And you know what they are?
Lizards.
FEDYA: This man in England, David Icke.
- You know David Icke?
- Of course.
- Very smart man.
- Very.
- Knows many things.
- YULA: See?
We blow your mind.
MAN: [ON TV] ... the United
States and the United Nations.
- [THUDDING NEARBY]
- These lunar samples...
[RUSSIAN POP MUSIC PLAYS]
[GRUNTING]
Glupyy! Glupyy! Glupyy! Glupyy!
PYOTR:
How many grams is an ounce?
[TAPS PHONE KEYBOARD]
28.35.
Hmm.
And what the hell do I do with that?
VILLANELLE: That looks like shit.
- I'm screwed.
- You totally are.
SONG: ♪ Nothing matters
if you bury it deep ♪
♪ Take away the worry ♪
- ♪ What's left, you keep... ♪
- [SNIFFS]
♪ Never say you're sorry
if what you need is... ♪
Wow.
[SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
How many times have you been married?
Three.
Three?
Yeah.
Which one was your favourite?
Come on.
You must have liked one the most.
Tatiana is my wife now.
- I love her.
- She never used to be like this.
She was different.
It sounds like you were different too.
Mm!
So, she told you about me?
Yes.
What did she say?
She said...
she had a daughter who die.
She was very sad about you.
If that is what you want to know.
What did she say I was like?
She said you were difficult child.
Did she tell you she dumped me?
Yeah.
It was very hard time for her.
You know how many things
she had to deal with.
She still doesn't tell me everything.
But she... cries every night.
She had a...
... sadness in her heart.
Maybe she feels like dirt for
letting her family down.
I brought you tea.
Hey.
[GROANS]
Spasiba, moya dorogaya.
I have something for you.
It was mine from '80s.
I adjust for your size.
I think I got size right.
You like it?
I love it.
[FESTIVE RUSSIAN MUSIC PLAYS]
[CHATTER IN RUSSIAN]
Spasiba.
[GUNSHOTS]
[GUNSHOT]
Mm-hm. Spasiba.
[HORN HONKS]
[CHEERING]
[RAPID COMMENTARY IN RUSSIAN]
[SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
- [LAUGHS]
- [APPLAUSE]
[SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
[CHEERS]
[ANGRILY] Vali otsyuda!
Tan', ya tebe zvyaku, da?
['KAROBOTSCHKA' BY TIBOR BORNAI PLAYS]
[ANNOUNCER SPEAKS
RUSSIAN ON LOUDSPEAKER]
... Nadege!
[ANNOUNCER CONTINUES IN
RUSSIAN ON LOUDSPEAKER]
['KAROBOTSCHKA' CONTINUES]
[INAUDIBLE]
[BELLS RING]
This place is wonderful.
Is this your dance group?
Performance troupe.
- And we're called All Around.
- Mm.
- Is that because you all get around?
- [LAUGHS]
- [MAN SPEAKS RUSSIAN ON LOUDSPEAKER]
- [INAUDIBLE]
[LAUGHS]
[BELLS RING]
[WOMAN SPEAKS RUSSIAN ON LOUDSPEAKER]
[FLY BUZZES]
[SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
[GRUNTS]
- [YELLS]
- [APPLAUSE]
Yes!
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
[GRANDIOSE MUSIC PLAYS]
[WOMAN SPEAKS RUSSIAN ON LOUDSPEAKER]
- [GASPS]
- [ALL CHEER]
[PYOTR SHOUTS TRIUMPHANTLY IN RUSSIAN]
- [LAUGHS]
- PYOTR: Whoo-hoo!
[CHEERFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
[CHEERING]
[SINGING IN RUSSIAN]
You don't want to dance?
I am bad at dancing. [LAUGHS]
Me too.
Pyotr was right.
[LAUGHS]
This is fun.
Don't do that.
I should never have entered.
Elton John isn't going anywhere.
It's his farewell tour.
Watch it on YouTube.
It's really not a big deal.
- I embarrassed family.
- Don't be silly.
I did. Mum said I did.
- When?
- After I lost.
She came up to me and
said I was stupid and...
... and embarrassed her and...
[GRUNTS]
You are freaking me out.
Eat this.
Be quiet.
[SOMBRE ELECTRONIC MUSIC]
SONG: ♪ Just as time ♪
♪ You float by ♪
♪ I see darkness in you ♪
♪ Close my eyes... ♪
[INAUDIBLE]
♪ Wonder why ♪
♪ I see darkness in you ♪
♪ I see darkness in you... ♪
Oksana?
♪ I see shadows here ♪
♪ Don't know why... ♪
[GROWLS]
[SIGHS]
Come on.
That used to make you laugh.
No, it didn't.
Okay, then. Dad laughed.
- I remember someone...
- He didn't.
You are wasting food.
- It's tomato paste.
- You are wasting our food.
I could buy 10,000 tomatoes.
Am I supposed to be impressed by that?
- 20,000.
- [LAUGHS]
You always laugh at
things that aren't funny.
Like you?
Yes. [LAUGHS]
Clean your face.
Can you do it?
You're not a child.
I want to feel like one.
Please. [LAUGHS]
Can you do it?
I want you to leave the house.
No.
- No.
- You leave tomorrow.
I don't want you to be here anymore.
Why?
- This is my home.
- No, darling.
[TOSSES CLOTH]
You're not a part of this family.
You do not belong here.
What are you going to do?
Take me to the orphanage?
Easier to carry a trusting
little girl out of this house
than it will be to carry me.
Especially after the last two days.
Don't pretend you were an angel.
Don't pretend that you were a mother.
Or a wife.
Oh!
You'll not bring your
darkness into this house.
[VILLANELLE SCOFFS]
You are the darkness.
You have always been the darkness.
He wasn't scared of me.
He was sick of you.
He knew I could see what you are.
What's that?
Like me.
[LAUGHS]
I have killed a lot of people.
I was not a happy person.
- You were never a happy person.
- [LAUGHS]
That's not true.
- Again.
That's not funny.
You were bad from the beginning.
You didn't cry as a baby.
Please.
Some bullshit myth to
make you feel better.
I did cry.
I did cry!
You ruined me.
You took everything from me.
You took him.
You could control him.
He would do anything for you
because you had a darkness!
This dar... darkness!
He thought you would do something to us.
To me.
I didn't mind that you took me there.
I didn't mind that you
never came back for me.
What I mind...
... is that you won't
admit what you are.
That I am my mother's daughter.
Get out of my house.
[SIGHS]
I...
I j...
[SIGHS] I think I need
to kill you... Mama.
[PIANO INTRO TO 'SPIRITUAL
(NEGRO SONG)' BY MAGMA PLAYS]
- [MAGMA SING 'SPIRITUAL' IN FRENCH]
- [GAS HISSES]
[LIGHTER STRIKES]
[ALARM BEEPS]
[ALARM STOPS]
['SPIRITUAL' CONTINUES IN FRENCH]
[YELLS]
[PANTS ANGRILY]
[UNSETTLING SOMBRE MUSIC]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC BUILDS]
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --