How was your meeting
with Helene?
To Villanelle.
The keeper.
She's moving up
in the world.
You can't beat us.
You understand?
Are you working for them,
Paul?
Are YOU,
Carolyn?
- What did you want with my child?
- She kissed me!
Geraldine kissed you?
Irina.
Be ready.
Your plan to get out. I'm in.
- I'm done with it. I'm leaving.
- What do you mean, you're leaving?
I don't want to do this anymore.
♪ Fell into the fire, falling
♪ Flames of desire are calling
♪ Fell into the fire... ♪
Villanelle.
Finally.
That guy was really staring
at me.
This is Rhian.
Nice collection.
What are you doing?
Working out how I'd kill you.
I thought killing wasn't really
your thing at the moment.
You want to test that theory?
You're only as good as your last.
Go on, tell me. How would you do it?
I don't know yet, but it would
definitely involve the tiny chair.
Sit down.
Not on that one.
Show me. Your injury.
Here.
Do you know
why I love you, Villanelle?
Because you're an agent of chaos.
And I love chaos.
Chaos disrupts.
It rips apart and starts again.
It's like a forest fire.
It burns. It clears.
It's monstrous, but it's beautiful.
You're a beautiful monster,
Villanelle.
A monster?
Monstrous people
like you often
feel like
they have to fly solo,
like they have to keep things
bottled up inside them
thoughts, feelings... secrets.
And that can affect their ability
to be truly monstrous.
Do you have anything you would like
to get off your chest, Villanelle?
Has something happened recently?
I did something bad
to my mother.
Whatever it is, you can tell me.
I don't want us
to keep secrets from each other.
I took a shit in her shoe
when I was three.
A really big one.
Give me another job.
You're injured.
I'll take Dasha.
OK, but success is essential.
Otherwise, what's the point
of sending you and not Rhian?
Thank you
for the inappropriate touching.
It's actually pretty nice.
You wouldn't be able to, by the way.
Wouldn't be able to what?
Kill me before I killed you.
You're a child. You have no idea
what you're dealing with.
God, you're sexy.
♪ I don't like your little game
♪ Don't like your tilted stage
♪ I don't like you
*KILLING EVE*
Season 03  Episode 07
♪ I got smarter,
I got harder in the nick of time
♪ Honey, I rose up from the dead
I do it all the time
♪ Look what you made me do
♪ Look what you just made me do
♪ What you made me do
Episode Title: "Beautiful Monster"
Aired on: May 24, 2020
Captions by Red Bee Media
Sync corrections by srjanapala
♪ No, I don't like you. ♪
Three trips to Waitrose
and an abortive
attempt at hot yoga?
It's just
standard white-person stuff.
I've been tracking him
for a week
and there's nothing to suggest
he's working for The Twelve,
unless they've branched out into, uh,
groceries and hot vinyasa.
Jokes are for people
who do their jobs correctly, Mo.
So are omelettes.
- Do you want me to make up evidence?
- No!
I want you to uncover
the evidence that already exists,
which you haven't
worked hard enough to expose.
Thank you.
I know you're upset
about Kenny,
that we haven't found out
what happened to him.
Your powers of deduction
are incredible.
But are you sure
Paul's a member of The Twelve?
A bottle of chablis,
a stir-fry kit and a bath bomb.
What does that say to you?
That he's planning
a lovely evening in?
Or that he's trying to seem
that he is.
Trust me. That vintage of chablis
is undrinkable.
Off you go.
Another young person inspired?
Don't complain.
I've saved you his omelette.
Villanelle
has been promoted.
Dasha told me as much.
That should be our focus for now.
Oh, dear.
You don't deserve it after all.
Villanelle is rising up the ranks.
She is our best chance
of getting to them.
Oh, Eve,
what a blinkered approach.
Do you ever think
of anything else?
Don't pretend that
I'm the only one.
You have your own thing going on
with Villanelle.
For all I know,
you have a direct line.
Isn't it time you told me?
What was it you said to her
in that prison?
I offered her work and she refused.
Hmm.
Good for her.
Eve, I won't have
my investigation derailed
by your undiagnosed,
and, frankly,
a little trying,
Messiah complex.
Wow. Wow. I'M the one
with the Messiah complex.
Carolyn, why did we start this,
any of it?
Information,
intelligence gathering,
to compile
a comprehensive Filofax
of despots,
maniacs and extremists
in case we want to throw
a Christmas bash.
I mean, that's what we do,
isn't it?
No, it might have been once,
but not now.
Not after
everything that's happened,
after everything we've lost.
Eve, you'd do well to remember...
...heroes only get the girl
in Hollywood.
SPEAKS FOREIGN LANGUAGE...
MAN SPEAKS FOREIGN LANGUAGE...
Is it over?
Can we go now?
Your daughter is extremely bright.
Believe me,
it's a nightmare.
Getting told "Go eat a dick"
in Icelandic!
She is also manipulative,
calculating.
- Almost entirely lacking in empathy.
- Like her mother.
When I ask her about the accident
involving your ex-wife's partner,
she said she wished
she could go back in time
so she could reverse back
over his body.
Kids' imagination, huh?
It's wild!
This is not
a joking matter.
Who is joking?
10% off your first massage
at The Ritz-Carlton.
Great!
The only straight pencil-pusher
in Moscow? What do you want?
You need to take Irina's symptoms
seriously.
I DO take them seriously.
Look at my face.
I take them
very, extremely seriously.
Now, can you
discharge her, please?
- It's not in my power.
- You sign for her
and she walks! Right?
It will take us several weeks.
We have a holiday booked!
Do you want to sit down?
No.
Your daughter isn't going anywhere
for quite some time.
She's a very disturbed child.
Where IS it?
I know you're in here somewhere.
Is this one of those moments
we pretend never happened?
Ew! Who recycles boxer shorts?!
Will you help me?
I don't know. I mean, are you
gonna tell me WHY you're in the bin?
'Cause I don't want to enable
a mental health crisis.
I'm looking for my birthday cake.
You know, I could just give you
money for a croissant.
Might be easier,
bit more dignified.
I obviously
don't want to eat it, Bear!
I'm... I'm trying
to find the box it came in
so I can see the bakery
it was ordered from.
Right. Right. Got it.
Oh, my God! Oh!
I found it!
What's this really about, Eve?
- Villanelle sent me that cake.
- Oh, shit.
Jamie, what happened?
We got raided.
- By who? Who... who raided us?
- The police.
Came with a warrant
this morning.
Something about
the Official Secrets Act.
Something about obtaining data
illegally. I don't know.
Colluding with foreign criminals
on the dark web.
Do we do that?
We don't NOT do that.
Does this mean I'm out of a job?
'Cause this is the only place
I've ever worked where people
don't talk about me
behind my back.
Yeah, that's what YOU think.
Honestly...
I don't know what it means.
I just need a moment
to process this.
No. No, you don't.
We don't have time for this.
Bear, do you have your laptop?
Get it out. We've got work to do.
What are you gonna do?
Google "How to bring down
a global crime syndicate"?
No! I'm gonna Google
a bakery in North London.
Bear.
- Don't get involved, mate.
- Why not?
It's not like
I have a job anymore, so...
Well, I'm gonna start drinking.
SHOUTS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE...
This place is amazing.
Look what someone just gave me.
It's a shank
made out of a toothbrush.
Don't take anything from anyone.
Don't make eye contact with anyone.
If someone tries to talk to you,
walk away.
- What are you doing?
- You're trying to talk to me.
Don't wander off.
There are children here
who would kill you
and wear your skin as pashmina.
Oh, my God, Dad.
I know what you're trying to do,
but your performance
is way over-the-top.
You're, like, up here
when you need to be here.
You know,
you should read some Stanislavski.
- I'm not acting.
- Exactly!
You're OVER-acting. You need to
mobilise your subconscious.
Tone all this down a little.
It's too much.
Listen to me.
I am leaving you here.
No, you're trying to scare me.
Standard parent crap.
You're doing the whole,
"If you don't stop running over
your mother's boyfriends,
"look where you'll end up" schtick.
You're so transparent!
If you hadn't been so
damn stupid,
we'd both be
lying on a beach right now!
So you're actually leaving me here?
Just for a couple of days,
then I come back for you.
You're a liar.
I have to go to London
and show my face. I can't be here.
You're a liar.
Why are you
making this difficult?
I don't think you understand
the pressure I am under!
There are so many... many balls
in the air above my head
and they're all made of napalm!
I see you in two days.
Bastard!
Yes, I'll hold.
I can't believe I'm still here and
not halfway to cirrhosis in a pub.
Uh, you're here
because you know she's brilliant.
Yes, I know technically
it's not legal
to divulge
customers' personal information,
but it's not like anyone would...
find out.
You think SHE'S brilliant?
Maybe I should explain
why this cake meant so much.
You see, not long ago, my husband
was involved in a serious accident.
- And it's... it's...
- Hold up.
I've... I've...
I've got something here.
Thank God. Had no idea
where I was going with that.
Yeah, 'cause pitchfork to the neck
is such a cliche.
So these are
all the telephone orders
made in the days
before the cake arrived.
And you can see
the origin of the calls here.
So London, London, London,
Hertfordshire,
London, Essex, Reykjavik.
You know, I lost my virginity
in Reykjavik.
What?
Nothing.
Just surprised.
Surprised that it was in Reykjavik
or surprised that it happened?
Can we get back to it, please?
London, Barcelona.
There. Stop there.
Dasha Duzran has been
running Villanelle out of Barcelona.
That's got to be her.
Um...
...what about recent activity
on the card?
Can you get to that, Bear?
- Not legally.
- OK.
Do it anyway.
You can't get raided twice in a day.
It's a rule.
OK. Looks like it was used
just 20 minutes ago.
Where?
Aberdeen.
You look ridiculous.
It's my family tartan.
We agreed, German.
Germans don't wear kilts.
Yeah. I changed my mind.
So, here we are.
You ladies celebrating
something?
- Yes.
- No.
My promotion.
We are here on business.
My mother
has a funny sense of humour.
It's dementia.
Come on, Mother. Hurry up.
Doors closing.
You think you've won because
you've got your stinking promotion?
I was trying to be modest,
but if you're going
to force my hand, then...
You have not won. I have won. I've
done everything they asked me to do.
Ever since
they first dumped you on me,
when you had
little mosquito bites for breasts.
And now I get to go home.
Home.
Doors closing.
Do you know what's waiting for you
at home?
Vodka. Proper Russian vodka.
Indifference.
Do you think anyone in Russia
cares about a bendy KGB crone?
Russia has vegans now.
Did you know that?
You go into a restaurant,
you ask for a stroganoff,
they're going to laugh
in your face.
So what?
So what? I'm not interested
in hero's welcome.
And if I want stroganoff,
my son can make it for me.
Oh! You didn't know
I had a son?
Oh, maybe
I forgot to mention him.
I'm going to die
with my feet up and my hand held.
Whereas you, you have destroyed
any home you ever had.
And you're going to die alone.
Does your son have
your halitosis?
Well, you're funny.
I give you that.
No, seriously.
Can I have his number?
It's such an intoxicating scent.
Hi.
What is it
with everyone hiding in the dark?!
You want to send me
to an early grave?
I'm so sorry. I... I thought
it would be a nice surprise.
There's no such thing
as a nice surprise!
- How do you get in?
- You left a key with your neighbour.
How stupid of me!
Uh, here.
Have some water.
You look nice.
Oh...
I... I feel so stupid now.
I... I...
...I brought steak and wine.
I thought we could have a...
proper dinner together, but...
...maybe I should go.
It's not a great time.
Yeah, I should go.
I sh... I should...
...I should never have, erm...
Uh...
...I guess Mum's been
extra difficult recently
and I... I just wanted
to get away for a night.
I...
...I think she's on the verge
of discovering something big and...
...you know how she is when
she's got the bit between her teeth.
Anyway.
Stupid.
What kind of steak?
Uh...
...fillet mignon.
I do like fillet mignon.
You bastard!
What?! I said I liked it.
Mum said you were trying to play me
and I didn't believe her.
Can we do this another time?
And let you disappear
into the ether?
I won't disappear into the ether.
OK, I WILL disappear into the ether.
But you have to understand,
it's not personal.
Not personal?!
Shh! Inside voices.
I will make as much noise
as I like!
Just once, I want to make a scene
and not be told to be quiet
or to pull myself together
or that I'm being ridiculous!
- Fine.
- Seeking out someone
whose brother has just died,
taking advantage
of their grief
when they're at their
most vulnerable,
what kind of person
does that?
A shit.
I'm a shit. OK?
I used you
to spy on your mother.
Happy?
I hope you die.
It's very possible.
I am going to miss this.
Looking like a prophylactic
that can't play golf?
Killing people.
That feeling you get the moment
before you snuff out a life.
When you can see your own eyes
reflected in dilated pupils,
when you can count the number of
breaths they have left on one hand.
Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
Ha-ha! Whoo-hoo!
He's crying out to be killed.
- OK.
- Ugh!
I killed so many Americans
in Cold War
you could make
giant greasy tapestry out of them.
They were less fat then,
but just so loud.
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Whoo! Yeah!
Oh, yeah.
You can do it if you like.
Kill him?
One of us has to do it.
If it means so much to you,
you can do it. Hm?
Look at it
as my retirement present.
- You have lost it, haven't you?
- What?
Yeah, you have lost it.
You want me to kill him
because you are afraid
you won't be able to do it again.
Oh, boy. This is priceless.
I tell you one thing.
I'm glad that they agreed
to send me home
before they realised
they had promoted a dud.
Get out of my way, please.
Whoops!
I got the train
down to London couple of years back.
Me and the wife are big fans of
true-crime walking tours, you see,
and if you want to get the most
serial killer bang for your buck,
the capital is the only place to be,
you know.
Jack the Ripper, Dennis Nilsen,
John Christie.
Ah, we've done 'em all.
You ever tried one?
What? Oh. Uh, no, I don't think so.
Och, you must. Aye, sure.
Some people have a problem with the
glorification of the violence, etc,
but me and the wife, we love it.
Not in real life, you understand.
No, no, no.
We're really very law-abiding.
I mean, I don't even kill spiders.
- Yep?
- Bear. Am... am I in the right place?
Um...
- ...Castle Stuart?
- Yeah.
Sure this is the last place
- the card was used?
- Positive.
Hey! They're coming.
Hey!
- Hi.
- Hey!
Oh, yeah, pull over here.
Excuse me! Sir?
Will you help me get my ball?
My mother's frail
and unsteady on her feet
and we don't want to
go into the woods alone.
Catch you later.
Sure.
Deal's off.
I'm doing this one.
You know,
some girls would stop themselves
asking for help from a man
these days.
They do it
as a matter of principle.
Oof! Not me.
I was brought up in a family where
men were men and women were women
and women liked their men to be men.
Aye. That's how we did it.
Damn right.
And that's why I don't have a
problem promoting women to my board.
Because your lack of know-how
gives me an excuse to feel heroic.
I'm only joking, natch.
What do you say in this country?
Don't get your knickers in a twist.
No, no. You got it in one.
I can't tell you the amount of times
I've gone to hit the ball
and hit something else entirely!
It's just in here somewhere.
OK.
Oh, I think I see it!
It's just
in that patch of ferns over there.
- Allow me.
- Oh!
Isn't this wonderful, Mum?
The kind gentleman's
getting the ball for us.
It's playing hard to get.
Do they not have belts in America?
Ugh.
Three...
...two...
...one.
There you go!
Oh!
Oh, God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Stuff that
in your fanny pack and eat it!
Oh, my God!
What are you waiting for? Run!
I didn't care much for London,
it must be said.
Too busy for my liking.
Too dangerous.
I always feel safe round here.
How about you? How do you find
our wee part of the world?
Jesus Christ!
- Oh, my God!
- Let him in!
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
Oh, my God!
- What happened?
- There's a crazy woman on the loose!
- What does she look like?
- Why? Why? What does that matter?
- What does she look like?!
- I just saw a pretty face.
Pretty girl. Nice figure.
- She was with her mom.
- Her mother?
Yeah. She hit her mom in the head
with a golf club.
- OK, where was this?
- What?!
Where was this?!
I don't know. Uh, 16th hole.
About half a mile that way.
OK, get out.
What?!
Get out! Get out! Get out!
What is this vile country?!
Get out, get out, get out!
Drive to the 16th hole, now!
♪ I'm stuck here
♪ No way out
♪ Back, you can never go
♪ Back, you can never go back
No, no, no... ♪
What took you so long?
You were supposed to be here
hours ago.
I don't want to talk about it.
Where are we going?
To get my money.
♪ ..Never go back, no, no, no
♪ No yawning
♪ Smile for me
♪ Back, you can never go
Back, you can never go... ♪
Dasha.
Where is she?
Mous...
...moustache.
I can't... I can't hear you.
Say it again.
Mousta...
He has... lovely moustache.
Like Stalin.
♪ I see darkness in you... ♪
♪ I see shadows here... ♪
Carolyn, it's me.
Call me back when you get this.
I found the thing
linking Thingy to The Thingy,
you know, Paul to The Twelve?
OK, I'm gonna make myself
an omelette to celebrate.
Omelette, run a bath,
put a bath bomb in it.
♪ You float by
♪ I see darkness in you... ♪
The FSB wants to kill me.
The Twelve want to kill me.
Carolyn's daughter wants to kill me.
My ex-wife wants to kill me.
My daughter wants to kill me.
My ex-wife's new boyfriend
would want to kill me
if he wasn't already dead!
Look where you're going, idiot!
That random guy
now wants to kill me.
I thought you didn't want
to talk about it.
I don't.
Well, I'm hearing a lot of
something that sounds like talking
for someone who
"don't want to talk about it".
I think I'm just
really, really tired.
Ugh. Up your magnesium.
Maybe I shouldn't go.
Oh! Are you serious?
Maybe I should
just let them kill me.
Wow!
Bring the mood down,
why don't you?
What I am going to do
in Cuba anyway?
I burn like that!
Read books on the beach.
Smoke cigars.
Get your legs out.
Don't get murdered.
Wherever I go,
someone wants to murder me.
I can run as far as I want -
they will still come!
Ha! I probably deserve it.
You definitely deserve it.
This way, you can get murdered
in a cute Havana shirt.
Let's face it, Villanelle.
I'm a prick.
And the only thing I'm
waiting for is another prick to...
...another prick to...
Shit!
Another prick to shit?
What is that?
Are you faking it?
Get up! Get up.
Oh! You can't die on me now.
Oh! How do we get the money?
Where is the money?
I don't want to die.
I'll come back for you, I promise.
- But I need the money.
- My pocket.
I don't want to die.
Shut up!
I don't want you to die either.
I really don't.
But you actually might.
MAN SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY OVER P.A....
No, he just collapsed.
Can anyone help?
I know him.
OK.
Konstantin!
Has anyone called
an ambulance?
They're on their way.
Konstantin.
Where is she?
♪ I once
♪ Had a love
♪ Or did love
♪ Have me?
♪ It
♪ Set me free... ♪
Perfect place for a yoga mat.
Geraldine!
I'm going to get a takeaway,
and it's terribly un-cost-effective
for one person,
so you're going to
have to come in on it.
I don't know
what kind of thing you find...
...acceptable to eat nowadays,
but I'm sure that...
...Hampstead will provide.
- What's the matter with you?
- Nothing. What's the matter with you?
Nothing. You're ordering a takeaway?
Don't argue with me.
We're celebrating.
A weasel that I thought was a weasel
turns out to be...
- A weasel?
- Yeah. Well done.
I don't mind.
Uh, anything vegetarian.
Of course.
Uh, I'm going to order upstairs
and then I'm going to run a bath
while we're waiting.
That's the kind of self-care
you're always advocating, isn't it?
Hugh. This better be good.
I'm about to have a bath.
Mum, the bath's overflowing!
- Did you turn it off?
- Of course I turned it off.
There's two inches of water
all over the floor!
You're not really OK, are you?
Don't be ridiculous. I've had
some disappointing news, that's all.
- Nothing to get het up about.
- Well, what was it?
The news.
I can't say.
His family haven't been informed yet.
Mum, did someone die?
Don't look so shocked,
Geraldine.
It's not like Kenny.
He wasn't a
member of the public.
He was... fully briefed.
He knew the risks.
It was Mo.
I fear the walls
may be closing in on me.
It's starting to feel personal.
Why didn't you tell me?
You said it was
nothing to get het up about.
How can you be so bloody calm?
What is wrong with you?!
You're an emotional iceberg!
I'm sorry.
I-I'm...
...I'm sorry.
Don't... come at me like that.
I'm not... coming at you.
I'm trying to hug you.
Just don't.
Mum!
I'm warning you, Geraldine.
This isn't healthy.
It can't go on.
You can't... just refuse to feel
anything for the rest of your life.
What... what kind of existence
is that?
You... you have to find some way
to express yourself!
Is that the kind of thing
you were after?
We've put
in a stent to unblock your artery,
but we'll need to look
at some lifestyle changes.
Have you been under
any increased stress lately?
- Mr Vasiliev?
- Yeah.
Heart attacks are associated
with greater levels of cortisol
in the blood.
Is there anything
that's been bothering you?
- Mr Vasiliev?
- Yes.
♪ I see you
You see me
♪ And I say yes, but my heart stops
♪ You're looking
right through me... ♪
Jesus Christ!
♪ Beside myself, I better not... ♪
Hello?
We have to stop
running into each other like that.
It's not good for both of us.
Demolition girl by billy childish
and holly golightly plays..,
♪ Demolition girl
♪ Demolition girl... ♪
Captions by Red Bee Media
Sync corrections by srjanapala